Something a bit more upbeat.
This is it.
Maybe the tempo should be a little faster.
Oh, that's nice.
The drums carve out the rhythm.
The melody stirs my emotions
and the words come spilling out.
The moment when you find yourself going,
"Oh, that's nice."
That excitement sends you through the air.
It's past midnight...
Wait, wait, wait! What am I doing?!
I have to study! Study!
I guess you can't simply layer them.
So maybe this would be better
if it were a little quieter.
Study!
This unfinished beat covers the night
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
Embracing us before we're crushed
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
There will be change
If you just reach out
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
In a world where nothing changes
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
We have to live through it
kyou datte ikite yukunda
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
We've already started walking
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
uso mitaina baka mitaina
This hopeless city of ours
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
But I still saw it with my own eyes
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Embracing us before we're crushed
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
There will be change
If you just reach out
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
MISALIGNED QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS
Ah! No!
Shh!
I'm sorry.
The pigeon was on the rhythm...
No!
I've barely made it past the first page.
It's like I wasted the whole day.
Oh, a guitar.
Did she have an acoustic guitar too?
Excuse me.
Hey, Nina! Welcome!
Did you eat already?
Not yet.
You want meat buns? Meat buns!
That's bad manners!
I knew you were a rich girl.
Sauce on meat buns?
It's real good.
Oh, a friend from school works
in Chinatown and brought back extras.
I see...
Is it good?
Yes, it's tasty.
Good, I'm glad.
So, about our first song.
Did you finish it?
I wish it were that easy.
Oh, then why did you call us over?
This is pretty far for me, you know.
I thought we should talk about
what kind of song we want.
I'm having a hard time picturing
what fits the three of us the best.
I don't care as long as
I can bang the drums.
What about you?
Yes, it's tasty!
I taught you how to use this app
only a week ago, right?
And you made this already?
Wow!
Momoka said I could just write by ear
instead of learning how to read music.
So, you know.
But the fact that
this song is so well-made means...
you spent over
eight hours a day on it, right?
Huh? Where are you going?
-I'm going home.
-What?!
I have to study! I have to study!
I was right on the mark.
It's your fault for showing me this app!
You said it wouldn't affect my studies!
This isn't my fault.
I know that.
Then don't say it.
But...
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry for showing it to you.
I'll uninstall it, so just sing...
You don't need to do that.
Which is it?!
It's my fault!
I just need to shift my focus
and leave the band to you, right?!
Who are you talking to?
Myself!
I'll be back next week.
What is with her?
I don't get her at all.
I'm going home too then.
Hey! There's still meat buns left.
You can have them all.
Bye!
Nina!
Let's walk together.
Sure.
It's impressive,
being able to make a song just like that.
I couldn't do it.
Um, but I only just
followed some tutorials.
But I know I wouldn't be able to come up
with any lyrics.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Um, I need to stop by
the convenience store.
What? I'll come with you.
No, but I'll probably
just walk home after.
I see.
Okay. See you.
Subaru, too?
Why can't you just go yourself?
I have a shift scheduled at my job.
You can't go?
I mean, I could, but...
Nina, it can be after school.
Just take it to her.
For the meat buns.
This is that famous place...
Seriously?
A country bumpkin.
Which way?
Hmm.
This way?
I guess not.
Found it.
Excuse me.
May I help you?
Y-Yes!
Is Ms. Awa here?
Ms. Awa?
Oh, Subaru!
Hey, Subaru!
For that act,
we can just go with the flow.
Oh, Nina!
What happened?
Did you find this place okay?
I would've come to get you
if you called the school.
I'm sorry I took so long.
Here.
Thanks!
You forgot your phone?
Yeah.
I'm such a ditz.
Anyway, they're waiting for you there.
-Okay.
-Later.
Have a nice day!
You're free after this, right?
Let's grab some food.
My treat.
I have to go home and study.
Okay, how about this weekend then?
Like Sunday?
Really, it's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Well, goodbye.
Should I quit?
Should I quit the band?
I'm not stupid. I know you're avoiding me.
Um, I...
I'm not trying to get in your way.
There are other bands.
No, it's not anything like that.
I'm just...
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Are you sure?
Yes, I can always study later.
Or whenever.
No, I meant about me.
I mean, I only started playing music
in middle school,
so I don't have much authority.
But bandmates tend to be close since they
have to come together to make one thing.
And when there's a difference in opinions,
you can't just ignore it.
If you just try to gloss it over,
there's bound to be a misunderstanding.
So you should speak up
if there's something you don't like.
It's not that I don't like you.
It's all my fault.
Stop doing that.
I'm used to being hated.
No, that's not it!
I kind of tend to keep my distance,
so people often
make an effort to interact with me.
What? You don't like that?
I don't hate it.
But when people approach me
to be their friend, for some reason,
I'm like "You think I'm just going to
to be that easy?"
I can't help but think that...
What a pain.
So that's why you dropped out of
high school, huh?
No, that was...
Wait, she told you?
Yeah.
Must be nice looking down at me.
Listen!
You've got the wrong idea about me!
For your information,
I may go to acting school,
but it doesn't give you
a high school diploma!
I'm basically like you!
But you're striving to be an actor!
That means you're chasing your dream!
You can proudly tell people that!
That's what you're misunderstanding.
Do you know her?
I think I've seen her before.
The Detective Granny Case Files.
They play reruns around noon.
Oh...
She's my grandma.
What?
She's a real nag.
She told me to follow in her footsteps
and arranged for me
to go to acting school.
So what about being an actor?
I'm not really trying to be one.
But you're still going to acting school?
Yeah. It makes me hate myself.
Seems stupid when I'm not trying
to be one.
But nobody around me seems to see that.
They just assume that I'm trying to be one
because of my family.
Then what about the band?
Just my way of gently pushing back.
I didn't just want to be in the drama club
back in junior high.
So I joined the band club
since I liked bands,
and it was pretty fun.
I even secretly joined a band once.
Your grandma doesn't know?
I couldn't tell her.
Oh, did you see Hachiko?
Won't they call us country bumpkins?
Who cares? You are one anyway.
This is in exchange for
me opening up to you.
We're friends now!
Girls Band Cry.
SUNDAY NOON
A street show?
Yeah, I figured that would be
a good start.
I've already reserved a spot
for the weekend.
I thought we were going to record
and upload a video first?
Yeah, we'll do that too.
But I feel like a live show
is the right call,
especially for this trio.
A live show?
That picture you sent made me think
the two of you are like
oozing with misery and discontent.
How rude!
Yeah!
But that's exactly why
I reached out to the both of you.
What do you think, Nina?
It bothers me a little.
But I guess I can see her point.
Can we play without a bass, though?
Nina can't play, right?
It's an amateur event. We'll make it work.
And we also have this.
What's that?
A looper.
You put in sound like this.
See?
Wow.
Wait, by a street show,
do you mean in front of a crowd?
Obviously.
I mean, you came to see me perform...
-Huh?
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Cut it out!
Let go! We never talked about this!
Calm down!
You sang in front of the station.
It's the same as that.
It's not that easy!
I don't have any experience.
Don't worry, when worse comes to worst,
I'll do something.
Then you should sing instead!
You're way better than me anyway!
Then will you play the guitar?
You know I can't!
I told you. I want to hear you sing.
Why?
You'll see if you sing. Just trust me.
I'm going home.
So you're quitting the band then?
What?!
Yes, thank you for everything!
Hey!
It'll be okay.
That's so unfair,
holding the band hostage!
Your logic's not adding up.
-But I--
-Stop being scared.
Whether it goes well or not,
whether you succeed or fail,
you're going to regret it either way.
Because that's who you are.
That's...
The truth.
Then you might as well go all out
and sing what you're feeling right now.
Am I wrong?
Okay. You lose.
Shut up, Subaru!
Put that anger into your singing.
That's how you really feel.
They've got a nice set here!
Plus, it's the cheapest rate around here.
Let's see.
Seems good.
Nina, did you learn the song I sent you?
I added the part you composed as well.
Yes.
-Then let's try running it.
-Huh?
What did you think we were going to do?
It's way too sudden!
I told you not to be scared.
It's practice. It's gonna suck.
We're gonna fail.
Here.
Slowly.
One, two, three, four.
How was that?
I have goosebumps.
I got them all over!
-Aww.
-Hm?
You fell right for Momoka's trap.
Once you know this feeling,
you can never quit.
But why?
Humans have a gene
that make them move to sounds.
Music and dance are human instincts.
Right?
Yeah.
What is it?
Just thinking how good your voice sounds.
Really?
Yeah, I got goosebumps too.
Okay, let's sing.
Okay!
One medium bowl and a beer.
A medium bowl, no onions.
A medium bowl.
You're so hoarse!
You both told me to sing hard.
But who sings to that point though?
Shut up.
"Thank you very much."
It should be back to normal by tomorrow,
but take care of your voice.
Are you a trio?
I saw your guitar case.
Come check us out.
Thank you.
SHINKAWASAKI (PLACEHOLDER)
So?
So what?
I could hand them ours too.
Only after we check them out.
Thank you for the food.
I should get going.
Go where?
My job.
Later.
She treated us again tonight.
The beef bowls and the karaoke box.
What is she looking at?
They're Momoka's former bandmates.
Look.
Today is our next band's
first live performance!
A three-piece girl band hailing
from Kawasaki!
Their name is...
Shinkawasaki?
We need to have a meeting
about the band name.
I said it's a placeholder.
Sorry I'm late.
Wait...
Are you wearing that on stage?
Is it bad?
I told you to bare your heart.
Get changed.
This is a band message.
I figured it'd be better
if it was an outfit you hated.
Don't overthink it.
Just express what you're really feeling.
Don't worry, I've got your back.
You're timid, but stubborn.
Cowardly, but confident.
You're a walking self-contradiction.
These aren't compliments!
Nina! It's almost time!
You've got so much angst
and energy built up inside you.
And that's...
rock and roll without a doubt.
Rock and roll?
Nobody knows who you are
and nobody will wait for you.
But that's what makes it interesting.
You're rock and roll, Nina.
If nothing changes
No matter how long I wait
Then there's nobody I can rely on
It's not as if the pain disappears
When you blame someone else
I pray to say goodbye
To cowering every day
Holding my knees to my chest
I don't even believe in God
Shut up (Shut up)
Leave me alone (Leave me alone)
A stranger sings
Until they lose their voice
Telling me that I'm not alone
I'm sure that to some people
Those words are enough
I don't know
I see
Was that right?
I forgot
It's all a pain
I want to break it
I don't have the courage
Someone hurry up and teach me
A reason to live
There are so many people to take my place
You can't just tell me to be myself
Take it back if it can be granted
I can dream all I want
There's still reality
Is anyone there?
This is...
amazing.
It's rock and roll.
Next episode, "Appreciation (Surprise)"