SAMPLE ITEM
SHINKAWASAKI (PLACEHOLDER)
T-shirts for sale!
T-SHIRTS 2,500 YEN
ONE SIZE FITS ALL!!
We also have towels!
SAMPLE
Thank you!
Thank...
That's why I told you
not to bother with merchandise.
Why did you make these when
we haven't even decided on a band name?
Well, I thought it could
help fund our activities.
What are we, a soccer team?
But I guess it might become valuable
if we become famous.
You're way too positive.
Hey!
Stop spacing out!
RUPA
THANK YOU FOR TODAY!!
I'm rooting for you!
I believe in you!
I'm coming to your next show too!
Yes, please do!
Wow, Rupa's so popular.
More importantly,
we need to decide on a band name.
Okay.
Got a second?
Yes?
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
A live show?
I'LL GIVE IT A NAME
Yeah. Someone who helped me
when I was starting out
asked if we wanted to play.
Where is it?
Suwa in Nagano.
We'll arrive the day before to rehearse.
The show will be the next night
then we'll head home right after,
so I can go do this by myself
if you're busy.
And I'm sure
you have studying to do, Nina.
I'll go.
-Okay?!
-Seriously?
We're still out of sync.
But the more shows we play the better.
Okay, if you say so, Rupa.
So we're in!
Okay.
Uh...
What?
What were we gonna do
about our band name again?
AT A LATER DAY
Just so you know,
I'm really quitting if it's Shinkawasaki.
I know.
I mean, we're aiming
to go professional as well.
Has Momoka said anything since?
No.
She didn't even say anything
about us really trying to go pro.
A cold war.
Why do you seem happy?
Momoka tends to make
snide comments to Nina.
Huh? Where's the lizard?
Gecko!
I temporarily moved it
because it wasn't feeling well.
What the hell?!
If she wants to say something,
then she should say it!
You're bothering the neighbors!
I think it's natural to assume she's mad
because you keep making decisions, Nina.
This was your idea.
Tehee.
Just so you know, if this is
going to be a fight, we're both out.
We don't have the time.
I know that. Geez...
So, what are we going to do
about the name of the band
whose members are all over the place?
-Do you have any ideas?
-What? Me?
You suggest one first!
Yeah! You should suggest one
before asking others!
What? I'm too embarrassed.
What if the three of you say it
at the same time?
If you say so, Rupa.
Okay, we say it together.
Okay.
Ready, and...
Dream Girl.
-Chocolate.
-Undine.
Ready, and...
Dream Girl.
-Chocolate.
-Undine.
It wouldn't be in katakana.
"Chocolate" in hiragana.
What a suggestion.
You stubborn Kumamoto girl.
It sounds cavity-inducing.
That's mean!
What did you say? "Undine"?
That's...
It's way more embarrassing than mine.
What?! Are you crazy?
They're both terrible.
Then what's yours?
Yeah, say it again.
Dream Girl.
Any progress?
I had no idea we'd have this much trouble.
That's because
you're being so picky, Subaru.
I'd like to say the exact same about you.
"Did you settle on a name?"
So annoying.
We basically wasted the entire day.
She's so late...
Sis!
You could've messaged me!
I wanted to surprise you.
But I didn't think you'd be this late.
I usually don't stay out this late.
Things just ran long today.
You got a boyfriend?
Are you doing something weird for money?
Then what?
A band.
What?
A band?
Yeah.
You? Really? Are you serious?
Do you have pictures?
I do.
Whoa, you're serious. Are you the singer?
Wow.
What's with this outfit?
That's...
rock and roll.
Rock and roll.
What's that?
What does it matter?
That's why your grades crashed.
How did you know that?
Your cram school reached out
after your grades dropped
and you kept missing a bunch of classes.
That's so unnecessary.
Just be thankful that
I stopped Dad from coming.
What will you tell him?
I'm leaving home.
That's fine,
but that means you'll never be
able to come home again.
You know, I do think Dad was in the wrong.
He was revered enough as a teacher
to have written about education.
he couldn't accept
his own daughter's truancy.
I know you must have been hurt.
But I also see where Dad's coming from.
At the very least,
if we had overlooked the bullying,
the school would've owed us.
You could've easily gotten
recommendations with your grades.
That's cheating.
Which is why you said you'd come here
and make it to college on your own, right?
But now you're abandoning that
and leaving home?
Even I can't support you on that.
DAYS LATER
Come on, hurry.
We have rehearsals tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Sorry I'm late!
What is all that?
Is something wrong?
Show me.
This and this...
The rest are clothes, right?
Leave everything else.
What?!
You have to pack as light as you can.
Now then.
The Chuo Expressway, right?
Then just go--
Quiet.
A manual transmission? That's rare.
I asked an acquaintance
and this was all they had.
Uh...
I think...
Oh, did that do it?
Who votes for a new driver?
Rupa, you're a great driver.
I used to drive at my last job.
We'll make a rest stop, so could you
drive all the way there?
You hate my driving that much?
I'll stop at a rest area if I get tired,
so you guys can all rest.
What? But we're all here together.
Want to play a game then?
If everyone raises their hand
to your question, you win.
For example...
Who likes cats better than dogs?
Wow, I'm surprised Tomo's a dog person.
They say cat-like people
tend to love dogs.
You're next, Nina.
Um...
Who has few friends?
Yes!
Don't end the game so fast!
Momoka's up next.
What? What a pain...
Fine. Who hates my driving?
DANGOZAKA
Let's take a break.
We'll be right back.
So cold!
Stop that!
Rock paper scissors!
When are we leaving again?
Excuse me.
What took you so long?
What is this?
Did you want something else?
I mean, it's fine.
Good.
Tomo...
why did you quit school?
Why are you asking?
Because I have nobody else to ask.
I didn't have time to waste there.
My parents were never around
so I knew I'd be on my own
after graduation.
Mom?
She was acting like someone else
with another man.
Seeing my mom like that,
it flipped a switch in me.
It's not rare to see singers
who are 18 or 20 years old these days.
So the earlier I start, the better.
Which is why I came to Tokyo
and recruited band members.
The time I had spent at school
seemed like a waste.
That's all.
Wow.
I never even thought like that.
Anybody would think like that
if they had nobody to rely on.
When Rupa lost her family
in an accident...
She said she thought about it.
I'm not on that level at all.
I've always wanted to do this.
Okay, smile!
Momoka, Tomo, smile a bit more please.
Okay. Say cheese, please.
We're like idols.
Shut up.
WELCOME TO THE LAND OF SUWA
FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
I know we're on a budget, but this is...
It's so hot.
So heavy.
Good morning.
Girls Band Cry.
SUWA FIREWORKS SHOW
PREVIOUS-PREVIOUS-PREVIOUS NIGHT FESTIVAL
That went well.
How?!
We weren't in sync!
What? You two are behind!
That's not possible!
You're both off.
More importantly, Subaru,
your neck is bent.
I know! I slept on it funny!
So this is your new band, Momo?
"Momo"?
Yes!
"Yes"?
Oh. My neck's fixed.
I won't say you're good,
but I don't hate it.
Better than being just a little good.
Sorry, we'll do our best
not to embarrass you.
Oh. That guitar...
Yeah, it's still the same one.
It still has the sticker you gave me. See?
She seems like
a completely different person.
I'm sure that's close to
how she used to be.
I want to play one song together
at the end.
Is that okay?
Are you sure?
You're okay with us?
I invited you because
I wanted to play with you.
So, are you guys in too?
What? O-Oh, yes.
Are you guys up for a jam session?
-Jam session?
-Basically to sing together.
You're the vocalist, right?
Yes.
Goodbye the melody of yesterday
Until we can meet again
We're growing up
Once more
Even if we've forgotten
-So?
-What?
-Can you sing it?
-Oh, yes.
Probably.
I'll do my best.
Okay, it's decided then.
I'll tell the owner.
-It's a good song, right?
-Yes!
When I moved to Tokyo,
I saw Mine's show and thought to myself...
She was like a bonus to the opening act.
But she stood firm
and fought with her song.
It was so rock and roll.
It's perfect for my last show.
I'm going to quit this band.
Tomorrow's show will be my last.
Then I'm out.
What are you talking about?
Sorry, but I don't feel like
I can carry this band to go pro.
Why not?
Because the songs I make
won't work on a professional level.
I'm happy that you like my songs.
And I'm grateful
that you've taken this seriously.
Thank you.
You're fine with that?
Yeah.
I'm fine with that.
NICHOME
Who knew you'd become such
a heavy drinker!
And you can hold your liquor, Rupa.
She loves drinking people under the table.
Do we have to carry her again?
She may not look it, but Momoka is heavy!
You'd better do the show
properly tomorrow.
You have to pay the audience respect.
I know that.
What's with the scary looks?
Are you guys fighting?
More importantly,
what kind of music do you like, Mine?
Have you ever thought about
quitting music before?
Where is this coming from?
You're being annoying.
She must not like coming to a conclusion.
The longer you do something,
the clearer the results become.
If it didn't go well the first time,
you can chalk it up to bad luck.
But a second time
may point to a lack of talent.
Can't she believe that it will go well?
I'm sure she wants to.
But if you have faith, it cuts
even deeper when it doesn't work out.
She's scared.
Because she truly loves music.
See you tomorrow.
Um...
are you not scared?
Me?
Yes.
Of course, I'm scared.
Even now, there are times
when I lose sleep or my appetite.
Still?
Of course, but that's what happens
when you do something you love as a job.
I thought about it
when I was in music school.
To just become a teacher
and sing as a hobby.
That it would be the smartest path.
Why didn't you do that?
I wonder.
I forgot already.
You forgot?
Except, for me, the stage is
where I can say whatever I want.
I love it.
So it doesn't matter how scared I am
or how tough it is.
I bet that's what I thought.
Hey!
What the heck?! You stink of booze.
What are you talking about?
I didn't drink a drop!
How can you say such an obvious lie?
Geez, you're so annoying.
You're always, always, always...
-Bye.
-Always!
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Take care of Momoka for me!
Hey! What are we supposed to do?
Nina! That's so unfair!
Excuse me, which way is the lake?
Thank you!
I've decided!
I've decided.
SUWA FIREWORKS SHOW
PREVIOUS-PREVIOUS-PREVIOUS NIGHT FESTIVAL
Thank you.
I really like this next group,
so please hear them out.
Ready?
Yeah.
So the band name?
Has it been decided?
We were going to decide while we ate,
but we still haven't...
Shinkawasaki is... well, whatever.
Huh?
Good evening!
-We are...
-What?!
Seriously?
Um...
TOGEARI TOGENASHI
TOGE TOGE
Togenashi Togeari!
That's the same as my T-shirt!
Wow, what a coincidence.
Hello, I suddenly found myself
joining a band this spring.
I didn't know why I did,
or why I was singing at all.
But it was fun.
For the first time in my life,
I got sucked into something.
Come on, hurry.
There's a song
that completely changed my life.
This song really helped push me forward.
That's why I want to prove to everyone
that the song isn't wrong!
I want to move people with that song,
and brag about how awesome it is.
With Subaru, Rupa, Tomo, and Momoka.
I'm sure they all feel the same.
So we're seriously working hard.
We're scared,
but we believe and we work hard.
Which is why I...
I--
It's annoying...
to keep talking about yourself.
Sorry.
Seriously?
What kind of messy start is this?
Whatever!
I'm always full of scars
My body and mind are fragmented
Passion is heartless
It's all tattered inside my heart
I plunge into the city
Where it's full of lies, it makes me sick
Within the stench and the noise
I cry out alone
Nothing is happening
How was it today?
Don't say meaningless things all the time
That creepy voice echoes in my mind
While I can't stop crying
"You don't have to be afraid
So stop hiding
Come and dance with me," you said
I want to get away from this putrid world
Disperse right now
Disperse, disperse, quietly
Quietly, don't let me be alone
Like sorrow laid out in the bars of a song
Forever and ever and ever
Until love can be proven
I don't want to believe
That love is an emotion
I could go insane
Rupa.
Tomo.
Subaru.
Momoka.
I...
I'm quitting cram school.
Oh boy.
Next time, "If You Were to Cry"