What a nice breeze.
Momoka, I...
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
THE CENTER OF THE WORLD
So close!
You're so close!
Deal with it.
Why did we end up here anyway?
The other rooms were full.
The studio we used before was empty.
That room's expensive.
Are we going to be okay?
The festival is coming up.
"Are we going to be okay?"
"The festival is coming up."
We're wasting time.
Are you okay with that part?
Should I just jump in where you said?
Want me to time you in?
Thanks.
Do we need the last part?
I thought the same.
I prefer the way it is now.
I think they both work,
but let's ask Momoka.
What do you think?
It might feel noisy
because we're all playing at once.
Let's try it where I don't play.
From the last chorus.
Okay!
I'm so tired.
Oh, Burton Sister is the closing act!
No way!
You like them?
N-No.
They're hot, right?
I said I'm not a fan!
Look, we're on it too!
Well, obviously. We're performing.
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
The first day, right?
Yes, the first ones on this stage.
So we can go see the closing act.
And this one and this one and...
Are you really going to see them all?
Of course I will.
We're getting in for free after all.
How many people will be there?
The festival goes long, so it'll vary.
It'll be full during the main acts,
but not so much with side acts.
And we need to try to leave our mark?
Actually...
Hey!
I heard you guys are playing
a different time at the festival!
I'm rooting for you!
We might be playing the second day.
What?
One of the bands had to drop out.
We'll be playing the same stage, but
they asked if we'd take their time slot.
The second day lasts all night.
There'll be way more people there
than our current slot.
That's amazing!
So you're all good with it?
Does this mean things are going our way?
Do you guys have time right now?
This is...
Yeah.
I figured we should scope out
the stage while we can.
We really get to play somewhere this big?
Unfortunately, that's the main stage.
Main?
We play on the small stage
they made over there.
What? There are multiple stages?
You really don't know anything.
Popular bands play the big stages.
Bands like us play small ones.
Diamond Dust plays
on the big stage, of course.
I'm happy.
It's kind of cool.
We're challenging Diamond Dust
on the main stage from the small stage.
Like giant-killing.
Even a cornered rat will bite a cat.
Hold on.
They don't see it like that,
neither do the fans.
Well, we do.
Momoka and I.
You're really okay
about our new time slot?
It's okay, right?
Okay.
It's going to feel great
playing under these stars.
Momoka!
Please lend me a guitar for the festival!
I'm off to work then!
Huh? You're not going too?
No, Nina started a second job on her own.
What?
Call her selfish or just fickle.
She decided she was going to
make it on her own.
She has changed recently, hasn't she?
Can she actually play the guitar now?
No idea.
FROM: TENDO AWA
TO: SUBARU AWA
Come on.
Must be nice to work out your issues.
Damn it.
LIAR
I'm not a liar.
Subaru's still hiding the fact
that she's in a band, right?
I like that about you.
I-I don't care or anything.
I hope you can forgive them, one day.
That's not happening.
You never know what the future holds.
There's no way.
But they're still in reach.
Even if you never meet or talk,
they're still alive.
The people I cared about are now ash,
nowhere to be found.
You still have me.
Thank you.
What? Why do I sing?
Maybe it's because
it lets me connect to someone else.
Hmm.
Maybe it's because
it's where I can be honest.
Yeah.
Because I can forget everything
and just be free.
For me...
it's because I want to feel like
I'm not wrong.
There are so many people.
Things are about to get into full swing.
You are...?
Oh, we're Toge Toge.
Togenashi Togeari.
Ah, yes.
You can get off here.
We play in the evening?
Yeah. Don't be late.
We might have time to see other bands.
But today's our big day.
I mean, checking out other bands
could fire us up.
Just don't be late.
You got it!
Can I come with you?
Nope, not you Nina!
Meanie!
This is our space.
Yeah.
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Yo!
You came!
Mine!
-Is this a good time?
-Yeah.
Good to see you again.
Hi.
Long time no see.
You could've told me you were coming.
Where's the fun in that?
Anyway, playing this slot
on the second day is a big deal!
Thank you.
It was mostly luck though.
How've you been, Nina?
Good, but I'm still learning the guitar.
Good.
You look like you're settling in.
Really?
You have the look of a singer.
Thank you.
How long are you gonna talk?
Introduce me already.
Yo!
We're under attack!
Oh, sorry.
This is Kyoko.
It's a small world, huh?
Hello.
Hi.
Kyoko here is a fan of yours, Nina.
I love your voice.
Come play with us again sometime, yeah?
I-If you'll have me.
Really? That's awesome!
Let's take a picture.
Can you make a funny face?
F-Funny face?
Come on, you guys, too!
What... Why?
Ready?
Say cheese!
Your faces are hilarious.
I can't believe you and Rupa backed out!
We got a lot of likes.
And comments too.
They're looking forward to seeing us.
We're getting attention!
It's all we can drink!
I'm jealous.
Down the hatch!
Stop!
Just a little?
Your "little" is never just a little.
Ms. Miura!
You're Ms. Miura, aren't you?
Y-You have the wrong person!
What? Wrong person?
-Down the hatch!
-No!
Hey, Subaru hasn't made it back yet.
She's probably still checking out bands.
So unfair. I wanted to go with her.
She was already back in the dressing room.
Really?
No!
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Subaru.
Yo!
Did you get to check out
some performances?
Yep!
I'm so jealous. I wanted to go too.
I bet you're jealous.
Must be nice to have closure.
What is it?
The first time I went to a music festival,
one of the drummers said something.
How they always do their best to play,
watching the other members' backs.
That really resonated with me.
I'm in the exact same position.
Subaru.
I texted my grandma yesterday.
Texted her what?
What?
That I wanted to do something
other than act.
Really?
So let's keep this band going.
Even if it doesn't work out today.
Are you sure?
You're narrow-minded and stubborn
and you preach morals.
Yet you're shy and unfriendly.
No wonder you got bullied.
But you don't lie.
Plus, you give everything your all,
and that's reassuring.
It makes me want to stick with you.
Thanks.
I'm lying though.
You liar.
Let's go.
Momoka.
Go where?
Follow me and find out.
It's huge.
It's the main stage after all.
The crowd's getting bigger.
Can you see, Tomo?
That's why I hate these.
Want to get on my shoulders?
Looks like you've gotten used to
doing that naturally.
They started.
This song...
Yeah, that's right.
Momoka.
Thank you for inviting us here!
And to all you first-timers, we are...
Diamond Dust!
Please stay until the end!
How long are you planning on
playing the tragic heroine?
You were in the wrong.
Keep it up and you'll just hurt yourself.
You must be stupid.
Shut up.
Let's go!
At the end of this world
That heralds the beginning
Only the suspicious looms
My boredom continues to accelerate
Living inside a dream that cannot end
We laugh, surrounded by enemies
I want to go crazy
To match your eerie gaze
But that won't be enough
Those who haven't screamed enough
Enjoy the results of others' past efforts
A single wish for those who change
I will continue to scream over and over
Wrapped in the chains of cruel fate
A different cycle of sorrow
Thank you!
-Welcome!
-We can see you in the back there!
They've gotten better.
True.
They got slammed for being over-produced
after they got an idol as their vocalist.
I know they're thinking, "Don't mock us.
I'll change your mind about us right now."
The fans got the message.
They're serious.
So they're game too, huh?
Now I'm pissed off.
I love this type of thing.
All right everyone,
let's steal all their fans here.
Yeah.
Can we get Togenashi Togeari
to do a sound check?
Okay.
Wow.
Can we start with the drums?
Okay.
Okay, we're good.
Can you test your mic?
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Can't wait for today!
Okay, can we get the bass next?
Okay.
Do you use other tones?
Yes, I use distortion.
Okay, any others?
Nope!
We're almost up.
Then a little pick-me-up!
No booze!
Oh. Where's Ms. Miura by the way?
GANSO NEW TANTANMEN HONPO
She texted me earlier
saying she's in the crowd watching us.
She's not coming to say hi?
I prefer the distance.
It makes her seem more trustworthy.
You think that's it?
Togenashi Togeari!
We're ready for you on stage!
Okay.
Want to huddle up or something?
No way.
Our pinkies...
What about putting our pinkies up?
Yeah!
Yeah.
Lame.
We're about to start
the most important show of our lives.
Let us all hear you sing and shout
on that stage, Nina.
Go hit that crowd
in the emotions with our song.
Okay.
Look! You made her cry!
We're about to take the stage!
I can't play the guitar!
You're crazy.
You suck.
So rock and roll.
Um, nice to meet you.
We're Togenashi Togeari.
We're in a band.
Um, but it's not easy at all.
We're all timid
and distrusting of others
and always grumbling.
We invite others
then end up not giving it our all.
You talking about me?
What do you mean grumbling?
I mean, we are!
That's enough.
That was Momoka on the guitar,
and Tomo on the keyboard!
And our Morality Monster,
Nina on vocals!
And Rupa on bass!
I love fighting!
And on the drums...
I'm Subaru!
"Give up. It'll never happen."
"You can't do it. Just face reality."
"This is enough."
"It's hard for me too."
Reality tries to swallow
and undermine me with a kind expression.
So I'm putting it all on this song.
And...
turn the nonbelievers
into believers with this song.
To all the people who rejected all of me.
I'll scream to them that I wasn't wrong!
No matter how much I get
No matter how much I make it my own
My own, my own
I can never catch up
To tell someone they're shooting too high
Is a rotten thing to do
Nobody wants others to be better than them
The reason is simple
They want to break through this emptiness
By the time you see it with a pure heart
You assume everything will look rosy
Even what you want to grasp
Begins to look blurry
I don't want to die
I live life hard
I want it, I want it
My soul screams
Irrational irritation can't be stopped
Unforgivable, unforgivable
It's so pathetic
Everything, everything
It's all worse
You just can't see the tears I'm hiding
To tell someone to be obedient
Is a nasty thing to do
THE ANGER OF BEING ALONE
Insubordination is a form of admiration
Sad and alone
The pain of having nowhere to go
I kicked it off
THE LOSS OF HAPPINESS
Unable to cry with an empty heart
THE SORROW OF LYING
Suppressing my flame, my voice silent
NATIONAL PIANO...
GOLD PRIZE
SHOVE ALL OF IT...
Everything I want to do
Going up in smoke, becoming faint
ALL OF IT...
INTO THIS SONG
Even what you want to grasp
Begins to look blurry
I don't want to disappear
I want it destroyed
The rusted and tangled
Distorted commotion
The muddy transparency can be pretty
If pulverized into powder
So pathetic, so pathetic
I can't stand it
Faint significance, breathing stopped
Ideals are old fantasies
Scared to even try to resist
Scared to...
EMPTINESS AND CATHARSIS
Momoka.
I wasn't wrong, was I?
Next episode, "The Sky Darkens Again"