All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"The Greatest Bloodbath in History"
What do you want?
Jeez, stop sitting at that desk all the time.
How about getting outside a little?
But I have to start getting
ready for the next summer Comipa.
Flabbiness, puffiness...
Do you realize that your face has been
turning into a stereotypical otaku's lately?
You think so?
It's going to be summer soon!
Yeah, that's why
I'm getting ready for Comipa.
Comipa, Comipa!
What's with you today?
This is exactly why...
Okay?
It's good to see you've
resolved yourself, Comrade Kazuki.
Next year's World Cup in Germany,
and next month's summer Comipa...
With these two great
worldwide events ahead of us,
--we sacrifice the brief
moments of sun in the rainy season,
--What are you going to do for the cover?
--in order to press forward into a
--It's going to be in color with leafing on it!
--secret training camp in an unexplored region.
--I can't wait!
--This shall be our first stept
--Wow...
--towards world conquest!
Good grief!
We were supposed to be going to a totally
normal, ordinary, run-of-the-mill camp,
so how'd it end up like this?
Just like Major League Ball 3 was born
through secret special training
held out of the sight of the public,
through this training camp, we shall
take the world in the palm of our hands!
Seriously...
"Mountain Campground"
Hold it, what do you mean by that?
You're not seriously saying
you forgot the food, are you?
I am floored by your level
of misunderstanding, my sister!
I did not forget it.
When the amount of
baggage becomes bulky,
the occurrence of a slight
miscalculation in loading strategies
is an inevitable result of current statistics.
Slight miscalculation?
Inevitable result of statistics?
He sure brought a lot of different stuff.
Seriously, take a look at this!
There's even a toy for
playing in a hot spring!
Anticipating various situations
is common practice
at a secret training camp!
So you're telling me that
you've forgotten our food?!
What are we going to do about it?
Did you know that the speed of light
is 7 1/2 times the circumference
of the Earth, my sister?
We really don't have anything?
Nada, zilch, absolutely nothing!
So then, if we don't turn around and
go back, we won't have anything to eat?
But there weren't any
stores at all on the way here!
That's the ticket, bus ticket!
I poured my entire soul
into selecting this final frontier!
It would easily take three hours
to reach the closest store by car!
Not only that, it closes at 6:00 like
some relic from the previous century.
Even the hot spring panda is rejected?
I think you mean "dejected".
Huh?
What's wrong, Minami?
Oh nothing, this
road just seems familiar...
Hey, Taishi! Did you just say we're lost?
What are you hearing, my brother?
What I said was, we took
only one road to get here,
but before I realized it, we started
traveling through unfamiliar territory
which isn't recorded in my memory,
and I feel a certain ambivalence...
That's the same thing!
Hey, if we keep going this way,
won't we end up who knows where?
There is no need to worry about that.
What do you mean by that?
If you want to know, just look ahead.
Huh?
Hey, isn't this the same
campground we just came from?
How did this happen?
We didn't go back down at all.
It seems the legend is true.
What legend?
It is a booby trap once set up by
defeated warriors of the Heike clan
so that they could
escape the pursuit of the Genji.
Once someone sets foot here,
they must wander for all eternity.
That's right!
This campground is in an
inescapable forest of wandering,
which is even compared to the
dense forest at the base of Mt. Fuji!
"Forest of Wandering"
Dense forest at...
The base of Mt. Fuji?
Inescapable labyrinth?
Even a three year old kid wouldn't
believe somethin' like that these days!
"Out of Area"
What the heck?!
Did you really think a cell phone
would connect in a dense forest like this?
Don't be so patronizing!
Sputnik!
Just great! The GPS is shot too.
What should we do?
Try going back down again?
But if we move through
the dense forest carelessly,
there's a danger we
could get even more lost.
Mizuki, a local old guy
came asking what's wrong.
A local old guy?
You mean there's actually
someone around a place like this?
You must be the ones who are lost.
Yes, actually, we got lost and then...
You were careless.
You want us to tell you the route from
my troop's garrison, back to the local town?
I'm sorry, but I cannot relinquish
Class 1 classified information.
We understand, our destined rivals.
We must obtain the information
we want through strategic maneuvers.
That is the iron-clad rule ("okite") which
governs campgrounds all over the world.
Hold it, what does he mean
"Soji Okita of the Campground?"
Taishi probably just made it up.
And by the way,
it's not Okita, it's okite (rule).
Do you intend to declare war on us?
Indeed!
As long as you don't run away, that is.
So I guess this means we're going to
have to play a survival game after all, huh?
Wrong, Comrade Mizuki!
This is not a simple survival game.
It is a sacred battle with
the rule of the world at stake!
A sacred battle? With these laser gun toys?
What?!
Are you saying that
you see this practice system,
which is officially used by armies all
over the world, and has improved sim fire,
as a mere children's plaything?
It's not?
Of course not!
It detects a beam with
an optical receiving device,
and acknowledges a good shot with
the warning device worn on the head.
It's the latest
super-interactive virtual device.
If you think of it as a mere plaything, you
will be the first to fall to an enemy bullet!
It's just a toy!
But Taishi, we're up
against survival game pros.
Do we even have any hope of winning?
That goes without saying.
Comrade Kazuki,
thoughts deeper than the Mariana
Trench run through my gray matter.
Thoughts deeper than...
The Mariana Trench?
You don't know your place.
I'm going to teach you real
good what the fear of death is.
Comic Party Revolution
Comic Party Revolution!
Gelbe Eins to Hertz.
I can't detect Fritz in Area 87.
This is Hertz. Roger that.
Proceed to Area 89 immediately,
and continue scouting.
Gelbe Eins, Roger.
In battle,
victory or defeat depends entirely
upon how quickly you can find the enemy.
We've polished our scouting
skills through numerous actual battles.
Against us, you're just sitting ducks.
Yes, you probably do have good skills.
However! That will not
be enough to win against us.
Be aware that against our secret plan,
your skills are nothing
more than a rusted door knocker.
You shouldn't be saying that when
you just got shot in the blink of an eye.
"Corpse"
"Taishi Team Corpse Storage Site"
I found them. Ahead
100 meters. Two enemies.
Good. Attack them immediately.
Gelbe Eins, Roger.
So you think you're hidden, huh?
Stupid amateurs!
How cute!
"Corpse"
"Pro Team Corpse Storage Site"
Did you see that?
That is the ultimate defense,
which utilizes the enemy's psychology
under the extreme conditions of battle
to neutralize every
conceivable attack instantly:
the Cosplay Barrier!
What do you mean, "Cosplay Barrier"?
But it seems to be so
effective, I'm almost embarrassed.
So cute!
Did you witness our secret plan?
What do you mean "secret plan"?
Co-Comrade Kazuki! It couldn't be...
"It couldn't be," my ass. I was shot!
What?!
That's so pathetic when
everyone else is risking their lives...
Look who's talking!
But at this rate,
even if we could defend ourselves,
we can't go on the offensive.
Don't worry! Forget your
fragile-handle-with-cares!
I am already waiting for
Secret Plan 2 to be put into action.
Secret Plan 2?
We'll rebuild front line defense.
Gelbe Drei, proceed to Area 86...
I can't stop!
What?!
Will he be able to stop
Chisa Tsukamoto's headlong charge,
which is even compared to the out-of-control
human dumptruck, Stan Hansen's rush?
All men, concentrate your
fire on the out of control cart!
Damn, what incredible speed!
I can't stop!
Dammit! Dammit!
What was that?
That can probably break
through the enemy's front line, but...
I just got a tinge of worry.
My, what nice tea.
"Checkerboard Pattern"
Why you...
But it's boring being a corpse!
You were the first one
shot, so it serves you right!
You are wrong about that, Comrade Mizuki!
I got shot in order to lure the
enemy into letting their guard down,
an ingenious plan worthy of Hakuoro!
Who shot you?
I despise you!
I want to catch you and
toss you into a scorpion tank!
Take that! And that! And that! And that!
Welcome back.
Cosplay Barrier...
Certainly a terrifying strategy.
However, there is one
big thing you overlooked.
That is...
What?
The Cosplay Barrier didn't work?!
You guys probably don't know this,
but our captain has absolutely
no interest in girls aged over 1[censored].
To our captain, girls who are
more developed than necessary
are the same as vegetables in a field.
No, they are nothing more than
despicable, abominable creatures!
There you are.
Th... This is...
I was so captivated by the floatation ring,
I got dangerously close
to getting too excited, but...
It seems your overly-developed
body turned out to be your fatal flaw.
I've confirmed that Fritz 7 is down.
Good. There's only one left, huh?
We'll switch to
surround-and-destroy maneuvers.
All men, converge on Area 85.
It seems they think they've won.
However! You do not know
how frightening we truly are.
What?
Where is she?
She's gone?
What's going on here?
Yes, the last one of us
left is our ultimate weapon,
Stealth Aya!
It couldn't be... A stealth human?!
Not only does she have an
overwhelmingly weak presence,
she went virtually unnoticed
even in the Comipa Exhibition Hall,
and she continues to have a menacingly
high rate of doujinshi left unsold.
She is the invisible
one-person circle, Aya Hasabe!
All men gather up and form a circle!
Yes, Sir!
Can they possibly find Aya Hasabe
in this complex survival game field?
Wh... Where is she?
Where did she shoot from?
I don't know!
Caught you!
A bunny?
Got you.
What?!
I lost? Impossible...
I lost?
Thus,
the most perfect and beautiful victory in
the history of mankind was accomplished.
Behold!
The great first step in our ambitions for
world conquest has taken place right here!
What are you acting all high and mighty
for when you're the one who got shot first?
Actually, this is the first time my
troop has been so completely defeated.
You have such little
presence you're almost not human.
What an incredible skill.
What the heck,
that's not a compliment at all.
That's right. Aya, I think
you should get angry, just a little.
No, I...
More importantly, the promise.
Oh, that's right!
All right, we won, so keep your promise.
Promise?
Did I make a promise?
What, you forgot?
You said you would tell us
the way to get back to town!
Subaru is starving!
Oh! Right, we were supposed
to guide you from our garrison.
To tell you the truth,
we've been wandering
this dense forest for a week,
but we haven't sighted a
route back down from the garrison.
Yup, yup.
So in other words...
I guess that means we're lost too.
Then you should have
said that in the first place!
You saved me! You're my savior!
If you hadn't been so kind as to stop me,
Chisa would have ended
up becoming another Vostok,
going around and
around the Earth forever!
Huh?
Wh... Where am I?
There was a town right on the other side?
I've been kinda worried about something.
Don't it seem like
we're missin' somebody?
Really?
If it's me you're thinking about,
I'm right here, Comrade Mizuki.
Who cares about you?!
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I'm super pissed off!
How dare you treat me, the Comipa Queen,
the Great Eimi Ohba,
like some ordinary citizen?!
Uh, um, Ms. Ohba?
Are you saying that I, the Great Eimi,
am not good enough to
be Asahi Sakurai's friend?
No, that's not it at all.
I'm the one who...
Now that it's come down to this,
I'll just have to show you
the Great Eimi's true powder!
It's "true power."
Next time: "Let's Start by Being Friends."
I'm the one who's
always standing in line...