They're so cool!
What? You want to play guitar too?
I've never played,
but do you think I could?
Could I play like you, Momoka?
Forget it.
You've got no experience.
You'll end up neglecting your singing.
Doesn't seem like she hears you at all.
Well, people tend to become like this
after their first performance.
Wow, look at her.
Like she had meant for all this to happen.
Shouting the things I'm feeling...
at the top of my lungs
while giving it my all.
It was the first time
I ever did something like that.
Before, I would always care so much
about what other people thought of me,
I often choked on my words.
Nina!
Let's go practice!
Okay!
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
APPRECIATION (SURPRISE)
Okay, stop.
What do you think?
Looks good.
Let's play it back.
I want to break it
I don't have the courage
Someone hurry up and teach me
A reason to live
Oh! Sounds good.
There are so many people
Nina, can you modulate more
when you enter the chorus?
Someone hurry up and teach me
A reason to live
Like that?
Yeah. It was kinda obvious and boring.
And let's retake the drums.
What, now?
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Diamond Dust?
Yeah. She was looking them up online.
I bet they're getting in her head.
Yeah, but they're a hit band.
That's true, but...
If she really was wary of them,
she wouldn't have recruited
amateurs like us.
But...
-Hm?
What? No way...
No way!
What's wrong?
Sorry, I have to go now!
Huh?
See you tomorrow!
What?
SUBARU? ARE YOU OKAY?
She's not reading our texts.
It's a guy then.
What?!
But it really didn't seem like
she was dating.
Maybe she's trying to get back with an ex.
W-What are you saying?!
Why are you so upset?
B-Because...
Is she really...?
Girls in bands do get attention
from guys in bands.
They see us as easy prey.
"Easy prey"?
You should be careful, too.
I'll call her.
She won't answer.
We'll find out tomorrow.
But I think we should be free to choose
who we date and where we work.
What do you think about them?
Hm?
The current Diamond Dust.
Nothing really.
What do you mean?
I don't hate them or anything.
I honestly wish them the best.
Then why did you quit?
We don't need to talk about that.
Stop worrying about these things.
Just focus on singing.
What kind of band were you?
I said drop it.
Please tell me.
Here.
Whoa... Hm?
We started out as a school music club.
But everyone was already good.
And we had passion.
We all had the same goal
and it felt like fate.
It felt so much like a miracle
I got goosebumps.
My prediction was right.
We packed our entire gym with a crowd
at the fall school festival
in our freshman year.
We were the closing act. It was awesome.
So we decided to
drop out of school to go pro
and we moved here, put out a CD ourselves,
played some shows
and came close to a major debut.
That's when I quit.
Momoka.
So this is how you smile.
Sorry, I wasn't sleeping.
Huh?
I should've just slept in my bed.
It's from Subaru!
Hm? Huh? What?!
HEY
IS THERE SOMEONE YOU LIKE?
Hey!
I'M QUITTING THE BAND, SORRY!
This isn't a good idea.
Why? The three of us made a pact
to do this together!
Are you really giving up already?
It's not that I'm giving up.
She can always dump the guy and come back.
Try to force it
and it might reignite their spark.
What? Really?
Wait, have you never dated a guy?
Have you?
Excuse us.
What are you doing?
This place makes me nervous.
Please take charge
since you're our leader.
Since when?!
Also, Subaru acts pretty annoying here,
but don't let that get to you.
Huh?
Oh?
Subaru...
What?
Grandmother. It's this way.
May I help you?
-Suba--
-What? You're lost?
Grandmother,
I'll just go help her very quickly.
Why did you come here?!
Of course we'd come
after that text you sent!
I'll explain later! Please go home!
At least tell me the reason!
I just said...
Who are they?
Grandmother.
Th-They're my actor friends.
Actors?
Right?
It's so lively here,
it's a bit overwhelming.
Yes, it's very crowded.
Subaru.
-Posture.
-Yes, ma'am!
I always tell you
to maintain good posture.
Your regular mannerisms
will always come out in your acting,
so you must always maintain
a healthy mind and body.
Yes, Grandmother.
Feel free to remind her
whenever you see her do something wrong.
Please excuse me.
Subaru!
I know, I know.
Was that the actress Tendo Awa?
You just noticed?
How was I supposed to know?
Yes, she's my grandma.
She told me yesterday
that she'd be visiting.
Wait, are you from
a family of celebrities?
It's not like that.
My parents have normal jobs.
You don't want to be an actor, right?
I don't.
But I told you that I can't tell her now.
Then why did you say
you were quitting the band?!
I kinda freaked out.
And they say to trick your friends
to trick your enemies.
I don't get it.
That's how committed
I need to be to trick her.
She seems nice though.
On the surface, sure.
But she's from Kyoto,
which means you shouldn't take
what she says at face value.
Really?
-Posture.
-Yes, ma'am!
I'd like to get back and see
how much your acting has improved.
W-What?
Would you two like to join us?
-W-What?
W-What is it?
Well, t-truthfully, I actually like you.
Don't laugh!
An étude?
Yes, a lovers' étude.
You confess your love to her,
just as her ex, Subaru,
comes to win her back.
-I... see.
WHAT'S AN ÉTUDE?
That's wonderful, Grandmother.
AN IMPROMPTU ACT! IT'S BASICALLY IMPROV!!
Let's head back to the school and try.
AS IF WE COULD DO THAT!!
Are you ready?
NO WAY!!
YOU CAN'T BACK OUT!
NO WAY, NO WAY!!
No thank you.
Oh, it seems Nina didn't hear you well.
Just do it!
Do it if you want me in the band!
SOME THINGS I JUST CAN'T DO!!
You can't talk about the étude beforehand
on your phones.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Let us go then.
Wait!
Y-You're...
I don't want to lie to myself anymore.
I love you too!
Then why did you break up with me?
What?
I was committed to us from the very start.
I was sure we'd never split up.
So how could you say
that you were leaving so easily?
Well...
How could you?!
Did you lie when you said
you were serious about us?
No, I was serious about that.
Then what?!
That was low, unloading all that
during the improv!
What's the problem?
I know you're not satisfied.
I'm not looking to quit the band.
Besides, everyone in the industry
just sees me as Tendo Awa's granddaughter.
-It's just...
-What?
It's been bugging me.
My grandma normally wouldn't just drop by.
She's not a spontaneous person at all.
So this is why!
Girls Band Cry.
Appearing in a drama?!
The feedback!
Don't use the mic for talking!
I don't have a choice, my grandma decided.
It's a minor role,
so I should be done after a week,
but I'll miss practice.
Got it.
Really?
You skip practice to study too, Nina!
That's different.
It's the same!
No!
Don't fight.
But... Subaru might not come back!
It happens all the time.
But...
What are you so mad about?
Because you don't seem to care.
You're the one who doesn't seem to care!
I told you I'm coming back.
Why can't you trust me?
But...
Look, everyone has personal issues
they don't want to share.
You don't like being asked about
why you moved here, right?
That's...
We're wasting time.
We'll just re-record Subaru's part today,
so you can leave, Nina.
What is their problem?!
I am being caring!
Seriously...
Huh?
You free tomorrow?
No!
I lied. I am!
Where are we?
Hm? This is my home.
Come on in.
THE NEXT DAY
Oh, wow.
You get over it quickly.
-Is tea fine?
-Oh, yeah.
Sit wherever you want.
That's the best seat for gaming.
Thanks.
Look at this.
She's so pretty.
I figured I should tell you
since you might moan about it later.
STARRING TENDO AWA (UP-AND-COMER)
SUBARU
I was named after this title.
My grandma picked it.
Wait, is she your...
Yeah, she said this movie made her famous
when she was young.
I wasn't born yet, so I don't really know.
Mm.
But she said it's an auspicious name
if I'm going to be an actor.
But you don't want to be.
Yeah. I can't stand getting
special treatment for who my grandma is.
And I just don't like acting.
I get embarrassed.
But when I tell her
that I'm trying to become an actor,
she smiles.
It's the only time she really smiles.
Not a forced one.
What do you think?
What would you do?
There.
Do you see now where I'm coming from?
But something has to change.
You should tell her soon
if you don't want to act.
Right?
Yeah.
It's too bad.
I figured if I went to acting school,
she'd realize I can't act
and give up on me.
-Bye.
-Yeah.
Don't worry, I won't quit the band.
-Really?
-Yeah.
When we did our live show,
I kinda realized that
I really like hitting the drums.
Ow...
It's rare for me to open up,
so at least say something!
Yeah.
Hm? What's this?
I'm sorry. From Nina.
Then try to not get so mad
in the first place.
DAYS LATER
Welcome to
The Detective Granny Case Files Part 6!
This is Tendo Awa who plays Granny!
Thank you.
I'm her granddaughter, Subaru.
I'll be playing the store clerk.
It's nice to meet you all.
That's a lot of makeup.
You need that much to see it on camera.
It's the same on stage.
You do makeup?
Depending on the situation.
Stop imagining it.
Okay, ready!
She's really gonna tell her?
Yeah, that's what she said.
She might need to quit her school
and move back home,
but she wants to stay in the band.
If it's that big of a deal,
she doesn't have to tell her.
I know.
But she knew
she eventually had to one day.
Okay!
Checking the footage!
Are you sure we can be here?
Yes, I'm done for today.
It was our first time acting together.
That's great.
It's been my dream...
to appear in the same title as her.
Do you really want her to be an actor?
Of course.
Subaru was named after the role
that gave me my big break.
You see, my daughter hates my job.
She says I'm never home
and I'm too bossy for someone
who can't take care of a home.
That's why it made me so happy
when Subaru said she liked my job.
She was the only one to smile.
The only one who liked my job.
And when she said she wanted to try,
I was so grateful.
Okay!
Checking the footage!
Now, shall we go check?
Grandmother!
Ah, good work.
Um, I'd like to talk to you
about something.
What is this about?
It should probably wait, but you need to
catch your bullet train, right?
Yes, I should be going soon.
Right.
Then I'll say it.
The thing is...
Um...
I...
Grandmother.
Subaru, come quick!
-What?
-Hm?
You forgot something! We need to go!
Huh?
We have to go now! Come on, let's go!
What? Ow! Hey!
Ow. Don't push me!
Hey! What...
Your words don't match your actions!
I'm sorry!
Keep it down!
You're the one who said
I should come clean and tell her already!
-I did!
-How can you say that proudly?!
I finally got ready to tell her!
Well...
Everyone has their own personal issues.
Huh?
It's not easy, but you need to
grow to be more understanding.
Right?
That's rich coming from you!
Ow!
I knew that already, unlike you!
And you just...
But you will have to tell her eventually!
When?
When you find something you want to do.
What's her problem?
I don't know.
I'm over it! I'm so over this!
I finally made up my mind
because you told me not to quit.
But now I'm stuck with a Morality Monster
who suddenly changes her mind
and someone who gets it,
but won't help.
I'll make my own decisions,
so leave me alone!
Subaru...
How was my acting?
Wow, I feel so much better.
It's fine, I know I'll have to
deal with it eventually.
So I'll be here
kicking your asses forward until then!
Let's go then!
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
dareka ni somarenai dare ni mo narenai
I laughed, thinking it a dream
yume da to omotte waratte miseta
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
wasureta yowasa kajikande iku
I can't even say that I'm lonely
samishii nante ieru wake mo nai
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
sarigenai kaiwa sura kizutsuku kokoro wa
Is incapable of making anyone happy
dare hitori dare hitori shiawase ni shinai
But still, I feel a growing hope
nee sore demo mada kitai fukuramunda
Moving past all of the lies
surechigatta uso nante zenbu sutete
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
daisoretenai yo tte tada kikitakute
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
yume bakari de osanakutatte
I don't care if I'm still the same today
kyou mo kawarenai mama datte iinda
I just want to sing with you
kimi to utatte itai
My emotions stir so often
nando datte kanjou bakka yure ugoite
I've been hated
kirawarete kita kedo
But I'm going to keep walking
kono mama de aruite yukunda
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
darenimo narenai watashi mune hatte sa
Even if I'm alone
tada hitori demo
I believe in myself
magiremonai jibun wo shinjite
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
kizutsuki ochiru tabi utaeba ii
Next episode, "Rising Vocals"