Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Save Tsukamoto Printing!"
Ow!
I did it again.
Oh no, I'm late!
I have to hurry and help Dad!
I'm home!
"Tsukamoto Printing"
Dad?
Dad! What's the matter, Dad?
Mom, Dad needs help!
Please take a look at this,
Kazuki. It's my manuscript.
I have confidence in this one!
You don't say.
But I'm busy with my
part-time job right now.
Oh, welcome!
All right, I'll just take a quick look at it.
This is...
Ta-da! The theme this time is...
Friendship!
Hard work!
And victory!
Superheroes who combine
their strength with their friends,
and fight the evil aliens who are
plotting to take over the universe!
It's so exciting!
Hot!
How do you like it?
I think it's fine!
I guess I could say you're the only
one who can write something like this.
Or maybe I should say that you're
the only one who can understand it.
Subaru is so happy that
Kazuki complimented her!
I wasn't really complimenting you...
Now that I've received official approval
from Kazuki for it as a great masterpiece,
I'm going to have it printed at Chisa's!
Please get out of the way!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Chisa...
Big Brother, Big Sister Subaru,
I'm embarrassed that you saw that.
"New!!"
It must be tough always helping
your family out with the business.
Not at all.
Hey Chisa, take a look at this!
I've already finished my
manuscript for the next Comipa!
I'm going to have
your father print it for me.
Chisa?
Big Brother, Big Sister Subaru...
Chisa!
What's wrong?
What? Your father?
Yes, when I came home
from school yesterday...
Dad?
Dad! Dad! Hey, come on, Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
So, he had to be admitted
to the hospital right away.
Luckily, it seems like it
wasn't anything serious.
But he has to rest for a week.
Chisa...
You poor thing.
This is why I kept telling him
not to play online games!
Even though he was busy with work,
he stayed up all night for three days!
He said he wouldn't
stop until he got a rare item.
Dad is so stubborn.
You're saying that
was the cause of all this?
But I guess this means
Tsukamoto Printing will
be closing for a while, huh?
What? Really?
We can't do that!
For a small business like this
to close is simply unthinkable!
The economy is bad enough already.
If a small business like us
doesn't fill its monthly quota,
the debt collector will
seize the entire business
and the whole family will
be forced out onto the street!
I didn't know that...
I'm sorry.
I won't let them get away with this!
The Devil of Bad Economy and the Debt
Collecting Demons are picking on Chisa,
and she's only a frail maiden!
Subaru absolutely will not
let them get away with this!
"Bad Economy" "Debt Collector"
Say, Big Sister Subaru?
She's worrying about you in her own way.
She's totally missing the point though.
In a situation like this,
we should get everyone to help out!
"Kuhonbutsu, Taishi"
"Ohba, Eimi"
we should get everyone to help out!
Tsukamoto Printing
has always helped them out,
so once they hear it's in
trouble, I'm sure they'll help out!
Right! Right!
Yes, hello?
Eimi? This is Sendo.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You see, Tsukamoto Printing is...
I'm busy right now.
I'm in the final stretch with
my manuscript! Talk to you later!
Oh! There it is! God has descended!
Are you kiddin' me?
I'm the one who needs help!
By the way, Kazuki,
where's the number 61 tone?
Oh, it's in the second drawer...
Wait, you're drawing your
manuscript in my apartment again?
Yup!
Sorry, I was asked to help
with the costumes for Comipa.
Haga begged me to.
I'm really sorry.
I guess it can't be helped.
Marvelous!
To think that as the first
step towards world conquest,
you've set your sights
on the printing industry!
It seems like you're beginning
to understand, Comrade Kazuki!
After all, printing is said to be
one of the world's greatest inventions.
Sorry...
It's okay...
It looks like everyone's busy getting
ready for the Comipa coming up soon.
I know! I'll help you!
No!
You're busy with your manuscript too.
Yeah, that's true, but still...
I don't want to bother
everyone else either,
when they're busy
getting ready for Comipa.
Will you be okay handling
all the printing work by yourself?
Well...
I'm sure I'll be fine!
When it comes down
to it, Chisa can handle it!
Chisa...
Are you really sure you'll be okay?
No need to worry!
Leave helping Chisa
to me, Subaru Mikage!
I've finished my manuscript,
so there's no need to worry!
Subaru...
Big Sister Subaru!
Let's work together, Chisa!
The theme this time is
friendship, hard work, and victory!
Big Sister Subaru! Thank you so much!
This is the birth of the
ultimate team of Chisa and Subaru!
Hey, hey, what do
you mean, "ultimate team"?
All right, together we're going
to rebuild Tsukamoto Printing!
Let's try this again:
Together we're going to
rebuild Tsukamoto Printing!
Yeah!
Big Sister Subaru, if there is a paper
jam or something, just let me know!
Okay.
Big Sister Subaru?
"Super Cheap"
"12,000,000 - No down payment!"
It's plain.
Huh?
It's plain!
Even though I'm going through all the
trouble of helping you, it's totally plain!
There's nothing I can do about it though.
Not only that, but the
only things we're printing
are small jobs like
supermarket leaflets and stuff.
You seem to know a lot about that...
At this rate, we'll be
playing right into the hands of
the Devil of Bad Economy
and the Debt Collecting Demons!
I know!
Why don't we print it in full
color with super-gorgeous gold leaf,
to try to give it some impact!
"Super Cheap"
"12,000,000 - No down payment!"
We don't have that kind of money!
Then, we'll put my four-panel
manga on it as a bonus!
With a premier manga on it,
I'm sure it will be popular!
"Heroes wanted!"
"Meow"
"I pick you!"
"M... Me?"
"And you!"
"What about me...?"
"Let's go!"
Anything but that!
Boo...
Oh, there it is!
Huh?
It's going to get busy!
Huh? Huh? What is it?
What is this?
When it gets close to the
deadline, everyone asks to draw here,
so they can get it printed right away.
Wow...
Chisa, please do this as fast as possible!
Okay!
Huh? Umm...
This dialogue balloon
is too long, it won't fit!
Oh, and if you don't press this
tone down a little more, it will come off.
I see, I didn't notice.
You're really something, Chisa.
Chisa, I'm finished over here too!
Me too, Chisa!
Okay! Wait just a moment!
She learned all that just
by looking at manuscripts?
Chisa's really something.
Excuse me miss,
are you working here part time?
Oh, yes!
I'm helping out Chisa.
Subaru will check your manuscript too.
It looks like I'll be working
all night, so buy me some coffee.
I want mine without sugar!
Huh? Coffee?
I'll have a boxed lunch.
The special "power" lunch
with fried chicken. Make it a large.
Oh, could you record today's
episode of Card Master Peach?
My shoulders are stiff,
so could you give me a massage?
Subaru isn't an errand girl!
"Uchuudou"
And another masterpiece
by the Great Eimi is born!
My talent is frightening!
Yup, frightenin' all right.
To me, you're the most frightenin'
thing around when you get like this.
What's with you?! Just shut up!
You're just jealous of my talent!
Who're you callin' jealous?!
Don't say freaky stuff like that!
Excuse me.
--Please do not argue in front of the store.
--Please get out of the way!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--Those two...
--I'm sorry!
--It's just like Kazuki said.
--I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--Subie's helpin' out Chisa with her work.
You know, in a way, they
actually make the ultimate team.
--I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--It's come down to this!
Daiei Ryuu final ultimate technique!
Earth Dragon, Covering the Distance!
Chisa!
Ouch...
Are you okay?
I really am sorry.
We don't have time!
We have to pick this up fast!
Right!
What are they doing?
Seriously...
Comic Party Revolution!
"Second Half"
Here is your delivery of 5,000 leaflets!
Thanks as always.
It's tough what happened to
your father, but hang in there, Chisa.
Yes, Sir! Thank you very much!
Chisa! We still have to do more deliveries?
Yes, we have many regular
customers at this shopping arcade!
Come on, let's keep at it,
Big Sister Subaru!
Printing work is so hard!
They're hitting the top!
Then lower them a little.
Sorry, everyone.
I did it again.
But she's working so hard...
I want to do something for her.
G'Afternoon!
Thanks again!
Th... Th... That's it!
"Victory Victory"
Chisa, something important just came up!
Big Sister Subaru?
Now we can turn
things around in one shot!
Today is going to be the start of
Tsukamoto Printing's major debut!
Did you call me?
--Oh, we're out of coffee!
--Now it's my hips. Please give them a rub.
Like I said...
Subaru isn't an errand girl!
Please don't think bad of me for this!
It's all for the rebirth
of Tsukamoto Printing!
All right, it's going to get busy now!
"Shonen Jumbo" "Dengeki Shooh" "Maganone"
I'm finally done.
But I wonder what happened
to Big Sister Subaru so suddenly?
Chisa!
You look like you're working hard.
Oh! Big Brother!
I managed to finish my manuscript
in time for tomorrow's Comipa.
I'd like you to print
it as quickly as possible.
Leave it to me!
By the way, where's Subaru?
She didn't run away because
the work was too hard, did she?
No, not at all...
Look, how many times do I have to say it?
I want you to let our
company print your magazine!
If you have a circulation of 20,000,000,
then couldn't you allow us to
do even a little bit of the printing?
Huh? No?
Boo! You're such cheapskates!
I'll never read your
magazine even if you beg me to!
Next I'll call here!
Subaru?
Oh, welcome back, Chisa.
And I see Kazuki's with you.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm doing sales, you know, sales!
Sales?
There are so many magazines in this world.
And they have a lot of printing work.
So if we can get work from them,
we can pay off the debt in one shot,
and we can make Tsukamoto
Printing into a huge company!
It's a great idea, don't you think?
And were there any
places that okayed your idea?
Well... not yet.
I thought so.
Or I guess I should say, it's only natural.
Really?
Yes, really!
But I thought it was a great idea...
Good grief.
I don't know if I should say this
is just like you, Subaru, or what.
But I thought,
if we're going to be printing,
it'd be good if we
could do a big, famous book.
Thank you very much, Big Sister Subaru.
But Chisa is happy just
being able to print for everyone.
Chisa loves printing!
Stuff like the whiteness of
new paper, and the smell of ink...
And how with just a little ingenuity,
the result is completely different...
And the excitement of
checking to see if it printed correctly...
I love all of that.
Chisa...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've been talking only about myself.
No, it's okay. Because now
I know just how much you love printing.
It looks like Subaru was
moved by your story, Chisa.
Big Sister Subaru...
Come on, Comipa is tomorrow,
so let's put in a little more work!
--Chisa, I'm sorry!
--Hey, Subaru!
All the work is gone!
Huh?
But, but, I thought we
were going to get a huge job,
so I cancelled all the jobs we already had!
What did you say?
I'm sorry!
Chisa...
What will I do?
Now I won't be able to
reach this month's sales quota
and we really will be foreclosed.
Then, what will happen
to Tsukamoto Printing?
I'm sorry!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh! There you are!
Please print 100 copies of
my super-gorgeous extra volume,
as fast as possible!
Eimi!
Big Sister Eimi...
Well you see, the book itself is done,
but this time, I decided at the last
minute to put out an illustration book too.
No doubt it's going to sell like mad too.
Hold it right there!
Forget about that lame
illustration book, and print my paper first!
What do you mean "lame"?!
You're the one whose
paper is lame, hot spring panda!
Stop sayin' stuff that could ruin my rep!
You started it!
Excuse me...
I only need ten copies,
but could you print this for me?
Huh? Even Aya?
Yes, it's going to be my
first offset book in a while.
Ta-da!
Mizuki!
I came to see how you were doing
with all the work. Let's eat together!
Mmm, it looks even
better than special shake-ben!
What is everyone doing here?
--Everyone's thinkin' the same thing.
--Catch!
Huh?
When they saw those
two klutzes workin' so hard...
They just couldn't let it go, ya know?
An' besides, they all
love the heartfelt feeling
that Tsukamoto Printing
puts into their work.
They really are the ultimate team.
I think you're right.
Everyone, well...
Come on! If we don't hurry,
we won't make it in time for Comipa!
Big Sister Subaru...
Right!
There we go!
Okay, you're good to go!
Thanks again!
It's over!
Everyone, thank you so much!
You don't have to be so formal!
Right! You're a part of
the Comipa team, just like us!
Thanks!
That's right!
It's already morning, huh?
All right, I'm gonna do my best today!
My books will sell
even if I don't work hard!
Well then, I will see you later, Kazuki.
Okay, we should...
Huh?
Those two must be exhausted.
You're late!
When in the world will
our new volume be delivered,
My Brother?
Chisa, Subaru, wake up!
I need you to do a rush printing!
I forgot about my own manuscript!
Hey, wake up! Come on!
I don't have any time! Come on, please!
--I'm begging you! Chisa! Subaru!
--Bring however many gold leaflets you want!
We're the ultimate team.
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
He seems like a pretty nice boy.
No wonder you picked him!
You think so too, Ma?
Yes! Have you come out
and told him how you feel?
Not yet.
Then do you want me to tell him?
No, that's not a good idea!
I'll find out how Kazuki feels myself.
Taking over the inn is my dream.
Next time: "Bravo at Inobou!"
Say, what kind of story is it anyway?