Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Let's Start by Being Friends"
"Video Games"
Go!
Yeah, that's it! Eat this!
Did it!
A stunning victory for Eimi!
Just who do you think I am?
I am the King of Queens of the
Comipa world, the Great Eimi Ohba!
Jeez, you just attacked
like that so I couldn't get away.
That was just nuts.
There's an open spot over there.
Let's go!
The next challenger, huh?
I'm ready to serve up some
more pain, so let's see what you've got!
Huh? What's going on here?
How come she's pounding me
and I'm not getting any hits on her?
This super pisses me off!
Why you!
Why you! Why you! Why you! Why you!
No way...
You smart ass! How dare
you take on the Great Eimi?!
Hey, you!
Oh, Miss Ohba.
I never expected to
see you in a place like this!
I always buy your books.
Your latest issue was the best!
What? You're my fan?
Wow, it sure is hard being a popular author.
Wait a minute, are you...
Yes? Wait a minute, are you...
Asahi Sakurai?
--Huh?
--What?!
Asahi Sakurai?
--Where? Where?
--Really?
"Nalpis Water"
That was close.
Sorry! I didn't know you like games.
Yeah, whenever some
free time opens up at work,
I head right to the arcade.
I keep it a secret from everyone though.
Why? You can come to an
arcade without trying to hide it.
Oh wait, I get it. People would
think it's lame for an idol to have
a hobby of going to arcades, so
you don't want it to get out to the public.
That's not exactly why...
It must be tough being an idol too.
As the King of Queens of the
Comipa world, I can understand, but...
You're probably surrounded
by mean rivals who bully you,
and scheming staff members.
They make you work from morning
to night without any time to yourself.
It's so hard you cry, and you go
through the same thing every day...
That's gotta be it! It's just like
the TV drama I saw the other day!
Excuse me, Miss Ohba?
All right, it's decided! I, the Great
Eimi, will take you out for some fun!
Huh?
You can talk to me
about absolutely anything!
And as for those bullying rivals
and staff members, I'll kick their asses!
Huh? Do you mean
you're going to be my friend?
Friend?
That'd be great! Yeah!
I'll be your friend, Asahi!
Okay...
Now that that's decided,
the first thing we have to do is...
We have to take a ton of
pictures of the two of us together,
as a symbol of our friendship!
Really?
Come on, let's just do it.
Yes, but...
Miss Ohba?
Ready? Okay, smile!
You can just call me Eimi.
We're friends after all!
Huh? Oh, okay...
What the heck is this?
This isn't any good!
We have to take another one!
Let's do it one more time, Asahi.
Okay...
That time I closed my eyes!
That one was bad too! One more time!
Okay!
Ugh, I'm the only one
who doesn't look cute!
That's not true!
No! I don't ever compromise!
--Okay, say "cheese"!
--Cheese.
"Peach" "Studio Tanaka"
Recording for "Peach" will be starting soon.
Please get ready, everyone.
Friends send each other email, you know?
Email?
Yeah! Friends email each
other about what happened today,
what they're doing,
and different stuff like that.
Well, you can write about anything, really.
The important thing is it just
kind of makes you feel connected.
But I wonder what I should email her about?
It's from Ms. Ohba... I mean Eimi.
"Hello, Asahi! How is your day going?"
"I'm in Classics class right now."
"The teacher's lecture is so boring,"
"I just want it to end already!"
"What about you, Asahi?
I'll email you again, all right?"
"What about you, Asahi?"
"I'll email you again, all right?"
"I'll email you again,"
"What about you, Asahi?"
"I'll email you again, 'kay?"
"Sent"
"How are you?" "Hello, Asahi!" (^0^)/
"How is your day going?" v(^0^)v (*^_^*)
How should I reply?
What? You're friends with Asahi?
Yup! She begged me to be her friend!
Well, I guess one idol attracts another!
They say genius comes right
when you've almost forgotten about it!
That's "natural disasters."
So, why is he all depressed over there?
Why?
How could Asahi
disregard a pure and innocent man
of spotless integrity such as myself,
and choose such a blundering
idiot of a girl for her friend?
And who exactly is pure?
Oh! It's from Asahi!
What did you say?
Show us Asahi's
heavenly email immediately!
But it's someone else's email.
But I'm curious too.
What does it say? Tell me too.
What am I going to do with you guys?
All right, just a little.
"It's Asahi"
"I'm fine. Asahi"
That's it?
That's more like a telegram.
What an incredibly
simple yet stirring phrase!
Bravo, Asahi!
But this isn't the kind
of email you send to a friend!
You have to write more,
or it's totally boring!
But since this is Asahi we're talking about,
I'm sure she put a lot of
thought into it before she wrote it.
But still...
"It's Asahi"
"I'm fine. Asahi"
Oh well...
Shopping?
Right!
After emailing, the next
step is going shopping together!
Then we'll watch a movie,
eat some hamburgers,
and last we'll go to the beach
and yell "You stupid jerk!" to each other.
That's how it always goes with friends!
"You stupid jerk"?
That doesn't seem right...
And besides, shopping is...
Come on, let's just do it!
Today, I'll be your stylist, Asahi!
I'll pick out some clothes
that are perfect for you!
Come on, let's go!
"♪1 in France" "Jean-Paul Evan"
"Making a comeback here at Comic Party"
Hurry up!
How about that? I think
it would look perfect on you!
You think so? Isn't it a little childish?
Not at all!
You look good in anything. You're so cute!
Oh, stop...
Sure you are, sure you are!
Well, I'd say you're almost as cute as me!
Excuse me...
Wow, the Great Eimi has fans
even here? It's so tough being an idol.
It really is Asahi Sakurai!
That last episode of "Peach" was great!
Are you filming today? Or are you off?
Oh yeah! Could you sign here?
Uh, well...
Hey, stop it you guys!
You're bothering my friend!
Friend? You're a friend? Of Asahi's?
Yeah, that's right!
You must be joking.
We're talking to the idol Asahi, right now,
so mundanes like you should keep quiet.
Mun... Mun... Mundane?
Who are you calling mundane?
Who do you think I am?
Eimi...
Asahi?
I'm sorry!
You'll pay for this!
Asahi!
I'm sorry.
Our shopping trip
was ruined because of me.
--Who...
--Huh?
Who are they calling mundane?
Who do those otaku think I am?!
I'm the Super Idol of
Comipa, the Great Eimi!
They think that I, the Great Eimi,
am just a mundane who isn't fit to be
friends with the super idol Asahi Sakurai?!
What are you saying, Eimi?
I'll show them!
I'll show them clear as night
that even I'm an idol in this field!
Right, Asahi?
Ri... Right...
It's "clear as day" though.
Comic Party Revolution!
Comic Party Revolution
Hmm, looks like another long line again.
It's incredible.
And they're all holding onto
200 yen just to buy my manga!
This is my true power! Incredible, isn't it?
Yes! I'm always lined up too.
But it was such a long,
hard proness to get this far!
Do you mean "process"?
"Process"
After being sold-out again and again,
then being recognized
by the preparation committee,
I finally reached the coveted peak of every
doujin circle, and was placed as a wall circle!
And beyond the peak, even
tougher challenges are waiting for me!
Catching on to the latest trends
to sell 10,000 copies every time!
Drawing the popular characters cutely!
Writing until my pen breaks!
I can kind of understand how you feel.
You understand?
I, too, wish that my
song will reach out to people,
so that my voice can be
heard by as many fans as possible.
And you're working hard so that
your manga will be read by as
many people as possible, right?
What are you saying? That's
not enough! They have to buy it!
They can't just read it,
they have to buy it too!
That's the part that feels the best!
The hall is about to open.
As always, good luck, everyone!
All right! I'm gonna
sell, sell, sell like always!
I will sell out of 10,000 copies!
Comic Party is now open.
Enter slowly, please.
Look how many people are in here already!
I'm kind of excited!
Oh come on, don't be so tense, Asahi!
What? Asahi?
Asahi? You mean that Asahi Sakurai?
You're joking, right?
Is that true?
It's really her!
Whoa! It really is Asahi
Sakurai! What is she doing here?
That's lovely Asahi in those glasses!
Could I get your autograph?
You're causing a disturbance,
so please form a line!
Stop, I can't buy a book!
--Shut up! Who cares about that?
--Get in a line!
Eimi...
How did this happen? Boo hoo hoo...
Oww!
Where do you think you're pulling?!
So, your circle was forced to
shut down because of the commotion?
Minami's tough.
"KEEP OUT"
Okay, you're all being taken out.
I hadn't even started selling yet!
Oww...
Hey, don't move around so much.
This will teach you a lesson!
Not that an idiot can
actually learn anything from it!
What do you mean
by that, hot spring panda?
That's what you get for being so greedy!
I can't believe you
used Asahi as a sales girl.
Yeah, you may be her
friend or whatever, but...
I didn't do anything wrong!
I...
By the way, where's Asahi?
I... I don't know.
It looks like we got
separated in all that commotion!
Unbelievable!
Not only did you use Asahi's
popularity in a plot to increase your sales,
you neglected the heartbroken girl!
That is simply outrageous!
You've got it wrong! I wasn't using Asahi!
You probably got close to
Asahi for your doujinshi, but...
The expression "The plotter
always gets caught in his own plots"
fits this situation perfectly, I believe.
You couldn't stop our
world conquest even if you tried!
Quiet, you!
Eimi...
I don't care.
I'm telling you, I don't care!
If it was going to turn out like this,
I wish we'd never become friends!
Now look here, you!
I finally found you.
I heard what happened.
It must've been rough.
It wasn't your fault.
But...
I completely ruined
Eimi's all-important Comipa.
Asahi...
I don't know how to apologize to Eimi.
I don't think it matters how.
I think that if you're friends,
it doesn't matter how you apologize.
How about you talk to her?
Kazuki...
Eimi was really happy that
she became friends with you.
She was?
"It's Asahi"
"I'm fine. Asahi"
"Mail"
"New Mail"
"Inbox"
"Delete Selected Item"
"Compose New Message"
"Sender: Asahi"
"Receiving... Asahi"
What's with her?
I said this wasn't the kind
of email to send to a friend!
"Asahi"
"I'm sorry. Asahi"
"Seaside Park Station"
You stupid jerk of an ocean!
Stop looking so big!
Who do you think I am?!
Eimi...
Come on, what are you all serious for?
But because of me...
I'm sorry.
You don't think I still have
some books left unsold, do you?
Don't worry.
I consigned my books
to Brother 2, and sold out!
Really?
It doesn't matter where they get sold.
You're pretty naive if you think
you can underestimate the Great Eimi!
Here!
This is...
It's for you!
Then I'll get you some money.
Nah...
Giving each other copies of the doujinshi
we've made is a sign of friendship!
Eimi...
Um, but I don't have a book to give you.
That's all right.
I'll wait for you to give me one
if you ever do draw a doujinshi.
Huh? Did you buy something else?
Ah! Th... This is, well...
I was just wondering what
manga that doesn't sell is like, and...
Oh, that's...
You bought it too?
By the way, do you
have someone you like, Eimi?
What? What brought
that on all of a sudden?
The script for the episode
of "Peach" I read the other day
said that friends start out
by talking about boyfriends.
Huh?
Well? Do you?
Speaking of which, what about you, Asahi?
Me? That's a secret.
That's no fair!
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Doujin...
The doujinshi of horror:
once you turn the page,
- -you lose 100 days
of your doujin life span.
- -you lose 100 days of your doujin life span.
--Doujin...
It's the demon manga,
which poisons the sensitivity
- -Doujin...
--and destroys the mind of those who look at it.
--It is a forbidden book which was burned
in a remote old college building.
- -Doujin...
--Now, let us go, young people,
beyond that door of horror!
Next time: "The Poison Doujin of Horror."
Has my doujin arrived?