Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Asahi Sakurai"
"New Single: Loving Feelings"
"Please Listen to My Feelings!"
So we were thinking about a concert
as part of the promotion
for her new single.
Okay, now I get the general idea.
By the way, the lyrics for the new
song will be written by Asahi herself.
My, that sounds exciting.
Yes, she's excited about it too.
I will work out the
details with the director.
Yes, please do.
I will be in touch with you again later.
Now then, it was nice talking with you.
Huh?
That girl...
She always comes to Comipa.
Huh? Ms. Makimura,
do you know Asahi Sakurai?
Huh?
No, I was talking about that girl.
Mmm, delicious.
The chamomile tea
here is great, isn't it?
Yes...
But at any rate, how
strange to meet you there!
Were you working at your part-time job?
No, it's not a part-time job.
Working for an entertainment
agency sure sounds interesting.
Yeah, it is fun, but...
What's wrong?
Is something worrying you?
It's not really worrying me.
I guess you could say
it does bother me though, well...
Oh dear, that's not good.
I could listen, if you'd like.
Well, the thing I'm writing
right now isn't going very well.
My, are you talking about a doujinshi?
Huh? No...
So you've started
writing manga now too, huh?
Reading them is fine,
but writing them yourself makes
the doujinshi world even more fun!
So, what kind of
story do you want to write?
--It's basically about love.
--My, that's so nice!
Oh, don't tell me it's
going to be a "boys love" story?
No! Not at all!
How do I put this...
I want to write something that will create
gentle feelings that warm you up inside.
Yu says...
Oh, do you know Yu?
The girl from Karamitei?
Yes!
She always says,
"Doujinshi are made of your
love for the story and characters!"
I guess she's right.
It's just like falling
in love with someone.
Is there anyone that you like?
No, there isn't.
Eimi says you can't
make a catchy doujinshi
if you can't even go on a single date.
Have you ever been on a date?
Uh... No...
Hmmm, I see.
Oh no, I have to get back!
Well, good luck!
Right!
Welcome!
Wow, so they put you in charge?
It's so hard...
Yeah, I guess so.
But you've gotten to the age
where you take positions like that.
Please don't mention my age!
Besides, I'm younger than you anyway.
Well, it just means you've gotten
one step closer to your dream, right?
I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
Ah, oh yeah.
Hey, what do you think is
important when writing manga?
When writing manga?
Well, not just when writing
manga, but when creating anything.
Let me think...
You mean, for example, how I say
that writers, particularly new ones,
need to always be in love?
I thought so.
Even a one-sided love is fine.
You just have to be in love with someone.
Well, I guess it's basically about
cultivating your sensitivity
by receiving mental stimulation.
Of course, there are some people who ruin
themselves by drowning in love though.
Why do you ask? Are you
thinking about writing again?
No, not me; a girl I know.
It seems she's trying to write a
love story, but it's not going well.
Oh, is that it?
And here I thought
I was going to be able to read Minami
Makimura's first new book in a long time.
I was kind of looking forward to it.
Oh, please. Don't make fun of me.
So it all comes down to
actual experience after all.
Yeah...
Yes, hello?
Oh, hello? This is Makimura.
Ah, hello.
I'm sorry to ask you so suddenly,
but are you free this Sunday?
Ah, um, I think I'm
free in the afternoon.
That's great!
Then leave that open, okay?
I'll call you again with the details.
Bye bye!
Huh? Uh, um...
That should do it.
Now, who should I set her up with?
Who was that?
Oh, the girl I mentioned before.
Oh, is that it?
And here I thought you were
making a date with your boyfriend.
But I don't have anyone like that.
You're getting older too,
Minami, so you should get a guy or two.
--I told you not to mention my age!
--You donn' get it!
You donn' get it at all!
Huh?
Is that...
What's with you?
The color is different, isn't it?
Thass w're you're
mistaken, Comrade Kazuki.
You're obviously drunk.
What're you saying?
M' not drunk or anything!
I am completely normal!
Stop it, Taishi, you're too loud!
So what?
The only dif'rence between
the Hemo-hemo and the Hyper
Hemo-hemo is the color, yer saying?
Yeah!
Foolishness! You're foolish, Comrade!
You see, the Hyper Hemo-hemo is...
Blue!
--Like I was saying, the color is different.
--Kuhonbutsu is the same as ever.
--No, yer wrong!
It's different from the
Hemo-hemo! It's different!
Oh yeah, that girl...
always buys Kazuki's books.
That's it!
After alla my explanation,
do you still not unnerstan'?
This is embarrassing, so stop it already!
Good evening.
Huh? Minami?
Funny meeting you here.
By the way, Kazuki...
What is it?
Do you have some
time free this Sunday?
Yeah, I do...
Wonderful! In that case,
could you please go on a date?
Jeez, what is Makimura
thinking at her age? I can't believe her.
Comrade Mizuki,
isn't spying on someone
else's date considered tacky?
Shut up! I'm worried about Kazuki.
Why is that?
Well, something strange
could happen or something.
I see!
There could be people out
there who would send an assassin
to suddenly kill my friend during
the date, in order to crush our ambitions!
Nope, absolutely wrong.
Very well! I will join forces with you.
It's not like I even asked you to.
Here she comes.
Wha?!
Wha... Wha... Wha...
What in the world?!
That's...
Huh? That girl...
Why you! I don't
care if you are my friend!
I wonder why Minami didn't say
that it was you who was coming, Asahi?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
But it's not every day I get
to go out on a date with an idol.
I'm sorry.
Um, shall we go then?
Sure!
After them!
I'll never forgive him!
--Huh?
Ms. Makimura?
What are the two of you doing here?
Uh, nothing. What about you,
Minami? What are you doing here?
Umm, it's a long story...
Let's talk about it later!
We're going to lose them!
Asahi, you don't have to be so scared.
I'll be fine once it starts moving,
but climbing up slowly
like this makes me feel so...
Yeah, I guess so. It's really scary, huh?
That's nice. They seem to be having fun.
What's with him, being all flirty?
Damn you, my friend...
By the way, what is this all about?
Umm, the truth is...
And there you have it.
Well, if that's all it is.
However!
Whatever the reason may be,
I absolutely cannot
forgive something like this!
I have reached the limits of my
perseverance! I am going to resort to force!
Hold it, Taishi! Jeez...
I wonder if Taishi likes that girl?
It looks like it.
He said he was a member of her fan club.
My, she has a fan club?
Umm, I don't really know.
Okay, I'm going to leave now.
But it will be a problem
if I let him get in their way.
Say, isn't this a haunted house?
Well, yeah, I think so.
It'll be all right!
The stuff here isn't very
typical, so it's more like a show.
This is young people's gateway to love,
the pitch black paradise
where they can deepen their love!
Riding in a gondola in the deep
darkness, two shadows become one,
and before you know it,
the mood becomes romantic!
I won't let that happen!
What's going on?
You mustn't cut in line.
Be sure to wait your turn, okay?
Okay, come this way please.
Ow ow ow ow ow
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow!
Huh? Was that Minami I just heard?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Thank you!
Back off, Kazuki.
I recognize that voice.
I knew it was you, Taishi.
My my, Taishi is very tenacious too.
Back off from Asahi.
But Minami asked me to go out with her.
I am well aware of the situation.
But I, Asahi Sakurai fan
club member number 00001,
cannot allow such a thing to
happen right before my very eyes.
If you insist on continuing,
my air gun will blaze!
Hey, come on now...
I am dead serious!
I will say it one more time: back off.
If you do not, it
will wound our friendship.
As if I care about that.
Go on now, go say goodbye to Asahi.
Here, Asahi.
We're getting out of here!
Bastard! I won't let you escape!
Wait!
I can't turn! I can't turn!
I'm falling!
Good grief...
Say, what's the matter?
Well...
I guess you could say I spotted someone
stalking you and got away from there fast.
Oh my!
Just kidding!
Actually, I was just in
a hurry to be alone with you.
But today must have
been a bother for you.
Of course not! I'm honored to
be able to go on a date with you.
Besides, I heard the
whole story from Minami.
If I can help you with
writing your doujinshi,
I'm happy to do anything you need.
Uh, well, it's not a doujinshi.
Huh?
Actually, I have to write
the lyrics to my new song,
but it's not going very well.
That's what it was?
I can't find the right words,
and I don't know what to write.
I want to say something to
my fans, but... I don't know how.
I've been thinking
about it for a long time.
Maybe you don't have
to think too much about it.
I'm sure everyone just wants to
hear the words that come from you.
Besides...
Besides?
I want to hear that song too.
Boy, Minami sure is a scatterbrain.
She thought you were writing doujinshi!
She's a really nice person though.
Yeah, a very nice person.
Looks like it's going well.
I'm glad I asked Kazuki.
But...
I think I might be a little jealous.
This tastes so good right after a bath!
Yes?
Minami?
Oh, Kazuki! Thank
you so much for today!
No, thank you! I had a fun date.
I'm sorry for asking such a big favor.
You can ask me for
any kind of favor, Minami.
Then would you go
on a date with me next?
Sure, my pleasure.
Oh come on, I was just joking.
What? A joke?
But I was looking forward to it!
By the way, how is your
manuscript coming along?
Excellent!
I'll make it in time for the
next Comipa with time to spare.
That's great.
And good luck with
Asahi's concert, Minami.
Thanks!
Okay then, goodnight!
Goodnight!
Good morning, Kazuki!
Oh, good morning!
Huh? Where's Taishi?
Oh, he's been pouting and
hasn't talked to me since that date.
Taishi must have liked
that girl with glasses a lot.
Oh, is this your new issue?
"Record Of The Japalan Era"
"The New Issue is Here!"
I'll take one. How much is it?
No, that's okay. You're always
helping me out, so it's a gift.
Oh yeah! Sorry, but
could you take another one?
Huh?
Excuse me.
Oh, hello.
Good luck today.
Yes, thank you very much!
Um, here, take this.
I got it from someone I know.
Oh! It's Mr. Sendo's new issue!
Thank you very much.
You know his doujinshi?
Huh? Uh, yes.
His manga is so good, isn't it?
Speaking of which,
I set up a date between him
and one of his fans a little while ago.
I was worried, so I secretly
followed them around,
but I lost sight of
them in the middle of it.
I was in such a panic, and then...
Uh, say, I've been
wondering about something.
Yes?
Could it be...
What?
Huh? It's you.
You didn't realize?
Oh, I didn't know!
I have to go thank Mr. Sendo again.
Do you like Kazuki's manga?
Yes! Very much!
I see.
I really like them too.
Miss Sakurai! It's almost time!
Oh, okay!
See you later, good luck.
Thanks!
Hello, everyone! I'm Asahi Sakurai!
Please listen to this new song that
I've poured all of my feelings into!
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
The time has finally come!
Huh?
Cosplay Fight!
The contest to decide the strongest
cosplayer in the country, no, the world!
It's time for a showdown, Mizuki Takase!
I've heard that Mizuki
is going to quit cosplaying.
What are you saying?
If you beat Mizuki in this contest,
you'll get a boys love
book written by Sendo!
Seriously? I'll do it! I'm going for the win!
Then we'll get his first boys love book!
Boys love book, boys love book,
a Kazuki Sendo boys love book!
Next time: "Fierce Battle! Cosplay Fight!"
I'm not gonna lose!