Are you done yet?
I really thought I was going to die.
Suddenly, only hot air was coming out.
It broke...
I couldn't sleep at all
since it was so hot.
Don't sleep now!
Yeah, we need to fix the lyrics
and songs by the festival.
We're fixing them?
I like them the way they are.
Really?
What don't you like about them?
Well... How do I say this...
Simply put, they just sound ordinary.
What do you think, Tomo?
What?
Look, I can't deal with
your perfectionism. I quit.
Then me, too.
I think they're fine, I guess.
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
THE WANING MOON WAS OUT
Why didn't you say anything?
You mentioned to me that something was
bothering you about Momoka's new songs.
No reason.
I thought they were fine.
I see.
That's fine then.
It's not eating at all.
You're gonna die if you don't.
Who could it be?
A neighborhood notice?
Could you get it
since our mailbox is broken?
Yes?
-Good evening! It's Nina!
-No thank you.
Wait, I haven't said anything yet!
What?!
It's so cool.
Don't steal our air-conditioned air!
It's not like you'll run out.
Stop yelling!
You're annoying the neighbors!
You're the one yelling!
Stop ringing the bell!
Paradise.
Leave after you cool down.
That's so cruel.
The AC repairman
won't come until next week!
Not my problem.
Does Momoka not have air conditioning?
She does, but she works nights.
I've been wondering.
Isn't it a bit weak?
DON'T USE
It's so cool.
A big difference from your janky AC.
Don't call it janky!
It's pretty janky if it can't run on high!
Well, it was labeled not to!
So, anyway.
Both of our apartment AC units broke.
We would appreciate some time
in your cool air.
Please, just one hour!
This is all her fault, by the way.
Okay, fine.
Just one hour!
Oh, that's Tomo's pet.
It doesn't like the heat.
-Wait...
-What?!
Don't just release it!
So powerful.
Stop saying that.
What an amazing apartment.
Good grief.
Oh, it's Momoka.
She works nearby,
so she's going to drop by later.
Really?
I'M WORKING NEARBY
I'LL SWING BY IN ABOUT 30
Then maybe we can all eat together here.
ROGER
When did that become an option?
You said only an hour.
Look.
Huh?
We missed our last train.
Looks like it.
I bet this was your plan from the start!
Now, now. How about we play cards?
You're well prepared!
I realized that we've never done
anything like this before.
Then since there's four of us...
-Count me out.
-What?
I'm borrowing this room.
I also have Ametaro Dentetsu.
Wanna try the 100-year mode?
We'll be up all night.
Did I do something?
You've done plenty.
No, it's not your fault.
Really?
Let me check on her.
Heading to bed first?
No.
You three can play cards
or whatever without me.
Just leave me alone.
Okay.
If you've got a complaint, say it.
A complaint? Why would I have a complaint?
LOSER BUYS BEEF BOWLS
I've lost.
What am I looking at?
You're the cause of all of this, Nina.
No!
It's my AC's fault!
Just tough it out.
I did!
I killed time at the convenience store,
hung out on a bench for an hour,
but it's so boring being outdoors
when you can't spend money!
-Where's Tomo?
-She went to bed.
Did she say anything about our songs?
Not particularly.
I see.
It looked like she had something to say.
Where are you going?
The fridge.
Can't have these going warm.
What do you think will happen
if my grandma finds them?!
Don't worry, I'll drink them all
by morning...
Snake?
It's Tomo's pet.
Don't worry, it's calm and not venomous.
Snake!
What a waste!
No!
What?
Momoka.
Momoka!
You can't lock yourself in there.
Get rid of it already!
I guess Momoka doesn't like snakes.
So old-fashioned.
It's a snake!
How are you all okay?
It's not a big deal.
That's weird!
How can all four of you
be fine with snakes?!
Just spend some time with it.
There's a snake behind you, Momoka.
A NORMAL HAIR DRYER
Oh!
It opened.
No!
Beer-tiful save!
Hold on!
-Momoka!
-Just get rid of it!
If we get caught doing that,
I'll be the one who gets in trouble!
Besides, we already put it
in the same room as Tomo.
So come out already.
Hey. You'll break--
No way.
You're not a child anymore.
-It's going to break!
-Nina!
How was that?
Seriously?
All of you!
-How could you?!
-You're nonassertive, aren't you?
Never come back.
So hot.
Whose fault is that?!
You all get along so well.
We don't!
I'm off to work.
Take care.
Get rid of that snake.
Where's the snake, by the way?
Subaru offered to keep it for now.
I wish I were the snake.
Well, we're done here.
Rupa, let's go.
We need to check up on the apartment.
What? You're ditching me?
Why do I have to hang out with you
when it's not even for practice?
Momoka said it's important
to do things like that.
If you have time,
can you watch me practice?
I'll go grab my guitar from the apartment!
An acoustic guitar?
Yeah.
When I asked Mine for advice,
she said to practice if I wanted to play.
And that this is old but a good guitar.
The second string's off.
Really?
That's so impressive.
You've been playing piano
since you were young?
That's unrelated, anybody could tell
when it's this off-key.
But guitars are amazing.
You really do get callouses
as you practice.
Is it okay now?
It's still a little off,
but it's probably the best you can do.
Here I go.
How's that?
I thought we'd play it at the next show.
You've really improved.
Go for it.
Adding an extra guitar
will elevate our sound.
-No.
-What?
You can't play a show at your skill level.
Tomo.
Tomo!
How was it?
How was it, Rupa?
It's not my expertise.
Well, I don't play the guitar either.
But you know a lot about music, right?
I guess.
It seemed fine...
as a hobby.
Hobby?
So not on stage?
Do you want to play on stage?
Yeah.
I realized something
when we went to the Diamond Dust show.
I want to become better.
Not just rely on Momoka.
I want to contribute.
Oh, I mean, with all of you too.
So let me know
if there's something I can improve.
It was fine.
Tell me! Tomo!
With your talent,
you'll never be good enough!
I see.
Girls Band Cry.
I keep telling you to play seriously--
Stop measuring us to your standards.
We're not like you, who's been winning
piano awards since you were little.
I can't do this.
-Um--
-Stay out of this.
Look,
I talked to her yesterday, but...
It's gotten cooler.
Has it?
It's good to go without the AC
from time to time.
You can feel the temperature
change gradually on your skin.
THANK YOU FOR TODAY
STILL HOT AT HOME
Nina was happy.
Of course she wasn't.
You got some guts coming back here.
I wanted your advice on something.
Huh?
I didn't come to use your AC!
Really?
I'm here for something serious
about the band.
I'LL REIMBURSE YOU.
(IN 36 INSTALLMENTS PLEASE) NINA
How was that?
What did Tomo tell you?
She said that with my talent,
I'll never be good enough.
Oof, that's harsh.
Though I'm sure
that's partly her personality.
Did you lose motivation?
Why would I?
Well, as long as you're not bothered.
So, what did you think, Subaru?
I guess I agree with Tomo.
Yeah?
I thought I practiced enough
to be able to play onstage.
It's not something you can do
only after a year or two.
Maybe if you were an amateur,
but not if you're aiming to go pro.
But you're managing.
I'm not so sure.
I bet Tomo has a lot
she'd like to say about me.
But she's never said anything, right?
Because I don't go out of my way
to ask her like you.
Tomo's probably a little timid.
She keeps her distance because
she doesn't want to be hated.
She never approaches people herself.
But if we approach her instead...
Grr!
That sounds like me.
Yeah, you were like that too.
Thank you.
I got it an aquarium, so take it with you.
It hasn't eaten though. Is that okay?
It's fine.
Oh! Tomo!
You're still at it?
Yeah.
I had Subaru listen too.
Ow.
Seems fine to me.
You should play on stage if you want to.
Why are you lying?
-I see.
-Oh.
Tomo?
Disbanded?
She came to Tokyo,
recruited members online,
and started a band.
Is that how you met her?
Yes, there was also a drummer
and a guitarist.
They said they were aiming to go pro.
Yeah, well, everyone says that.
Yeah?
People who are successful say that
they didn't have to work hard at all.
But if that was really the case,
anybody could be successful.
Exactly.
Tomo knows that too.
That's why she kept saying that
we weren't good enough.
Since she believed
we all felt the same way,
she became more and more demanding.
Yeah, I can see that.
But you still stayed with her.
Though Tomo said she'd set out on her own.
But being so young...
RENTAL GUARANTOR CONSENT FORM
Guarantor?
I don't plan to contact my parents.
I promise not to be a burden.
That's when we started living together
and formed beni-shouga together.
We had opportunities to go pro, but...
Each time, she'd butt heads
with someone and ruin it.
And because of that, I think she's become
scared to say how she feels.
That if she shared her true self,
it would ruin everything.
What do you think, Momoka?
My guitar skills.
Am I good enough to play on stage?
Are you serious?
I thought so.
I'm home.
You're late.
Oh! It's eating!
Look!
You're right!
No matter how scared you are,
you won't get anywhere
if you're just watching.
What do you mean?
Okay, Tomo.
Let's go for a walk.
It's not cooling down at all.
We're back to band practice tomorrow.
I hope it doesn't rain.
I'm not wrong.
I said she's bad because she is.
She's just not good enough.
Then why did you tell her
she could play on stage?
That's...
Because Nina's hoping to...
To play guitar on stage with Momoka.
That's why she asked you.
She wants to improve.
That's what they all say.
That they're serious, or want to improve.
But they end up just wanting compliments
or sing whatever way that feels good.
Can you hear that?
Ow.
Um...
Like this, this, and this.
Do what I tell you, stupid fingers!
I realized something
when we saw the three of them play.
These people are serious.
It doesn't matter how good they are.
They give it their all on stage.
I'm pretty sure
that's all you're looking for too.
You suck!
What...
I'm gonna get better!
You suck.
I love this sort of thing.
What's wrong?
It's just not feeling right.
What isn't?
It's fine.
Let's take a break.
Momoka.
I think this song is boring the way it is.
Right?
dareka ni somarenai dare ni mo narenai
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
yume da to omotte waratte miseta
I laughed, thinking it a dream
wasureta yowasa kajikande iku
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
samishii nante ieru wake mo nai
I can't even say that I'm lonely
sarigenai kaiwa sura kizutsuku kokoro wa
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
dare hitori dare hitori shiawase ni shinai
Is incapable of making anyone happy
nee sore demo mada kitai fukuramunda
But still, I feel a growing hope
surechigatta uso nante zenbu sutete
Moving past all of the lies
daisoretenai yo tte tada kikitakute
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
yume bakari de osanakutatte
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
kyou mo kawarenai mama datte iinda
I don't care if I'm still the same today
kimi to utatte itai
I just want to sing with you
nando datte kanjou bakka yure ugoite
My emotions stir so often
kirawarete kita kedo
I've been hated
kono mama de aruite yukunda
But I'm going to keep walking
darenimo narenai watashi mune hatte sa
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
tada hitori demo
Even if I'm alone
magiremonai jibun wo shinjite
I believe in myself
kizutsuki ochiru tabi utaeba ii
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next episode, "Wandervogel"