Okay, look over here.
Everyone looks so beautiful.
They've been retouched.
What?! Really?
You're right.
Her nose looks straighter.
Don't use me to check!
We'll choose a photo
when you sign your contract.
Okay!
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
THE SKY DARKENS AGAIN
What? Their part-time job?
You could've told me.
Today is Rupa and Tomo's
last day at the store.
They really wanted to go
since the job has been good to them.
Well, I understand then.
Sorry.
That's the CEO's doing.
Water bottles with our company name on it.
Togenashi Togeari water?
My throat feels scratchy
just hearing that.
Okay, the contracts look in order.
Which means as of now,
you are all officially part of our agency.
I, Miura, will be responsible for you.
I'm honored.
Us too.
Thank you.
And so, we were able to join an agency.
What?
200,000 yen?
Yeah, I think she said
on the 25th of each month?
And we can use it?
Of course.
It's our salary.
Really?!
I bet you didn't read the whole contract.
Obviously, the money
comes with certain conditions.
One day suddenly,
they demand you star in an adult-y video!
"It's in your contract!"
Keep it down.
But Subaru's...
It won't be like that.
The agency just gets a percentage
of our earnings.
Merch, concerts, and albums too.
The agency will help promote us,
and if we make it big, it's a win-win.
OPEN PRICE
79,200 YEN
Well, that's the gist of it.
I hope we can...
What? You're surprisingly not confident.
Are you still hung up
on that music festival?
I bet you're egosurfing, aren't you?
Of course!
We put on such a great show!
But all they talk about is D-D!
I know our show was way better!
I said keep it down.
Besides, we were on different stages.
And it's no surprise considering an idol
band impressed even the rock aficionados.
Of course they're going viral.
But we were great too! Why not us?!
Don't ask me.
Well, there still were people
who gave us recognition.
And it led to our contract.
But still...
I told you not to egosurf.
Sorry.
You don't have to rush.
The competition is just starting.
Right.
I guess you've been
thinking about it a lot too.
-Ow!
BEEF BOWL
Here you go.
CONTRACT ENCLOSED
Your copies of the contract.
Also, congrats on your last day!
What is that?
Just take it!
What would you like to order?
One medium bowl.
But we're having hot pot after this!
One beer and one medium bowl.
What? You're gonna drink?
Don't worry, I'll drink tonight too.
Then I'll have a medium bowl too.
Okay, wait one moment.
We came here a lot.
This was the first place
I bought you dinner.
Really?
It took her four hours to get here
from Tokyo Station,
and she was crying about
not having her key and whatnot.
How bad with directions are you?
THANK YOU. WE WON'T FORGET
THE BENI-SHOUGA SOUL.
No, it's because the Yokosuka Line
is so complicated.
Tomo.
Thanks for everything.
You too, although,
we're just getting started.
Now, it's time to kick off
our party for signing our contract!
Huh?
They said they just left work,
so they'll be here soon.
Okay.
They had some things
they needed to wrap up.
Ow.
I never knew raw pumpkins were so hard.
My, it's been a while, princess.
It's not like that!
I've told you before.
What is it?
Actually, you may have been right.
You know how you taught me a lot
when I first moved here?
I was really shocked at the time.
That I couldn't do anything.
That I didn't even realize
how much I didn't know.
Are you better now though?
Yes!
I'll keep working on the guitar though.
Are you sure this was for the best?
We just all need to get to a point
where we can say that it was.
Okay, okay.
We're here!
Sorry we're late.
It's freezing!
It's colder in here!
Oh! Beer! Beer! Beer!
Geez...
Also, I made our band logo.
What?
Cheers!
Don't start without us!
We haven't even kicked it off yet!
They can't hear you.
Honestly.
I guess we can start too.
Okay, fine.
I told you
I like my Napa cabbage really soft.
-I also like it soft.
-See?
You two are such a pain!
We have our preferences!
-Yes.
-Shut up.
It tastes way better this way.
It's started already.
It needs texture to be good.
I'll convert you to our side.
Try it!
-Come on, eat it.
-That's so hot!
-You can do it.
-What is this, an old skit?
-Let's eat it together.
-It's too hot!
-What is it?
-Don't be picky!
An idea for a song.
I came up with a title.
DAYS LATER
Wow...
So cool!
Good morning.
This is your engineer, Mr. Nakata.
I'm Nakata, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
And his assistant, Mr. Nakano.
Nice to meet you!
And Mr. Tanaka, the AP.
I'm Tanaka.
And Mr. Tano with promotions.
I'm Tano!
What?!
I don't think I can memorize all that.
Well, memorizing names
becomes part of the job.
Did you memorize them already?
Of course. It's common sense
for a grown-up after all.
Then what's the engineer's name?
Mr. Tanaka.
It's Nakata.
I'm sorry!
Don't laugh.
The song is the one you gave us
the other day, right?
Yeah, I put in some temporary lyrics.
Here.
Stop laughing already.
Sorry.
This title...
Yeah.
It's inspired by all of you.
When I thought about
what our first song should be,
I knew it had to be about us.
Momoka...
Okay, let's get started.
Nina.
If you're serious about beating on D-D,
put your heart into this.
Yeah.
The five of us began writing our new song.
BUDOKAN, HERE WE COME!
OPEN PRICE
79,200 YEN
BUDOKAN
Was it too much?
You think so? I think it's fine.
What about moving that part
to the beginning?
I guess that wouldn't be bad.
Yeah. We can try redoing it.
I'm sorry, but it's quite late.
Okay.
HEIWAJIMA STATION
We made it.
Good night.
I'll text you later.
It's pretty fun.
What is?
Making a new song for ourselves.
When I imagine it reaching
someone else soon...
It's not that easy.
Sometimes it never reaches anyone,
no matter how much you want it to.
Don't worry.
Look how hard we're working on it.
It'll be fine.
This part still bothers me.
Do you want to listen from this side?
Okay.
Huh? Where's Ms. Miura?
She stepped out for a call.
Can you go get her?
She should probably listen to it, too.
Okay.
-Ms. Miura...
-D-D?!
Really?
I see. I'll call back later.
Momoka wanted you
to listen to our song too.
Did you overhear that?
No.
I see.
What about Diamond Dust?
VALENTINE! BATTLE OF THE BANDS
DIAMOND DUST X TOGENASHI TOGEARI
They sent this over earlier.
Club Citta for two days.
First day, Diamond Dust.
Second day, Togenashi Togeari.
For real?
On a big stage?
It'll be in February.
It's like they know our song's schedule.
They want it to coincide with Valentine's.
Sounds good to me!
Bring it on!
Please read the next page.
You will compete over
ticket sales and attendees,
and the winner's song will be chosen
for a TV show's theme song.
I see.
That's how it is.
What is?
MARUFUKU COFFEE SHOP
We can't win?
Why give up before we even try?
-We won't--
-It's obvious!
D-D has doubled their follower count.
It's a fixed race.
They brought this to us
because they know they'll win.
Then they can openly say
they're better than us.
But...
But we'll be on the same stage this time!
Then we just need to get everyone pumped
like at the festival!
Think about it.
What?
The unfair thing about this is that
we're not playing to the same crowd.
We might be facing off,
but we're both playing solo.
Which means what's important isn't
the performance, but the crowd draw.
The more famous one will always win.
That's unfair.
There's no point in getting mad.
What do the D-D members think about this?
No idea.
They don't think anything of it.
At the very least,
the girl I know, Hina, won't care.
She sees nothing wrong with
getting an advantage.
I feel like talking about this
will start an argument.
What's wrong with that?
It happens a lot on TV.
Like throwing beer or drinks
at each other.
I've already been through that.
What?! Really?
Then...
All we can do is vote.
Who thinks we should do it?
Who thinks we shouldn't?
I see.
We discussed it as a group
and we think it's too soon.
We need more time to prepare.
Understood.
I'll let them know we decline.
Thank you.
What did you think about this?
Nina.
Honestly, I was torn.
I thought winning would be difficult,
but doing this against D-D
would help with your publicity.
Then...
But at the same time,
if the results are too one-sided,
it will leave the impression
that you're unpopular.
Were they aiming for that as well?
Build each other up
or tear each other down.
Either one could just be for show
or their real goal.
Honestly, I don't know.
Phew, I'm tired.
Everything seems like a scheme.
It's like we're in the adult world now.
What?
You still think we should do it?
I'm wondering if this is what
being a pro is going to be like.
You're the one who chose this path.
We're back.
It's not feeling right.
We can go back to the old phrase.
That wasn't working either.
It might be faster to just
rewrite it from scratch.
I guess we could.
What? Really?
The same part from before?
Yeah.
It seems a little dated,
and people might not like it.
Yeah?
I guess key changes are trendy now.
Like that?
Yeah.
Momoka.
What?
It seems like you're thinking too hard
and you're drifting further
from where we started.
This is supposed to be
our song by you, right?
Then why not just let it be that?
All that's important is
whether or not it is our song.
I think that's all that matters.
I will see you again tomorrow.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I still want to take on D-D.
I understand there are
other things at play here.
But we'll get to headline
our own show, right?
And we can sing our songs?
Yeah, we will, but...
Then I think we should do it!
I don't think we should ever
run away from playing our music.
If we do that...
We lose?
Yeah.
Can't we do it?
Momoka?
You should decide.
You're the one with the most history
with Diamond Dust.
Nina, Subaru, and Tomo,
you're okay with that, right?
What do you say?
CONSECRATION
S-So cold.
Really? I'm totally warm.
It's perfect fall weather.
What?! You northerners are crazy.
My legs are bare over here!
As expected of a high school girl.
What's that supposed to mean?
Honestly!
This is your neighborhood, right, Nina?
Why are we at a shrine?
It's actually the perfect time
for visiting shrines or temples.
So you're here to pray?
I see.
Did you ever visit shrines
with Nana or the rest of D-D on New Years?
Nope.
We didn't have time for prayers,
and it wasn't my thing.
I see.
But we can use all the help we can get,
be it from the gods or anyone.
If they exist, that is.
What is it, Momoka?
It's weird how irritated you've been.
Oh, that's it?
The song's just not going how I want...
Liar.
I don't want you to lie to us.
I'm scared.
The more I start writing seriously,
the more I start reliving that anxiety.
I get scared that
I might lose it all again.
I knew it.
That you were suffering.
We were all alone in this world.
But we had music.
Even now, your passion
still flows through me, Momoka.
And that's brought me all to you.
I trust this feeling
and our music.
So please trust yourself.
I want to create the story of
Togenashi Togeari.
I want the five of us
to continue to have the same dream.
I believe the god of rock exists.
That'd be nice.
If the god of rock existed,
what would you ask them?
To sell a million CDs, obviously.
How about 10 million then?
More! 100 million!
I'm asking to let us beat D-D at our show.
Momoka.
What?
There you go.
Do you have any thoughts?
I think it's good.
Yeah.
This seems clearest.
I like it, too.
I try not to express
if I like a song or not.
Right.
And I swear this isn't flattery,
but I like how it is now.
It properly has
all the things you want in it.
I've watched you all these last few weeks,
and this song is true to yourselves.
Really?
So it felt fulfilling to work on it.
I'm glad I took this job
helping a band like yours.
Just saying.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Tanaka!
It's Nakata.
I'll let you know
when the mixing process is done.
When will it be uploaded online?
If everything goes smoothly,
we're on schedule
for the start of next month.
Bye then.
I like it too.
I believe this song will be a hit.
Ms. Miura!
Yes?
Thank you!
Thank you.
It's too early to thank me.
We're just starting.
Bye then.
It's freezing.
Okay then.
Dear god of rock,
I wish for a billion views...
But even 10,000 will be enough.
Please.
Please!
VIEWS: 103
What is this...
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
dareka ni somarenai dare ni mo narenai
I laughed, thinking it a dream
yume da to omotte waratte miseta
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
wasureta yowasa kajikande iku
I can't even say that I'm lonely
samishii nante ieru wake mo nai
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
sarigenai kaiwa sura kizutsuku kokoro wa
Is incapable of making anyone happy
dare hitori dare hitori shiawase ni shinai
But still, I feel a growing hope
nee sore demo mada kitai fukuramunda
Moving past all of the lies
surechigatta uso nante zenbu sutete
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
daisoretenai yo tte tada kikitakute
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
yume bakari de osanakutatte
I don't care if I'm still the same today
kyou mo kawarenai mama datte iinda
I just want to sing with you
kimi to utatte itai
My emotions stir so often
nando datte kanjou bakka yure ugoite
I've been hated
kirawarete kita kedo
But I'm going to keep walking
kono mama de aruite yukunda
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
darenimo narenai watashi mune hatte sa
Even if I'm alone
tada hitori demo
I believe in myself
magiremonai jibun wo shinjite
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
kizutsuki ochiru tabi utaeba ii
Next episode,
"Rock 'n' Roll Will Never Stop"