Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Arise Kazuki, It Is Time for World Conquest!"
A professional cosplayer? What's that?
I was just talking about what
if there was something like that.
If there was,
then we'd find a job no problem!
A job? Isn't it too soon to think about that?
That's a carefree attitude to have.
Listen up.
Due to global warming,
the employment market is in an ice age!
If you take it too easy,
pretty soon you'll be too late.
Well...
But...
What's wrong, Mizuki?
Nothing really. It's no big deal.
But you've been doing
nothing but sighing for a while.
I have?
Hey, Kazuki, do you plan on
drawing doujinshi like this forever?
Huh? Uh, well...
"Uchudo"
When I get out of college, huh?
"Screen Tone"
Kazuki, is something wrong?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
The next three years are
going to go by before we know it.
If you're going to be a
professional manga artist, that's fine,
but with the way you're going,
are you trying to end up unemployed?
A pro doujinshi artist, huh?
There is no such thing.
Kazuki, are you going to
become a pro doujinshi artist?
Oh, no, that's not what I meant.
Our goal is world conquest, right?
But I was just thinking that at this rate,
we wouldn't even be
able to conquer Arakawa.
Oh, I almost forgot!
I'm out of paper for my manuscript.
Kazuki...
Are you busy this afternoon?
No, not really.
If you don't mind, might
I take up a little bit of your time?
"Yoyomori Central College"
"Club Meeting Hall"
Mizuki!
Perfect timing!
Hey Mizuki, do you
have any plans for today?
Nothing in particular...
Great, then it's decided!
Huh? What's decided?
Haga, wait a minute!
"Sunrise Café"
So the two of you know each other.
Yeah, we've worked together
a little on a joint project before.
Actually, I'm surprised that
an editor like you knows Aya.
Today was the first time I met her.
The first time?
Yes, at the last Comipa,
I happened to take a look at her manga,
and had Minami introduce me to her.
So then, are you going to
give Aya a job at your magazine?
That's what I plan to do.
Actually, Hasebe,
I'd invited Sendo once before.
Kazuki too?
What do you think, Sendo?
Would you like to
reconsider it one more time?
Well, I...
Excuse me, Ms. Sawada.
It's probably audacious
of me to ask you this
even though I haven't
given you an answer yet, but still...
What is it?
Might I watch you and the others at work?
You want to watch us at work?
What about you, Kazuki?
Me too?
Well, I guess I could take a
look at how the professionals work.
Then it's decided.
Nice idea. That might be good too.
But don't get disappointed, okay?
Huh?
"Monthly Gang" "Kadoyama Shoten"
Excuse me, but are you closed today?
Why do you ask that?
Oh, because no one's here?
Of course we're open.
It's just a little early
for people to be at work yet.
Early? But it's past 1:00!
Didn't you know?
In most places, the higher
ups can come and go late.
But with magazine
editors, it's the opposite.
What do you mean by that?
The executives are
the ones who come in early,
and most of the regular editors
don't come in until nightfall or later.
Hi, Ms. Sawada.
You're here really early as usual.
Oh, Cho.
Mizuki!
Huh? Kazuki!
Hasebe!
Are you plotting something again?
Oh, you mean these two?
They asked to observe us at work.
It looks like that's the
case with those two as well.
See you again later, Sir.
Who was that man we just met?
The associate editor of the anime magazine.
Although, I guess he might
as well be called the "chief."
He's the type who comes
up with unusual schemes.
Your friends must be surprised.
They're probably wondering if
editing really is such an impersonal job.
And then the abandoned
cat transforms into a dragon.
It looks like there's a story meeting going
on in the conference room right now.
So, would you like to take a look?
Oh, sure.
Could we come in?
No problem!
It really is too convenient.
Convenient?!
What's so bad about that?
Listen! If we are to win the
hearts and minds of the people,
we cannot do it with dull logic!
We need the arrogance of God!
Don't forget. In any
creative work, the author is God!
He is the absolute Creator!
Nonsense? Nothing wrong with that!
Convenient? Let me say it!
Anyway, when the hero sees
that the dragon can't step over fish,
he'll see right through to its true identity!
Well?
Doesn't it bring a tear to your eye?
He kind of reminds me of Taishi.
Yes, he does.
By any chance, was
that meeting about Ostwind?
Oh, do you read our magazine, Sendo?
Of course.
Yes, it was a meeting about the next story.
But I thought the
author Mr. Ueda was younger.
Ueda is still young.
What? But that guy was...
Sendo...
Did you think that the man who
reminded you of Kuhonbutsu was Ueda?
He wasn't?
That was an editor, Kono.
The one taking notes was Ueda.
Really?
Surprised?
But there are more cases than you think
where the manga's basic story
is thought up by the editing staff.
It's a particularly big trend
in major magazine companies which
are busy putting out large circulations.
But I'm against it.
That's because, though it
might reduce the risk of a title,
all manga artists have a
glimmer, like a rough gemstone,
and doing that would probably snuff it out.
A glimmer like a rough gemstone?
Yes...
That's why I want to respect
the manga artists' freedom
of expression as much as possible.
Now that you're going to
be meeting the illustrators,
do you know what the
most important qualification is?
Is it knowledge of art?
No, you're wrong.
It's having a tough, thick skin
capable of tolerating any amount of filth.
Are illustrators really that filthy?
I guess you could call
the level of filth "grand."
Do the two of you know
how often they clean their toilets?
About once a month?
Nope.
Not for as long as they live there.
You mean, they don't even clean it once?
It's terrible.
Not only does the place turn yellow,
years and years of it lump
together and turn into one single layer.
This is it.
Kacchan, it's me.
Mr. Cho?
What are you doing here at a time like this?
What do you mean what am
I doing here? It's the deadline.
I called you yesterday.
Huh? You did?
What are you playing dumb for? Anyway...
W... W... W... W... W... Wait, Mr. Cho!
Who are those two standing behind you?
"Katahira"
Oh, these two?
They're part-timers.
Part-timers?! Wait just
a minute, I'll be right out!
Hi.
They're beautiful.
They're going to be
working for us next year.
As part of their on the job training,
I thought I'd bring them
with me to collect the illustrations.
Bringing them to collect illustrations?
Well, they have school too,
so they can only
come for two or three days.
So... Well?
When do you think you'll be finished?
What are you saying, Mr. Cho?
The deadline is tomorrow, isn't it?
He did just say the
deadline is today, didn't he?
Relax!
I, the humble Beckham
of the deadline world,
shall overcome all
obstacles to finish by tomorrow.
Then I'll call you tomorrow.
Say, about that
conversation you just had...
Oh, sorry about that.
I took the liberty of using
you as the ultimate weapon.
Ultimate weapon?
The strongest weapon.
I don't know why,
but whenever we send a
young girl as a messenger to him,
he finishes his illustrations faster.
Oh, I see.
Then if I cosplay, maybe
he'll finish at super high speed!
Good idea.
But Haga, you didn't bring
anything with you today, right?
He took it seriously.
Comic Party Revolution
"Kadoyama Shoten"
"First Pressing Extra: Asahi Sakurai Figure!!!"
"Asahi Sakurai New Single Release!"
Huh?
--Yay!
--You did it!
"Kadoyama Shoten"
Comic Z Editorial Department...
Oh, hello Mr. Iwaya.
Huh? Your assistant?
It looks like I won't be
able to get my usual guy at all!
Don't you know any other assistants?
This is a really bad time.
Comipa is coming up soon,
so they're all holed up
making their own doujinshi!
He missed the issue before last,
so he has to get this
one in no matter what!
Well, he needs an assistant?
Yes, he's an old-fashioned guy,
so he still has the concentrated
linework drawn with a pen,
and he has problems getting assistants.
Well, Ms. Sawada, if he
doesn't mind, why don't I help?
Huh? Are you sure about that, Sendo?
I'll be okay helping for one night.
That would be a big help!
Excuse me, I'd like to too.
Hasebe!
Okay then, please do.
Hello? I've arranged for assistants here.
--Yes!
--I'll send them over to you.
Bye!
I'll get a map and a taxi ticket for you.
Excuse me, where are we going now?
In Shinjuku, there are two
booby traps for otaku writers.
One of them is the lounge
Takezawa. The second is...
Come in!
Sorry, just walk around the
mess somehow and come on in.
Th... Thanks for coming all the
way out to a garbage dump like this!
I'll go make some tea.
"Hobby Store"
I'd like you to draw the concentrated
linework on the parts I've marked.
Do you understand?
I think I'll be fine.
Excuse me, what should I do?
Please cheer for me in your heart.
Huh?
We've been walking around and
around to the same places for a while.
Are you looking for something?
I guess you could say
I'm looking for something.
Huh?
Today is the release
date for the Super Real Series.
Speak of the Devil...
If you're in a place like this shopping,
I suppose that means you've finished
your manuscript, right, Mr. Yamaguchi?
Mr. Cho!
Writers may try to run away,
but somehow I get the feeling
we'll be able to root them up today.
You said you draw doujinshi?
Yes, well...
I see. Then you must be busy right now,
with your manuscript for
the Summer Comipa, right?
You know about Comipa?
Of course!
I used to do doujinshi a lot too.
Doujinshi, huh?
Everything about it brings back memories.
What do you have that
distant look in your eyes for?
It's only been two or three years, right?
But back then, I was
just happy drawing manga.
I remember staying up all night
talking about each other's
manga before the print deadline.
Yeah, yeah. There was a group of people
who only saw each other at times like that,
in the second floor of the printing shop.
Hi!
Now that you mention it,
where is the editor?
You mean Mr. Iwaya?
He's at the printing shop.
The printing shop?
The truth is, this should've
been sent to the printer today,
but it looks like that's not going to
happen, so he's talking it over with them.
And whose fault is that?
But to tell the truth,
the Comic Z editors are good.
They must have been
taught well by the Editor in Chief.
Are there editors out
there who aren't very good?
Most of the editors at
major publishers are like that.
They're turning into businessmen.
Yeah, Mr. Cho said that editors
have been really amateurish lately,
and even people who draw doujinshi
know more about the basics of editing.
Mr. Cho? You mean the editor from
the anime magazine next to Comic Z?
You know him?
I met him today.
I heard that guy is something else.
They said he only goes
home about twice a month.
He does?
"Takezawa"
If you allow us to have an
exclusive on the movie announcement,
we'll think about giving you the cover.
How are you doing? Making progress?
Yes, they've been a big help.
Good!
I figured you probably
haven't had dinner yet,
so I brought some refreshments.
Oh! That's the elusive
yakiniku boxed lunch!
You've used up the production
budget for the new opening?
Fine, I'll make some excuse to
accounting and work it out somehow.
In exchange, I want you to jump
the gun on the next issue, okay?
That was an anime studio that
operates on a super-tight budget.
Say, you said "new opening"...
Do you mean they get the production
budget for it from the magazine?
Yes, it's their payment for
letting us use their illustrations.
Oh yeah, the sample copy arrived
from the printer, so I brought it with me.
"A Maiden's Vase"
So what do you think
about holding a book you made?
Well, you see...
To us, a book that's just been
finished is like a newborn baby.
I can't help getting excited
when I open it up for the first time.
A newborn baby?
It's the same...
They feel the same way as the people
who take a doujinshi that we just finished.
Huh?
Aya...
"Kadoyama Shoten"
What's going on, Sir?
Oh, perfect timing.
I just got a call from the printer.
They found a spot we forgot
to correct in the finished proofs.
In the finished proofs?
So, can we make it in time?
They're stopping the
printing for only one hour.
If you hurry up and get cracking,
you might make it just in time.
One hour, huh?
Then I have to hurry.
Aya, you set this up
today for me, didn't you?
Huh?
You asked the Editor in Chief...
Yes!
You didn't seem like
your usual self yesterday.
And it made me think, maybe you were
losing sight of your goal to draw doujinshi.
I felt the same way once before.
I see...
A train is now arriving on Track 1.
For your safety, please
stay behind the white line.
"Book Binding and Printing"
Is it always this tough?
I guess so.
500 yen per book...
To us, that's not much money,
but to the customers who buy
the books, it's no small change.
When I think about that,
I just can't do slipshod work.
Oh, it came from the author already!
Huh? Then we have to
go collect the illustrations.
That's okay, I'll go.
But...
Instead, could I ask you to
do the same again next month?
"Comic Z"
Thanks for all the help.
It looks like we're going to
make the deadline just in time.
Say, about what we
were talking about yesterday...
Hm?
You said you wanted to run
my manga in your magazine...
Yes.
Well, how about it?
I'm going to draw doujinshi after all.
You don't like the idea of becoming
a professional manga artist?
No, that's not it.
It's just... There's still
more I want to do with doujinshi.
Plus, you can find friends who have
the same spirit for doujinshi as you.
Am I wrong?
It looks like I don't even have
to ask Hasebe what her answer is.
Right.
Too bad...
Well, that's what I feel like I should say,
but I think I'm just a little
glad it turned out this way.
Oh, perfect timing.
We were just about to eat breakfast.
Why don't we eat together?
You were up all night, weren't you?
You too, Kazuki.
But you seem pretty cheerful.
Really? I don't know...
All right!
Taishi!
Good morning, My Brother.
All right!
What?
Let's do it! It's time for world conquest!
Y... Y... Yeah!
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
--Congratulations, Kazuki!
- -I heard! You're being placed along the wall!
--Subaru's going to catch up to Kazuki too!
Subaru's going to catch up to Kazuki too!
Please continue to do
business with Tsukamoto Printing!
Good luck.
I'll be cheering you
on from beneath the sod.
Draw what you want to!
That's what doujin's all about!
It doesn't mean anything if it doesn't sell!
What in the world should I do?!
My Comrade, just for today,
we'll do a pornographic story...
You be quiet.
Next time: "As Time Goes By."
Kazuki's art is so
gentle and warm. I love it!