Are we even popular?
Plus our merch is cute.
It's your fault for giving us
a weird name.
Is it?
We have Toge-Toge rubber bands!
How about a Toge-Toge towel?
I think it's selling better than
when we were Shinkawasaki.
Really?
Don't worry, the Polaroids
are still a hit.
Ready?
Hug!
I'll never bathe again!
Gross! Start by cleaning that brain!
True.
Not interested.
Excuse me.
This is my card.
GOLDEN ARCHER
MIURA
Golden Archer?
-Yes.
-That sounds familiar.
Oh! The talent agency!
Yes!
This unfinished beat covers the night
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
Embracing us before we're crushed
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
There will be change
If you just reach out
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
In a world where nothing changes
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
We have to live through it
kyou datte ikite yukunda
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
We've already started walking
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
uso mitaina baka mitaina
This hopeless city of ours
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
But I still saw it with my own eyes
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Embracing us before we're crushed
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
There will be change
If you just reach out
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
WANDERVOGEL
Are you scouting us?
Yes, that's my intention.
I see.
If you have doubts, please search online
for our company and my name Miura.
-What are they like?
-Pretty famous.
I have classmates who want to join them,
and they have a few bands signed.
But aren't talent agencies...
I'm actually a fan of Diamond Dust!
But I don't like the current Diamond Dust!
They've lost what made
the original band so good.
I love your music, Momoka!
I want you to actualize
the kind of music you originally pursued.
And this band can do that!
Right?!
Sit down.
Sorry.
When D-D wanted to go mainstream,
I was told that my songs won't work
and that they didn't match the trend.
Yes.
I don't think they were wrong about that.
And the fans followed D-D
when they adopted their new sound.
But these four here
still want to go up against them.
They want to give it a shot
with the music I want to write.
And I'm planning on doing just that.
Right?
Momoka...
Okay.
What?
You're entering
the upcoming music festival, yes?
"Leave your mark at the festival," huh?
If we stand out there, it'll be easier
for the agency to get labels on board.
GOLDEN ARCHER
MIURA
And if we have a lot of fans,
we won't need to change our music style.
So the festival is like
our final audition.
-Nina.
-Yes?
Would you mind
writing lyrics for that song?
What?
I want to see the song my music inspired.
Okay.
That makes no sense.
What are you saying?
Sounds fine to me.
They seem to understand each other.
Did you finish the lyrics?
Nope.
Didn't you say you had something
you wanted to write about?
I did.
Then just write that.
You don't get it...
What?
Words are outside.
Once you put it into words,
what you had inside gets out
and takes shape.
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Do you know how many songs I've written?
Ow...
I get what you're saying though.
Come on, break's over.
Already?
What?
Nothing.
Hello--
What is it?
Why? How?
What are--
Hello.
Excuse me.
I believe you have a girl named
Iseri working here part-time.
She's not on schedule today.
I see.
Are you looking for her?
You must be Rupa.
-MOM'S HERE!
-YEAH...
Tell me sooner if you knew!
Da--
Nina?
So that's why you came here?
It's so relaxing here.
You don't even know why they're here.
Shouldn't you talk to them?
Are you listening?
Mm...
Nina?
We can't understand each other.
What?
It's the same with your grandma.
We have different values.
All they say is nonsense.
But still...
Besides, I need to write lyrics.
We don't have much time
before the festival.
Everyone's future is on the line.
I don't have time to deal with this.
Sounds to me like you're running away.
Do you want to stay over tonight?
NEXT MORNING
Hello?
Stop calling.
You're the one who ran away.
It wasn't like that.
They keep calling me
asking where you might be.
Have you told to them?
TO: MUNEO ISERI
FROM: NINA ISERI
It's because you sent a letter like this.
Of course they wouldn't leave you alone.
Why?
Did you think they'd just accept it?
If you have something to say,
stop running and tell it to their face.
Nina?
She hung up.
Huh?
They changed the locks?
I'm the one who lives there!
Give me the new key!
What is wrong with everyone?!
Shut up!
But!
Here you go!
I took you off the schedule.
It's a present from me and Tomo.
TOKYO TO KUMAMOTO
Why?
I think Tomo might have mentioned it,
but I was supposed to
call my family that day.
My shift went long,
so I figured I'd call them
the next day or some other time.
But that was the last time.
You have less time
and opportunities than you think.
Sorry, I know it's annoying
to just talk about myself.
Do they really care?
They used to just ignore me.
Don't add sound effects.
I see.
So this was your weakness.
It's not a weakness or anything.
Then go do it already.
Not you too!
Well, it seems like
you're misunderstanding.
What?!
The thing you can't let go
isn't your exams or the bullying.
It's that your dad didn't take your side.
That's not...
If it's not true, then go meet them.
I will then.
Then go.
You're not welcome back here until you do.
Bye then.
I actually came.
The train bound towards
Suizenji and Hikarinomori will be...
TATSUTAGUCHI STATION
Okay!
Ready, and...
Ow!
Geez...
Nina.
We've been looking for you.
Girls Band Cry.
FAMILY PRECEPTS
A band?
Yeah.
And you want to make a living from it?
Seems like it.
She's already been approached
by a talent agency.
She's like one step from going pro.
Not sure if it's true though.
-That's all true.
-But...
You left home to study for college,
and you did all this without
telling any of us?
I did hear about it a little bit.
Do you know how hurt your mother is?
This again.
Mom's got nothing to do with this.
When I left home, you told me
to do what I wanted, Dad.
And I told you I would.
No.
I told you to get into college.
How much do you think
we've let you get away with?
You wanted to drop out of school,
so we did the paperwork.
You wanted to go to Tokyo,
so we arranged it.
Stop making things up.
I did everything myself!
Dropping out and going to Tokyo!
You only got that apartment
with your mother's introduction.
Whose name is listed as your guarantor?
You're still a minor.
Do you know what that means?
It means you have an adult
looking after you.
So I should do as you say?
Just act like I wasn't bullied?
Nina.
I can't do this after all.
I came here to try to talk to you properly
and get you to understand my side.
But this is how it starts.
I just can't.
I want you to come with me
somewhere tomorrow.
Hey.
Where are we going?
You'll find out soon enough.
I'm not going.
I'm not going back to that school.
I've already spoken to them.
I have something to say, just like you do.
Thank you for coming in this hot weather.
LETTER OF APOLOGY
It's nothing.
What is this?
It must have been hot for you too.
-So...
-Yes.
We followed up and the other student
admitted the truth.
I want to apologize on behalf of
the school for our lack of awareness.
Is that all? Are you saying
the school wasn't responsible?
That is not the case.
However, the school
doesn't recognize it as bullying.
I know it's not my place to say this,
but I think the school
was aware of the truth--
Don't.
But...
I said stop already.
You don't need to say that.
You're the victim.
Momoka, it's about Nina.
What if she doesn't come back
from Kumamoto?
It'll work out.
Tomo!
Are you okay?
It'll be okay.
Let's believe in her.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
Will you have dinner?
-You're going back?
-Yeah.
So you're really doing the band?
Yeah.
You love it that much?
That song...
gave me the push I needed.
I was told the smart thing to do
was to hold it in.
APOLOGY ESSAY
So I thought that I didn't have
any other choice.
That song pushed me forward.
If I wasn't wrong,
then I don't need to hold it in.
I should stop thinking ahead
and just take a leap.
Now, I didn't know
if that led down to hell
or up towards the sky,
but that song made me fly.
So there's no ground to return to,
not that I want to go back.
Back then,
I was trying to
suppress the person I was.
I might not even have wings,
and I might just be imagining
that I'm flying,
but I love who I am now the most.
I can proudly say that.
This is the real me.
I understand.
But be sure to eat before you go.
Okay.
Here. Spicy lotus root curry.
It's been a while, right?
-Shouldn't we go down?
-What?
Our family precepts.
Oh. It's fine.
It's been weird since you left.
Dad even had some beer the other day
even though he's not a drinker.
He got so drunk.
"What do you think I should do?"
-What?
-Can you believe it?
He's worried about you.
And despite being
a rather well-known educator,
he went around and asked for advice.
And your round-trip train ticket,
Mom secretly asked your friends
to give it to you.
You didn't realize, huh?
You're loved, you know?
Despite how they act,
our parents love you.
Don't forget that.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for being alive.
I love you, too, Nina.
It's so spicy.
Was Mom's curry always this spicy?
NINA 10 YEARS OLD
SUZUNE 9 YEARS OLD
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
Whether my fingers tremble or not
You like this song?
There's no right answer
There's no losing
Yeah.
I see.
I've been me all my life
That's all there is
You don't like it?
Of course you don't.
No matter how much I fight
There's no tomorrow
It's a good song.
Dad.
I'm sorry for being such a selfish
daughter who doesn't listen to you.
Try to cut down on the smoking.
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Nina!
Wait.
What?
Is there something else?
Have a safe trip.
Yeah.
Nina!
Your apartment key!
Key?
Why?
It's from Dad.
Dad!
I'm going to sing a song I wrote
at our next show.
Please come hear it.
Okay.
Yes!
Nina.
I'm off then!
Thanks for cutting the branch!
Take care!
They're nosy, noisy, and irritating.
But I love them.
Bye, I'll see you again.
Thank you for riding with us.
Passengers changing to
the Chuo Line, Yamanote Line...
Keihin-Tohoku Line, Tokaido Line,
Joban Line, Sobu Line, Keio Line,
EMPTINESS AND CATHARSIS
Miss? Miss!
Yes!
or the Tohoku, Hokuriku, and Joetsu
Shinkansen Lines. Please transfer here.
Oh! You again!
Did you sleep well?
Yes!
I'm back.
Nina.
Where's our souvenir?
No way.
How?
Momoka was so sure that you'd come back.
If you didn't come back today,
she was going to drive us all to Kumamoto.
She said she'd even drive us herself.
Rupa was about to be our hero.
You were all for it too!
Wait, she's crying.
Does that count as crying?
What? She's not crying.
What do you think, Rupa?
Hmm, maybe.
Thanks, you guys.
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Did you get it done?
Yes, I wrote a great song!
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
dareka ni somarenai dare ni mo narenai
I laughed, thinking it a dream
yume da to omotte waratte miseta
wasureta yowasa kajikande iku
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
samishii nante ieru wake mo nai
I can't even say that I'm lonely
sarigenai kaiwa sura kizutsuku kokoro wa
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
dare hitori dare hitori shiawase ni shinai
Is incapable of making anyone happy
nee sore demo mada kitai fukuramunda
But still, I feel a growing hope
surechigatta uso nante zenbu sutete
Moving past all of the lies
daisoretenai yo tte tada kikitakute
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
yume bakari de osanakutatte
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
kyou mo kawarenai mama datte iinda
I don't care if I'm still the same today
kimi to utatte itai
I just want to sing with you
nando datte kanjou bakka yure ugoite
My emotions stir so often
kirawarete kita kedo
I've been hated
kono mama de aruite yukunda
But I'm going to keep walking
darenimo narenai watashi mune hatte sa
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
tada hitori demo
Even if I'm alone
magiremonai jibun wo shinjite
I believe in myself
kizutsuki ochiru tabi utaeba ii
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next episode, "The Center of the World"