All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"The Greatest Bloodbath in History"
"Mountain Campground"
"Figures, Manuscript,
Video Games, Baseball, Passion"
"Common practice at a
secret training camp!! (A lie)"
- "You are here" "Final frontier!!
- - Convenience Store"
"3 Hours"
"Mountain Campground"
"Forest of Wandering"
"Out of Area"
"Corpse"
"Taishi Team Corpse Storage Site"
"Pro Team Corpse Storage Site"
"Cosplay Barrier"
"Human Dumptruck"
"Checkerboard Pattern"
"Stealth Aya"
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
"Next Comic Party"
"Let's Start by Being Friends"