All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"Fierce Battle! Cosplay Fight!"
How cute!
Peach, look over here!
Sure!
Do a different pose!
Uh, okay. Like this?
Over here too!
Takase sure is popular, isn't she?
She's really getting into it too!
Card Master Peach is
already popular enough.
The one cosplaying her has good skills,
and not only that, she has a cute,
embarrassed expression on her face.
You don't even have to be a
man to feel "it" coming from her!
Hey, why don't we do something
together as a group next time?
Sounds great! Like
Pretty Soldier <censored>
--Yeah, let's do a group of five!
--or Imperial Floral Combat Troop <censored>...
My darling Shou!
Darling Gawin! Commander!
Reiko, you're drooling.
You really like them, don't you?
What do you want to do, Miho?
Miho?
Huh? What?
Weren't you listening?
Sorry.
We're talking about
getting together with Takase
and cosplaying as a
five-person group at the next event.
Huh?
Dressing as a character you like is great,
but cosplaying as a group
is just so exciting, you know?
And it's fun making the costumes too.
I have to teach Mizuki
a lot more different things.
Yeah...
What do you think you're doing?
You snuck a naughty picture of me!
What?!
Snuck naughty pictures?
It's a misunderstanding!
We are very decent otaku!
--I swear, we would never sneak a...
--Then what's this?
Argh! That's...
--Those aren't things a young lady should see!
--Found it!
--Wrong.
--Those aren't things a young lady should see!
Found it!
No!
There's some sort of mistake.
Why you...
This must be a plot by
someone to demean us!
Yeah, uh huh...
Don't make up such obvious lies!
Peach sees through it all!
Super attack! Peach Home Run!
Yeah! That's our Peach!
Peach, you're the greatest!
--Amazing!
--Peach! Peach! Peach!
--So cool!
Wow, if she can perfectly
copy the character's killer move,
she's already a full-fledged cosplayer!
Incredible, she's already
mastered the technique
that was broadcast just last week.
Nicely done, Comrade Mizuki.
Are you sure that was right?
Man, Mizuki's late.
It's already closed!
Good work.
Oh, Minami, good work.
Huh? Where's Mizuki?
She hasn't come back yet.
Do you need something?
In that case, could I ask
you to give this to her for me?
Sure.
This is...
"Exhibition Hall Station"
Now that I think about it,
otaku are filthy and creepy.
I hate otaku!
Cosplay Fight?
Yeah! A cosplay contest organized
by the Comipa Preparation Committee.
Cosplay Fight International Treaty?
"You must be a cosplayer,
cosmetic surgery is forbidden,
and it's best if the
costume is entirely self-made."
Wow, sounds interesting.
Do you want to try entering together?
Reiko, this is your chance.
Huh?
This is the once in a
lifetime chance heaven
has sent you to battle it
out with that Mizuki Takase!
Huh?
Comrade Reiko!
Do you have a heart within
your chest that burns with passion?
I... I guess so...
Do you have a heart within your chest
that is made of steel
and will not lose to anyone?
Possibly...
Does a tremendous
ambition rest within your chest?
That, I don't think so...
Then that's good.
What is?
Reiko, as the one whose destiny
is to control the world with cosplay,
you of all people should
understand what this contest means.
Comipa is the largest
doujinshi event in the country.
And if this is being organized
by Comipa's preparation committee...
That makes it the largest
cosplay event in the country!
If you win this contest,
it will prove you are the
strongest cosplayer in the country!
It's not that big of a deal.
But we're not cosplaying
to win against someone.
I'm happy.
I'm happy when I see Reiko
surrounded by people with cameras.
I'm happy when I make crowds.
And so yesterday's Comipa was a disgrace!
Mizuki Takase is a frightening cosplayer.
I can't believe she perfectly copied
the killer move in such a short time!
Comrade Reiko!
This is your calling, your destiny!
She is blocking our path to world conquest!
Now, prepare yourself, Reiko Haga!
No, Cosplayko!
Don't call me Cosplayko.
That rattled my brains!
No, more importantly,
I know you already know this!
You can't avoid your fight with her...
I know what you're trying to
say, Miho. But I agree with Mayu.
Besides, I cosplay because it's fun.
And I want to keep doing that.
Ah, sorry, I have to get to my job.
Oh, that contest sounds like
fun, so let's all enter it together!
Reiko...
No matter how much you refuse,
you can't avoid the fight with Mizuki.
And you have to win.
That is your fate!
"Cosplay Fight"
What are you so mad for, Mizuki?
I won't know unless
you tell me. Come on...
Good evening, my comrades!
Is your blood boiling with anticipation
of the upcoming Cosplay Fight?
What's the matter, my sister?
You are the one who is
going to be crowned the winner!
So lift up your face,
--You're really not going to enter Cosplay Fight?
--and stand tall, future cosplay queen!
Not entering?
Are you insane, Comrade Mizuki?
This is your chance to be the strongest
cosplayer in the country, no, the world!
In order for us, Brother 2,
to conquer the world with doujinshi,
it is absolutely imperative
that we have your ability
--to control crowds
with cosplay, my sister!
--What in the world happened?
--to control crowds with cosplay, my sister!
Right! What happened, Comrade Mizuki?
--You should say something too, my brother!
--...remembered.
I remembered.
Otaku are filthy, they
use jargon I can't understand,
and they're a bunch of social
misfits who plot to overthrow Japan!
But even you liked cosplay, didn't you?
You need to open your eyes too!
Come on, let's go back to
our respectable lives together!
Mizuki...
I heard the whole thing.
You too, Miho?
It seems like I've
overestimated you, Takase.
You're going to quit just because
some guys snuck naughty
pictures of you one time?
There's no way Reiko could lose
to someone with that kind of attitude.
If you don't like it, then you can quit.
But I cannot allow you
to make Sendo quit too.
This has nothing to do with you!
Yes, it does.
If you leave, then we will
become the sellers for Sendo's circle.
Huh?
What did you say?
Hmm...
It's not a bad deal, is it?
Brother 2 will get four exclusive cosplayers.
There must be something in
it for you too. What are you after?
A boys love book drawn by Kazuki Sendo!
Of course, it will be about a group of five!
Boys love?! I won't draw that!
Very well.
It's not a bad deal.
Hey, Taishi, what are you...
Hold it, you can't just decide that!
You've quit being involved with
doujinshi, so it has nothing to do with you.
This is between Team Ikkatsu and Brother 2.
Right, Sendo?
Uh, well, you see...
Kazuki is going to return
to a normal life with me!
Right, Kazuki?
Uh, I, well...
You indecisive wimp!
You try to please everybody!
My brother...
Your kindness is a virtue, but
taken too far, it will become your ruin.
Very well!
I will become the guide that will lead you!
So now, it's obviously time for...
Cosplay Fight!
How did it end up like this?
Comic Party Revolution!
Comic Party
Revolution!
So, there you have it.
If Mizuki wins, she and Sendo
will quit being involved with doujinshi.
And if I win...
You'll get a boys love
book drawn by Kazuki Sendo.
All right! I'm going for the win!
That's the spirit, Reiko!
Defeat Mizuki Takase!
We're gonna get Kazuki
Sendo's first boys love book!
--Reiko!
--Miho!
Sendo's really, really
going to draw a boys love book!
If I win, I get a boys love book!
Boys love book!
Boys love book! Boys love book!
--Boys love book!
--She surrenders so easily.
--A Kazuki Sendo boys love book!
--She's honest to her desires.
--Boys love book! Boys love book!
--There's only one thing to do!
Momo, from now on you're a
Card Master! You're Card Master Peach!
This is all so sudden!
By the way, do you like your
seasoned eggs in your ramen soft boiled?
Ya need to take this more seriously!
Ummm, all I have to do is transform, right?
Then, umm...
Ramen tanmen tantanmen!
--Reimen nyumen hiyasomen!
--I don't like cosplay anymore.
Coming!
Huh? What's the matter?
We need your help to stop those two.
If you're the hero,
then take responsibility like a hero!
Excuse me!
♪ I can't tell my friends ♪
"Cosplay Fight"
♪ Brought by the gentle breeze ♪
"Cosplay Fight Participant Reception"
♪ I can't hide my cheeks
under a faint pink color ♪
Thank you very much!
That was our guest Asahi Sakurai!
Asahi, please stay
around as a special judge!
Sure!
--And now for the first Cosplay Fight,
--Sendo!
--organized by the Comipa Preparation Committee!
Kazuki Sendo!
Over here!
Cute.
Bravo.
Reiko, don't say anything,
just change into this.
This is... Rena from Psychic High School.
Miho...
Gash is so wonderful.
But that won't be enough for you to win.
So anyway, just
monopolize the guys' attention!
Luckily, it looks like
Mizuki Takase won't even show up,
but we can't be too cautious.
It will be all right!
With your attractiveness, I'm sure...
Don't you want to win?
I do want to win.
Then why are you...
It's because I want to win that I'm
playing Gash, the character I love the most.
If I didn't, this wouldn't mean anything.
Please believe in me!
See ya!
Reiko...
I was so nervous!
So you're going to quit cosplaying?
Uh, well...
I heard it from Miho.
That's, well...
But I guess I'll be a
little sad to see our friend go.
Hey Mizuki,
do you like Peach?
Huh?
Yeah...
That's good.
Then hurry up and change, okay?
Okay everyone,
next is young Gash
from "Fighters Breaker 2."
Operation complete.
I shall make this the
place where you truly die.
Do you like Peach?
Next up is a character
you'll be familiar with as being
voiced by today's guest, Asahi Sakurai:
Card Master Peach!
It's my character!
Hey, Mizuki, what about your costume?
I...
Yes?
I hate otaku!
Say, Mizuki, what's the matter?
If you don't at least cosplay,
it would break the rules.
Hold it right there!
At first glance, those
just look like regular clothes,
but that costume...
That's right!
Those clothes
are the ones Momo was wearing
when she first transformed into Peach!
It couldn't be!
My sister?!
I hate otaku.
And to be honest with you,
I don't understand cosplay much either.
But I like Peach!
Ramen tanmen tantanmen!
Reimen nyumen hiyasomen!
Card Master Peach!
It's getting very hot, so please be careful!
A transformation sequence?
Reiko...
She might reject otaku...
But her love for Peach is the real thing.
In the end,
we're just awkward girls
who can only communicate
with each other through cosplay.
Peach! Peach! Peach! Peach! Peach! Peach!
And finally, the last contestant!
Little Konomi Yuzuhara from "To Heart 2"!
Good morning, Taka!
How cute!
Super cute!
Who is that?
S-S-S...
Splendid!
Hey you two! You can't get on stage!
--Please stop!
--Those are the guys from before!
Stop it right there, you little crooks!
What do you want, huh?
You never learn, do you? Prepare yourselves!
What was that, huh?
What?
We let our guard down the other day.
This time you'll be defeated.
What are you going to do?
The event stage is sacred ground for otaku!
It's an otaku space, brimming with power!
Where is this?
This is the otaku dimension!
Here, we feel three
times better than normal!
Yeah, uh huh.
What was that?! Peach Home Run!
--Flick! Yeah, uh huh.
--Peach!
Get up, Peach!
I...
Peach will not lose!
Release the seal!
This is...
Three times more dangerous than usual.
Level 3, awaken!
Combined ultimate attack!
Peach...
Punisher!
Reiko!
Thank goodness! You did great!
--Reiko!
Don't push yourself so hard!
You don't have to cry.
Hey, you're...
Uh, umm...
Thank you very much.
No!
Jesus!
A... A guy!
Kazuki!
Honestly, what kind of treason
were you guys trying to pull?
We figured that if someone else
won, your fight would be called a draw.
That's no way to make a draw!
It went a little too well, didn't it?
Now, now, it's all good.
Besides, in the end,
Yuka and Mayu did what they
did because they thought of everyone.
Hmph!
And most importantly,
it looks like Sendo has realized
the joys of cosplaying as a girl!
Come on, that was a
misunderstanding, I tell you!
Little Konomi is angry!
How scary!
You're so mean!
You're the ones who roped me into it!
--Good luck, little Konomi!
--Little Konomi...
When I peeked at little Konomi's
panties I thought Kazuki was super cute.
Kazuki's panties... I am him, he is me?
Who am I? Little Konomi?
No, no, no, I am not little Konomi.
Because little Kazuki... Little Kazuki?
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
This is horrible! Chisa's father collapsed!
What will I do?
At this rate, we're going to be seized by the
evil god of bad economy and bill collectors!
I don't want to move out!
I don't want to do a moonlight flight!
It will be all right! Subaru will help you!
Really, big sis Subaru?
Next time:
"Save Tsukamoto Printing!"
And grow the business
while we're at it too!
I'm not so sure about this.