Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Princess of Tennis (tentative)"
"Yoyomori Hospital"
I-Wonder-Where-I-Can-Get-
5,000-Copies-of-My-Next-Issue-Printed
Serve!
The system can only
handle 2,000 copies at once,
but for 5,000 copies
the price would be...
15-Love!
And-of-Course-the-
Cover-Will-be-Full-Color
Serve!
Full color?
Along with the regular colors,
you're going to order
fluorescent colors and leafing?
In that case, the additional
fee would be... well, well...
30-Love!
While-I'm-at-it-I-Might-as-
Well-Include-the-Paper-Too
Serve!
The paper is going to have leafing too?
Big Sister Eimi, thank you so
much for your business as always!
Daiei Ryuu "hidden" ultimate technique!
Justice Return!
You're too soft, Subie!
Tsutenkaku Fall!
40-Love.
So flexibility is stronger
than stiffness, huh?
Subaru Mikage definitely isn't weak, either.
However, she had a bad opponent...
Now then, what are you going to do,
Comrade Mizuki?
Big Sister Mizuki...
Ikumi!
Big Sister Mizuki, what's wrong?
I'm okay. This always happens.
But!
I'm fine, really.
Because I can finally play
tennis with you, Big Sister Mizuki!
Even Ikumi is trying so hard.
I can do it too! I can do it too!
Ikumi, let's do our
best! Let's be sure to win!
Right!
Game set! Match won
by the Ohba-Inagawa pair!
Marvelous!
Excellent!
Nice!
Go easy on me, Mizuki.
Same here, Sakurai!
I don't intend to lose.
I can't lose either!
I've tried so hard...
There's no way I'm going to lose.
"Card Master Peach"
Good work. Thank you very much.
Game set!
Match won by the Takase-Tachikawa pair!
Even I, who has the power of being
Asahi Fan Club member number one...
Even I couldn't make her win?
I can't believe it.
Good game, Sakurai.
Mizuki...
How could I lose? I tried so hard.
How?
Let's play again some time.
A major leaguer training brace?
I can't believe she played a
match wearing something like that.
So, you've gotten this powerful?
To think that you've left
my expectations in the dust...
Truly frightening, Mizuki Takase.
Heh, heh, heh, indeed.
Uh-huh...
I-Don't-Know-Who-is-Who
Serve!
Yuka, it's yours!
Mayu, get it!
Miho, I'm counting on you!
15-Love.
It's-the-Same-Picture-in-
Both-Summer-and-Winter
Serve!
Yuka, volley it!
Mayu, I'm sure you can reach it!
Miho, get it!
30-Love.
Even-Though-There's-No-
Singles-Event-You'd-Better-Back-Off
Serve!
Yuka, return it!
Mayu, I believe in you!
Miho, you can make it on time!
40-Love.
--Umm-Umm-Yay-Yay-Kagoshima-Musume
--That should be Kashimashi Musume.
Serve!
Yuka, I choose you!
Mayu, one million volts!
Pika!
Game set! Match won
by the Ohba-Inagawa pair!
They won in the face of a 2 to 3 handicap.
You are the only one who
can stop these two after all.
Aren't they treating us a little rough?
To a small, weak yaoi circle,
the world is a harsh place.
We're just extras anyway.
Man, they didn't put
up any resistance at all!
Well, it was only natural we'd win anyway.
We're in a whole different
brass! Yup, different brass!
That's "class", you moron.
Well anyway, if all goes
well, we'll be playin' Mizuki next.
We'll finally be able to play an
opponent with some backbone!
"Takase"
"Yoyomori Hospital"
She said it's just an exam, but...
I wonder if Ikumi will be all right?
Ikumi's big brother...
I'm begging you, please
withdraw from the next game!
What are you saying?
Ikumi can only exercise
for 30 minutes a day.
And I'm afraid the next game won't
end before those 30 minutes are up!
Oh, no...
She's the kind of person who
hangs on no matter how tough it gets.
So please!
You're the only one who can stop Ikumi!
Oh no... What should I do?
Ikumi!
Ikumi! What about your condition?!
Big Sister Mizuki...
Ikumi!
Ikumi! Ikumi!
There are...
There are very few things that I can enjoy.
But one of them is the tennis court
I can see from the hospital window.
Kazuki...
And the person who
was always with him...
At first, she was just a mob
character who attracted my attention
--just because she was close to Kazuki.
--I won!
But...
Big Sister Mizuki taught me tennis.
She made a tiny little
dream of mine come true.
So, I...
Big Sister Mizuki, I want to play tennis.
Ikumi...
Ikumi?
Let's go.
To our court!
Right!
Ikumi!
It sure is quiet today.
Ow!
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Who in the world would do this?
Big Sister Mizuki, it's time to go.
Right, okay.
Let's go.
Right!
Comic Party Revolution!
Comic Party
Revolution!
30-Love!
Big Sister...
40-Love!
Time out!
Mizuki, are you going to withdraw?
I'll be fine.
Don't be so full of yourself.
They're too good for you
to win against in that condition.
Don't tell anyone. I can't give up now.
Very well.
Is Mizuki hurt?
So, you noticed.
Of course! But I wonder what happened?
Miss Ohba, the strategy was a success.
Hmm?
That ponytail girl isn't up to
even half of her usual ability.
Hey, what did you guys do?
Must you even ask?
In order to ensure that Eimi
Ohba is the winner of this battle...
We have thwarted your strongest enemy.
Why did you do something like that?
There is no need to thank us.
We'd just like you to give us
priority in buying your next issue.
What have you guys done?!
It's all for "Cat or Fish."
Not only that, I got a
picture of Asahi! I'm so lucky!
I preserved the moment in a movie.
--Oh, so that's what happened.
--We're lucky, lucky, lucky!
--Gulp!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
That's no fair!
Foul play is wrong!
You shouldn't take
pictures without permission!
No fair.
No way!
Are you serious?
I can't believe it!
Eimi Ohba!
To think that you used your fans
as pawns in order to gain victory...
What a foolish move!
Wait! They did it on their own! I didn't...
Eimi, they're your fans, so you should
be sure to keep proper control of them!
Like I said, they did this on their own!
How many times do I have to tell you?
What did we even do in the first place?
That's right.
We didn't put thumbtacks
and stuff in her shoes or anything.
Moron! Stop provoking Maki!
You should have just
come clean and apologized.
Difficult children make Big
Sister just a little bit angry, you know?
Maki has opened her eyes?!
She's the person closest to God!
Joint responsibility!
Nooooo!
"Banned from selling"
I'm in distress...
Looks like I'll have to take
responsibility for what that moron did.
We withdraw.
Understood.
However...
We'll be fine.
Please continue the game.
Very well!
Let's get back to the game!
Understood.
Fine.
Even against a rabbit,
a lion will bring the
prey down with full force.
Even if you are wounded,
we will not go easy on you!
I was so close!
Don't give up.
The moment you give up, the game is over.
Coach!
Remember all of the
special training you went through.
Takase, now is the
time to take off the brace!
I'm not gonna lose!
40-15!
Impossible!
I can't believe even I couldn't return it!
The game's just getting started!
Big Sister Mizuki is amazing...
I... I really do...
Game set!
Match won by the Takase-Tachikawa pair!
We did it!
That was a good game, wasn't it?
Well done, Takase!
You did it! Mizuki!
The Ohba-Inagawa pair withdrew.
Which means you win,
Mizuki Takase and Ikumi Tachikawa.
Is there something wrong?
There's still one last game left.
Isn't that right, Ikumi?
Yes, Big Sister Mizu... I mean, Mizuki.
What?!
I can't fight!
Don't be so soft!
But!
Then I'll do it instead!
Chiharu, run!
Why do those two...
Have to fight each other?
The main heroine and the hidden heroine...
It was destined to
come to this at some point.
Hold it! The real heroine is me,
Queen Eimi Ohba the Great!
Yeah, yeah, could you
please quiet down a little?
I'll get angry again.
A girl vs. girl showdown! Exciting, huh?
It was a pain in the butt.
Seeing your set-up,
and all the events you have...
I was so jealous of all that,
and I wanted to be like you.
I kept thinking, "If only
Mizuki Takase wasn't around!"
But now I'm thankful.
Interesting... We were
both thinking the same thing.
I was jealous of you too.
Just once, I wanted to be a sickly
heroine who makes the hero worry.
That's not a compliment.
It's not, but...
Now I feel like it was worth it.
Shall we begin?
Yes!
Ramen, tanmen, tantanmen!
Remen, nyumen, hiyasomen!
Card Master Peach is here!
This will be a best of one
game match! Takase serves!
Come on, Kazuki! Let's go!
Don't pull on me like that!
Today we're going to
visit Ikumi in the hospital,
and then you're going
to go shopping with me.
Yeah, yeah...
Who's going to do my homework?
You get what you
deserve, Big Dummy Eimi!
Excuse me, Big Sister Eimi.
About the printing
estimate for your next issue...
I wanted him to come to my concert...
Next time...
I will win.
Hey, what should we play next?
A fighting game!
A shooting game!
A training game!
How about cooking or something like that?
When it comes to making
sweets, I can take you all on!
Counting back from the
deadline for the printer...
Time needed for writing...
Time needed for part-time work...
I guess I'll still have
sufficient credits, huh?
Awright!
How are we going to decide
when Kazuki gets to have a day off?
I won't lose next time, Big Sister Mizuki!
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
What do we have to go all
the way into the mountains for?
What are you saying?
Isn't a training camp right
before summer Comipa inevitable?
But why do we have
to play a survival game?
There's no way we
could stand up against pros!
Why are you being so timid?
We have that plan, don't we?
You don't have any plan, do you?
No!
I can't believe I messed up!
There's a hole in my plan now?
Let's just hope Hasabe's efforts pay off.
Next time: "The Greatest
Bloodbath in History."
Mission complete.