Fui ni anata wa watashi
no te o tsunaide kureta
Hitogomi no naka hagurenai you ni
Sugoku ureshikute
umaku nigirikaesenakute
Koi o shiteru tte kizuita ano hi
Hajimari wa tomodachi
Sono kyoukaisen koete
Futari hashiridasou
Mou osaekirenai nakechau hodo ni
Anata no koto ga daisuki
Nee, uso wa tsukenai
Mou tomenakute ii terechau keredo
Watashi zenbu uketomete
Sou, kore kara mo zutto
"Fumyuun! Take Me to the Beach!"
Are you going anywhere
during summer break?
To the beach with my boyfriend!
What? Seriously?
"Summer Remedial Classes"
"Class 2-B Eimi Ohba"
"Live it up!"
"4 days ~ 39,800; 6 days ~ 79,800"
"The Island Where Summer Never Ends."
Eimi Ohba...
What are you staring at so intensely?
That's...
"Live it up!"
"Better Tours: China"
"4 days ~ 93,800 yen"
"5 days ~ 178,000 yen"
She wants to go to New York?!
Finally...
You're finally moving
forward with your plan, Eimi Ohba?
Taking your first step toward
taking over the entire world?
However! It's not going to be that easy.
Did you actually think
we'd let you get away with it?
"Watch out for Eimi Ohba!!"
The world belongs to us, Brother 2!
I really wanted to go...
to the beach.
Let's see... Next,
I multiply by X squared...
Stare.
Hey, why have you been staring at me?
Is there something on my face?
You want to go to the beach, don't you?
Huh?
Like I said, you want
to go to the beach, right?
Not really.
You want to go!
You want to go to the beach!
What are you talking about?
Like I said!
What?
I'm so busy during the summer.
And I have a part time job too.
And then there's the summer Comipa.
I'd better get to work
and draw my manuscript.
But you still want to go to the beach!
Fine, I want to go to the beach.
Then I guess I have no choice.
If you want to go that badly,
I, the great Eimi, will go with you!
Wow, I'm so happy. I get to go
to the beach with the great Eimi.
That's right! Be grateful!
Oh, but you know...
I'll be fine, but will you be okay?
What about remedial classes?
As... As if I'd ever have to take those!
That's good.
Because I'm not gonna
drag you to the beach
while you have remedial classes to take.
I'm not going to have
a single remedial class!
--Are you sure about that?
--Positive!
What's wrong, kid?
What's with the long face?
Because, because, because...
He finally promised to go to the
beach, but I have remedial classes!
Because of those stupid classes,
my trip to the beach,
my midsummer sun, are all gone!
You really are lacking in the
brains department, aren't you?
What was that?
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what I said.
Can't you understand that much? Hmm?
What was that?! How
dare you make fun of me?!
That pisses me off!
Pisses me off! Pisses me off!
There are plenty of
ways you can go to the beach.
Really?
Maybe...
What's with you?! Tell me! Right now!
Hey kid, is that any way to
ask someone for a favor? Hmm?
You really piss me off, you know that?
Well, it doesn't matter to
me if you go to the beach or not.
Hold it!
Hmm?
Please wait. Please
tell me. I'm begging you.
Then I'll tell you.
All you have to do,
is make sure no one finds out
you have to take remedial classes.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I just have to make sure no one finds out.
Wow, that's super simple!
Oh no!
I heard, Eimi.
So, you have remedial classes.
That means you can
forget about the beach.
Don't come this way. Don't
come this way. Don't come this way.
Subaru didn't see Eimi.
Looks like she didn't notice me.
Ow!
I'm pooped...
Oh no, that's...
What will... What will... What will...
I wonder if I bought a little too much?
Hey, watch where you're going!
Jeez...
What are you doing?
Just hurry up and go!
Signboards are so realistic these days!
Looks like I managed
to trick her somehow.
I'm seeing a lot of people
I know. I need to be careful.
With these on,
it won't matter who I run into!
Not again!
It's okay. There's no
way she'll realize who I am.
What is she looking at?
She looks kind of frozen stiff,
but it's not because of me.
It's okay! Hang in there, me!
Big sis Eimi...
Please overlook this!
Huh? What?
It seems my plan proved to be effective.
What do you think?
Is it not just like I said?
What's she doing?
What was that all about?
They were all acting kind of strange.
Yeah! That looks like
it'd look super good on me!
Thank you very much!
Hurry up and leave! Hurry up
and leave! Hurry up and leave!
Eimi!
Uh, well, just because I'm dressed like
this doesn't mean I just came from school.
Eimi...
Yes?
You shouldn't worry everyone.
It's great that there
are things you want to do,
but you're still a student,
so studying is important too.
She isn't talking about
going to the beach, is she?
Besides, you have a lot of fans,
and I think you're a fine doujinshi author.
But you know, if you always
keep saying selfish things,
I think it will worry Kazuki too.
--I knew it...
--When I was a student...
Well, that was a long time ago, but...
They're definitely harassing you.
Think about the
people you've run into lately.
Remember anything 'bout 'em?
Didn't they all seem like
they're goin' to the beach?
So, looks like you're the only
one not goin' to the beach after all!
They've been makin' a fool outta ya.
I get it.
They were all my enemies.
Now I'm definitely going to make them
take me to the beach, no matter what!
Good luck with that.
What do you mean by that?
You really sure they don't know
about the remedial classes? Hmm?
It's... It's okay. I'm sure.
Probably...
Are you sure?
Couldn't they be leaking the info?
Jeez!
Jeez, why doesn't anyone answer?
If that's how they're going
to be, I'll go see them in person!
You seem cornered, Eimi Ohba.
I shall crush your ambition!
Complete moron...
Destination: Kazuki's apartment!
Bloodthirst?
That was terror...
Huh? Eimi!
My glasses... My glasses...
Big brother is out. He's not here!
Is that true?
So he's at his job...
They're going to the beach!
They're going to the beach, aren't they?!
I knew it!
They're planning on leaving
me behind and going to the beach!
And I've never even been there once!
This is unforgivable!
How dare he leave me behind
and go to the beach with other girls?!
Oh no...
If they see me like this,
they'll know I just came from school.
What's wrong?
Nothing, never mind.
Why do I have to run away?
I'm the one who hasn't
been to the beach even once!
This... This is all because
of those remedial classes!
Because of the teacher who
made me take remedial classes!
Because of that nobody
who gave me remedial classes!
I wonder if they know about
the remedial classes after all?
I want to go to the beach.
Eimi?
What's wrong?
Why are you crying all of a sudden?
Because... Because...
Eimi...
Hold it right there!
Yu!
Panda!
And everyone else!
What in the world is going on here?
My comrade, this was a close call.
Just a little longer and you
would have fallen for Eimi Ohba's trick!
Huh?
Eimi, tell us exactly what you're up to!
What in the world are you talking about?
Don't make me laugh!
Do you still intend to persist
in putting up this charade?
I am already well aware that
you are plotting to conquer the world!
Huh?
That's enough outta you!
What are you doing, Comrade?
Every time you ramble on
with that big mouth of yours,
it only complicates things more!
Does she really look
like the kind who could
cook up some kind
of grand scheme to you?
There's no way she could possibly
think up a way to conquer the world
with this empty head of hers!
What do you think you're
doing, you hot spring panda?!
That's my line, ya big dummy Eimi!
It's because you've been actin'
weird that we got into this mess!
I... I...
All right, how's about comin' clean?
Confess!
Now, now. At a time like this,
you should have some katsudon!
I don't want it.
Then Chisa will take it.
Thanks for the food!
I've got evidence!
These are records of your recent activity.
So, how's about comin' clean?
I...
I was just going to
remedial classes, that's all.
Huh?
Like I said, I was
going to remedial classes!
Remedial classes?
Oh?
Remedial classes, huh?
No, well, uh, uh...
Thought it was somethin' like that.
In which case...
You'd better explain yourself,
Taishi.
I was... well, I was just
thinking of my friend Kazuki!
Wait... Everyone?
I see.
Since you made that promise
to me, you ran away and hid...
I just wanted to go to the beach!
Oh, so that's all it was.
Oh dear, but I'm glad to know
that you didn't turn evil or anything.
Chisa is relieved.
But it's super strange
that I, the great Eimi Ohba,
the Queen of Queens of Comipa,
hasn't gone to the beach
when everyone else has!
My, Eimi, you really want
to go to the beach, don't you?
I-want-to-go!
Of course I do!
A pool's good enough for you.
Yay! I'll give you a
ticket for the kiddy pool!
I don't want it!
I want to go to the beach!
Everyone else is going, aren't you?
Man, that's some snotty attitude.
Are you saying I can't go to the beach?
You really are just
a spoiled little brat, aren't ya?
Maybe ya should take that
kiddy pool ticket from Chisa after all.
Now you've said it, hot spring panda!
It wouldn't have
turned into such a big fuss
if you woulda just said ya wanted
to go to the beach in the first place!
What's with you?! I just wanted
a nice little summer vacation!
That's the kind of
summer fit for the great Eimi!
Who cares about the beach?
What are you talkin'
bout wimpy stuff like that for?
"Passion"
Listen up! We stake
our lives on doujinshi!
If you go around talkin' bout
namby-pamby stuff like that,
ya got no right to call
yourself the Queen of Comipa!
Who cares about the beach?
Besides, there are
other guys who haven't gone.
You haven't gone either. Right, Kazuki?
Uh, well, you see...
Jeez! Take me to the beach!
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
Mendou na koto ga kirai na
Anata no ude hiki nagara
Yatto mitsuketa 2LDK
Teeburu setto mo ii kedo
Kekkyoku wa kotatsu deshou
Futari nekorogaru dake
Igai ni daiji na jikan
Donna toki mo yurishiaeru hito
Kantan ni wa
Deanai anata dakara
Ima sugu issho ni kurasou
Tarinai mono wa jikan dake
Egao mo namida mo hima mo
Wakeau basho ga hitsuyou deshou
Anata to nara itsu made mo
I'm not gonna let you have
it this time, hot spring panda!
That's my line, big dummy Eimi!
Don't go adding things to my name!
Ha! "Big dummy" is
good enough for you then!
You called me "big dummy" again!
I'll say it as many times as I want!
Big dummy! Big dummy!
- -You panda! You panda! You panda!
--Big dummy! Big dummy! Big dummy!
Next time: "What We're
After is Superhuman Baseball!"
Okay, let's play ball!
Huh?