All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"The Poison Doujin of Horror"
"Super Manga"
"Resurrection Series"
Doujin...
I bet that's Taishi.
Momonga!
"Super Manga"
It couldn't be... Damn him...
Doujin...
Hey you, Great Eimi sneaker!
It's not "sneaker," it's "stalker."
You couldn't wait until
Comipa for my new issue,
and came here as an
illustrial spy, didn't you?!
That's "industrial spy."
Well, either way,
you still didn't use it right.
Well too bad! I haven't even finished
the rough draft for this manuscript yet.
So make like a tree and get out of here!
"Make like a tree and leave."
Dang it, stop correcting
me every single time!
What are you even
doing here in the first place?
Whatever do you mean, Eimi Ohba?
Have you forgotten that I
always show up without any reason?
More importantly, are you sure
you should be ignoring the stalker?
Oh yeah!
Doujin...
What's this?
Freeze!
Don't look at that, Eimi Ohba!
Let go of it! You'll get
hit with its poison waves!
"Super Manga"
That is the doujin of
horror, the Poison Doujin!
Anyone who looks at
the poison manga inside...
Poison manga?
Hmm, sounds interesting!
I, the Great Eimi Ohba,
will give my opinion of it!
Let's see...
Say...
--Yes?
--Huh?
Well, never mind.
Hi ya! Kazuki, are you here?
I brought some nice refreshments today.
Have you heard of it?
The number-one ranked choice for
refreshments among manga authors,
the yakiniku boxed lunch!
Eimi? And even Aya too.
This is unusual, for the three of
you to get together so close to Comipa.
Did something happen?
Allow me to explain.
What's with you, Taishi?
Don't you want to know why these three
young ladies have gathered here at Elsinore?
You know?
Of course!
You see...
Taishi, what in the world...
What are you doing, My Brother?
Certainly I was enticed by the
allure of the elusive refreshment,
the Doujouen yakiniku boxed lunch.
But you see...
No one said anything
about the boxed lunch!
What's this?
No!
Hey, Yu!
No, you shouldn't look at it.
I shouldn't?
Comrade Kazuki...
Don't tell me you do not
know of the Poison Doujin.
Poison Doujin? What's that?
To think that you've
entered the doujin world,
and yet you do not
know of the Poison Doujin.
That's as foolish as trying to talk
about popular songs from the Showa era
without knowing about Taro Hitofushi.
Well, what is it?
Poison Doujin...
It is the doujin of horror,
and once you turn its pages,
you lose 100 days off
of your doujin life span.
100 days? What are you talking about?
I've heard about what
Taishi's talking about too.
You too, Aya?
Don't tell me that's
why the three of you...
Hey, the name of the
circle on the back cover
--is our college's manga club!
--What?
Kazuki!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It has begun.
"Club Meeting Hall"
This is the old club meeting hall.
It's just as creepy as I expected.
Actually, I've never been inside either.
But doesn't your club
have a club room in there?
Only on paper.
But there is a legend
that I'm a little worried about.
"Club Meeting Hall"
Legend?
What do you want to do? Quit?
No, I'm going.
You can stay behind if you want, Mizuki.
What are you talking about? I'm going too!
You're really sure about this?
That was a nice display of
resolve, My Brother and My Sister.
Taishi! Why you!
Take this!
And this!
I can't believe you!
This is our college's Kitora tomb.
A quite appropriate place for us
to mark our first step
toward world conquest, is it not?
What are you talking about?
I just came to find out who's playing
this practical joke about the Poison Doujin.
Poison Doujin!
So you really do intend to
go to the manga club after all?
Is this the wildness of youth?
Or is it a tragedy woven by ignorance?
Hey...
No, I will no longer try to stop you.
Come, let us go, young men and women.
Beyond this door of horror,
as your convictions demand!
Doujin...
Comic Party Revol...
Sheesh, some "Door of Horror" this is.
It's just old and creaky.
But...
Kazuki, look!
What the heck is that?
"Manga Research Club"
It looks like the legend is true.
Legend?
Look!
What the...
They're tea bags.
Tea bags?
There are ten great horrors of the
old club meeting hall. This is number five.
The legendary "black tea cactus."
A nightmarish cactus field,
made up of a countless number of tea bags
that were thrown up on
the ceiling and stuck there!
That sure does sound like a nightmare...
Huh? Is that you, Reiko?
Yuka, Miho, Mayu!
What are you guys doing here?
Not good. I seriously can't draw!
Panda...
Me neither.
Po... Poison Doujin?
You know about it?
--No.
--What's that?
Of course!
Huh? You know about it, Mayu?
You've heard about it, haven't you?
They say it's a doujinshi
that the manga club
made a looong, looong, looong time ago.
Oh! Oh, that?
But I heard that it was banned,
and completely burned a long time ago.
It looks like it's being distributed again.
The Poison Doujin?
What are the three of
you so shocked about?
Don't tell me you're
going to the manga club.
That's what we plan on doing.
You can't!
You can't go there.
I can't?
Doujin...
Poison... Doujin...
100 days?
Do you seriously think that intimation
like that could possibly work on me,
the genius, the Great Eimi?
You mean "intimidation."
Well, whatever.
If that's what you think,
then try drawing one picture.
Fine, just watch.
To drain or destroy talent, that
is the fearsome destructive power
of the Poison Doujin.
Even the talented Eimi
Ohba won't likely be able to draw.
What's going on here?
What's happened to me,
the genius, the Great Eimi?
They said the manga club's
room is all the way in the back, right?
Those girls seemed really scared.
Of the Poison Doujin, huh?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well, they're just like Yu and Eimi.
No, you're wrong.
About what?
About why those three were so scared.
I'm sure it's not just the Poison Doujin.
This is it! Number seven
of the Ten Great Horrors!
Number seven?
That must be the legendary
huge wave, Big Wednesday!
Do you realize how many young
people have been killed by that wave?
My Brother and My Sister!
Come now, arise!
We must go immediately,
for the sake of our world conquest!
Tremendous!
Taishi!
Comics?
The huge number of comics and doujinshi
that the manga and anime
clubs buy and buy during the year
pile up until they collapse
under their own weight,
and become a horrifying giant wave.
It collapses on the third Wednesday of
December, which is right before Comipa,
so as the years went by,
it became known as the
legendary giant wave "Big Wednesday."
I... I see...
I wonder if Kazuki and the others are okay?
Don't say something so creepy!
You never know...
Right about now,
he could be caught by
an evil, horrifying mask...
Inagawa, what was that just then?
Is something wrong?
No, I just remembered something.
Aya, no!
I thought so.
What do you mean?
Look at this poison manga.
Have you seen it somewhere before?
Huh? Seen it before?
This is...
No way!
We're finally in the home stretch.
Hey, Kazuki...
What?
I've been wondering for a while...
Exactly what kind of manga is this
Poison Doujin everyone's so afraid of?
Huh?
I forgot to look at the manga inside.
You didn't look? Why, you!
At this rate, we won't make it in time at all!
Huh?
The poison manga...
It is a horrifying manga
that is so poorly drawn
it is said to destroy the skills of those
who look at it by poisoning their sensitivity.
There's no doubt about it.
This is Subie's manga.
See here? Take a look at this.
Look at that bad penwriting!
That's "handwriting."
That is definitely Mikage's handwriting.
Sheesh, what is Subie thinkin'?
Could it be... You don't
think she was scouted, do you?
Skirted?
Scouted!
But how could someone
do something so reckless?
But I've heard about this.
This club has a terrifying legend.
Legend?
Mikage, you don't have
to bind the books so neatly.
No, I have to!
This is our first comeback issue!
It's a memorable occasion, so I need
to bind them perfectly nice and neat!
Kazuki!
And Mizuki and Reiko too!
Oh my, if it isn't Miss Haga.
President!
President? Then he's...
The shadow president of the manga club.
His name's Tsukishima.
Are you making doujinshi again?
Yes!
We, the manga research club,
are going to regain our former glory!
We have once again begun making
doujin which shall rule the otaku world!
The things he's saying
kind of remind me of someone.
Has the club been dormant up until now?
I don't know much about it either.
Allow me to explain.
There was a time when the manga
club actively produced doujinshi.
However, the excessively poor quality gave
birth to the legend of the doujin of horror,
which reduces the doujin life span
of those who look at it by a 100 days:
the "Poison Doujin."
The doujinshi they sent out were
all considered to have poison pages.
In other words,
sadly, they were completely
ostracized from the doujinshi world.
Needless to say, after that, the manga
club was embroiled in a storm of McCarthyism.
Making doujin was deemed to
be an evil deed, an immoral act,
and it was completely suppressed.
What a sad story...
Don't act like it's someone else's problem!
But why did you start up again?
It was the suppression.
The college authorities
detest literary clubs like vipers,
so they just decided to turn the
manga research club into a "ghost club"
without even consulting us,
and they're going to kick us
out of the old club meeting hall!
So that's why you
decided to make doujin again.
However, there was one big problem.
Our club has been forced to
seclude ourselves for so long,
we've lost all of our manga authors.
However, God has not abandoned us!
We were stricken with despair,
but a muse of doujin
manga appeared before us!
That's Subaru!
That's right. When I saw Subaru's
manga, I had a feeling in my bones.
I knew that with her,
the manga club could once again
climb to the heights of the doujin world.
And so, I immediately invited Subaru to
be the main guest author in our doujinshi.
And that's how the
Poison Doujin was revived, huh?
As well as the destructively
bad tastes which produced
the poison manga in the first place.
I guess it really is true that
blood is thicker than water.
Mikage, let's grab that doujin star together!
Subaru will do her best too!
Subaru, there's one thing
I don't understand though.
Why was that doujinshi sent
to Eimi, Yu and Aya's apartments?
Subaru asked the president to do that.
You did?
Yes!
They're stars of the doujin world,
and I really wanted them
to help with the next doujinshi!
And I thought that if I left it
with people in popular circles,
our first comeback
issue would sell lots and lots,
so those are the first
places I had him take it to.
I see. That's why...
What's wrong, Kazuki?
Oh, I just remembered something,
about that "Your doujin life span
will be reduced by 100 days" thing.
Now that I think about it,
we could be doing doujinshi for years,
so 100 less days isn't all that big of a deal.
Oh, you're right.
Now that you mention it, that's true.
Why are you laughing, guys?
Whatever the reason, I'm glad you're happy!
"Super Manga"
Doujin...
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
Say, Ms. Sawada, I know it's rather
rude to ask you this all of a sudden, but...
--What? You want to come watch us work?
- -Yes!
--Good idea.
I guess it would be good for you to take a
look at the professional world at least once.
May I?
I think it would be
good for you to think about
how it's the same
and how it's different from
the doujinshi world,
and then make your decision.
I'm looking forward to it!
I don't mind, but don't
be disappointed, okay?
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Next time: "Arise Kazuki,
It Is Time for World Conquest."
Now is the time for me
to decide what I want to do.