Nice to meet you!
We are...
Diamond Dust.
Our debut single--
We're wasting time.
This place isn't free.
We should look for
a bass player after all.
If we can find one.
But I think the three of us
sound pretty good as we are.
What is it?
It's just...
Who's the girl that was just talking?
No idea, D-D's new vocalist, right?
Not that I've ever met her.
What about her?
It can't be.
No, it's nothing.
yari nokoshita kodou ga kono yo wo ootte
This unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
zattou no naka de
koe naki koe de naite iru
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
ashiato ga ima dareka no koe o keshita asa
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
itsu ni natte mo kareru koto no nai
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
fuhaishita machi no doro mizu ga tsumetai
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
nani mo kawaranai sekai de
In a world where nothing changes
kyou datte ikite yukunda
We have to live through it
kudaranai kedo shikatanai desho
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
bokura wa mou aruki hajimetanda
We've already started walking
uso mitaina baka mitaina
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
doushiyo mo nai bokura no machi
This hopeless city of ours
soredemo kono me de tashika ni mietanda
But I still saw it with my own eyes
kono te de tashika ni furetanda
nee hora hora
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
hora mata fuita baka mitaida
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
doushiyo mo nai yami wo terase
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
yume janai douse owatteru machi datte
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
akirametatte kawannai ze aa mada mada
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
mada yari nokoshita kodou ga
kono yo wo ootte
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
bokura wo tsutsunde
konagona ni naru mae ni
Embracing us before we're crushed
tayori nakute mo ii sono te wo
kono te wa jibun jishin no mono sa
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
kawaranai hazu wa nai yo te wo nobashite
There will be change
If you just reach out
RISING VOCALS
Yo.
Hey, Momo! How many years has it been?
Not more than two, I think.
This place sure hasn't changed.
Yes, it has! We're about to go under.
Maybe even tomorrow!
You're my only hope.
Is that Momoka?
Wow, so cute!
Shut up.
She only looks like her, right?
Nina.
Y-Yes?
He said we can look inside.
-Excuse us.
It's a bit smaller than
the stage we played on before.
So this is how much room I'll have.
It's like this at most live houses.
But this place
has been around for a while,
so there are a lot of regulars.
They'll be ruthless if you suck.
He said he wanted us to play a show here.
What do you think?
A live show...
We don't have to if you're not feeling it.
-We'll need to practice--
-Let's do it.
At least think about it a little.
You're totally hooked now.
You were so reluctant before.
Well, we have about 20 minutes
for our set.
It won't be that bad.
Let's try it.
Here are your tickets.
Also, don't mention that I'm a former
Diamond Dust member in the promos.
I'm forming a new band
with these two after all.
Here.
There's no running away now.
What?
THE NEXT DAY
I didn't expect that we'd have to
sell them ourselves.
Have you sold any?
Of course not!
I only have two left.
No way!
Ask around at your cram school.
It's not like
they'll hear about it back home.
What?
My band is playing a show...
Would you be interested?
You're playing?
Yes.
I'm more of a fan of heavy metal.
Oh, I think you'll like our music then.
And you just gave it to her for free?
We need to get an audience before profits.
And it's not like we're in it
for the money to begin with.
Isn't it more important
that a lot of people show up?
They won't come.
Look, people generally don't want to waste
anything they spend money on,
but they're totally fine
with wasting something that's free.
Besides, we eat the cost
of any ticket we give away for free.
Do you really not know anything?
What do you mean?
We paid the live house
our own money for these tickets.
What?!
One medium beef bowl.
This kind of
ticket-quota concept is dying out,
but live houses generally
get paid upfront by the bands
as a participation fee
or to cover tickets.
That way, even if nobody shows up,
the venue is guaranteed a minimum income.
That's unfair!
That's the business!
These rice grains...
Huh?
Here.
Sorry to interrupt your break.
What?
Momoka should've told us that
she was putting up her own money.
Well, from her point of view,
we're just kids.
Why?
Well, we're younger and
it's not like we're out here with jobs.
Oh?
You were with Momo!
Hello!
What's that?
Where did I put it?
Is he going to add more tickets
we have to pay for?
I doubt it.
Found it!
Here you go.
What is it?
You know how Diamond Dust
is making their major debut?
They came by around noon
to thank me for my support in the past
and said I should go see them.
You're giving these to us?
I kind of lose interest when they get
such a major label backing them.
Why did Momoka quit Diamond Dust?
She didn't say?
No.
I don't know the details,
but there were rumors that they were told
to be more mainstream before they debuted.
Momo was the only one against it.
Could you give a ticket to Momo, too?
So, should we give one to Momoka?
I feel like we'd just
get into an argument.
But... I want to see them.
Then, want to go together?
I'm getting curious too.
Subaru...
You're the one who gave me
the live show ticket, right?
Yes.
I have three friends who want to go.
Do you have more tickets?
It's 7,500 yen for three tickets.
Oh, you're charging money?
You don't have to buy them
if you don't want to.
You're too extreme.
Then what was I supposed to do?
"Oh! Last week, we were allowed to
give them away for free,
but from this week,
I have to start charging people."
"But how about this?"
"I can give them to you for 2,500 yen
instead of 3,000!"
Liar.
It's hard work.
Okay, queue numbers 500 to 550!
What is it?
They sold out the venue as expected.
I'm currently at a crossroads
You won't find on any map
What should I use to guide me?
It's your own fault.
-No way... It can't be.
-How would you move forward?
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
-You don't get to sing this.
-Whether my fingers tremble or not
-What? Hey!
-There's no right answer
Hold on. What's wrong?
It hasn't even been five minutes!
Subaru.
What?
Give me a minute, I just feel like
saying some really nasty words right now.
I'll shout out some meaningless words
to let off some steam.
Huh?
...die, you piece of crap!
Some of the words at the end
were comprehensible.
What the hell? What the hell?!
-What the hell?!
-I don't know.
It had to be Diamond Dust?
Something I care about
just as much as my life.
My treasure...
So what's the problem?
Their new vocalist...
I know her.
She used to be my friend,
before I cut contact.
She's dead to me!
Girls Band Cry.
Nice to meet you!
We are...
Diamond Dust!
You'll break it.
I don't want to hear them.
You decided to go to their show,
got bent out of shape,
and now you're whining.
You know what that's called?
Annoying.
You wouldn't know how I feel.
I wouldn't even want to.
What kind of coincidence is this?!
Like some bad miracle!
Why is she the vocalist for Diamond Dust?
Not to mention how superficial she is!
But she actually went to many auditions
and ended up doing well, right?
-But still!
-Shut up!
That's your problem.
You're right, but I've listened to
and loved Diamond Dust
way more than anyone at that show!
That's what's annoying.
D-D doesn't belong to just you.
Then you're fine with this?
Seems fine to me.
They're more popular than
when I was in the band.
Is that all that matters?
It's better than not being popular.
You're not answering the question!
You're really butting into
other people's business.
I told you,
it's a waste of money to argue here.
Subaru.
It's no use.
There's no way we can practice like this.
If you're gonna fight,
make sure to settle it first.
TORITEI
PUB
-So?
-Hold on.
So unnecessary...
And by the way, why did we come to a pub
when you're wearing that?
It shouldn't be a problem
as long as I don't drink.
Why are you always in
your school uniform, anyway?
I don't have to figure out what to wear
and there are other benefits
when you're a high school girl.
Liar.
Anyway, enough about me. Now go.
Why do you defend them?
I'm not defending them.
Yes, you are. Think about it.
The current Diamond Dust isn't
the same as the one with you in it.
So?
I'm saying that it's weird
you're backing them up.
It's not weird!
I'm not in their band anymore,
so they're free to do whatever.
It's not my place
to criticize their decisions.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm asking you if you like it or not.
It's whatever.
I don't like it or hate it.
It's the band you were in.
It's the band
that you poured your soul into.
Don't decide that on your own.
I guess I was wrong then.
I guess you never cared about Diamond Dust
and never poured your soul into it.
Shut up.
It's who the vocalist is
that bothers you, right?
No!
I just want to know if you're fine with
what Diamond Dust has become!
Please pay no attention to us!
Calm down, both of you.
Listen, just like people,
bands grow and change.
For all things, change is inevitable.
Then why did you quit?
You quit because
you couldn't accept that change, right?
You quit because it wouldn't be
the Diamond Dust you knew.
You quit because you thought
you weren't wrong.
You quit because you hate
the kind of stuff they're doing now.
Why won't you say anything?!
Does the song I heard back then
mean nothing?!
Isn't that the kind of thing
D-D wanted to do?
Just admit that they're different.
What they are now isn't Diamond Dust!
They're just--
Oh, geez...
Shut up.
No.
I just love the Diamond Dust
that you were a part of.
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
I just love the Diamond Dust
that you were a part of.
That song changed my life.
Whether my fingers tremble or not
That's why I don't want you to lose.
I know you're not satisfied,
but you still say,
"I'm in the wrong. They're right."
I don't want to see you lie to yourself!
Do you know what
Diamond Dust's goal was back then?
What?
To keep the original band members
until we were all old ladies.
To never quit.
It wasn't about music or direction.
We only cared about that one thing.
That's why it's all my fault.
"Just be patient."
"One day, we'll be able to do
what we want to do."
They desperately tried to convince me.
But I still quit. I did.
Here. More oolong tea.
Thank you.
Nina.
I'm sorry for the commotion, folks!
Still...
I still like you.
Because I like your music.
Because the one who moved me
was the Diamond Dust from back then.
Because it was you.
You're so stupid.
You're dripping snot.
Yes, I am stupid.
I wouldn't be doing this here
if I weren't stupid.
More alcohol, please!
-Subaru...
-Hm?
What? Wait, no...
I'm sorry, looking at your face
just ticked me off.
I thought you could hold your liquor.
She did drink a lot today.
She reeks of booze.
You're dragging her!
-Get her legs!
-Roger!
How's this?
This feels weird...
We're going to put you down for a second.
I'm sorry.
Maybe she was happy.
No.
You should pick our stage outfits.
What?
Having someone you have a history with
take over as the vocalist for
your favorite band is a rare experience.
Better make use of it
and not let it go to waste.
Make use of it?
Putting all your anger,
joy, and sadness into it
is what makes bands great.
What?
The promo page for our upcoming show.
"Featuring former
Diamond Dust member Momoka!"
That jerk!
But this means some of the people
who went to see that Diamond Dust show
will definitely check us out.
So think about what you want to show them.
You're right.
Outfits...
But we can't spend much money on them.
It's been three years.
We were talking about how we need
to leave a mark at the next competition.
Momo!
Yo.
Sorry!
I told them not to,
but the staff just wrote that about you.
Though thankfully, we sold out the show!
What?
So, what about our outfits?
I thought these might work.
Here!
What? You guys prepared these?
Let us know if you don't like it.
You'll still have to wear it though.
I want you to bare it all with us.
I see.
I like it.
You're Momoka?
Yeah.
No offense, but I don't vibe
with girl bands.
Mind if I go tear it up?
We're not really a...
No need to worry,
we'll tear it up on our own.
Whatever.
Nice one.
18:25 SHINKAWASAKI (PLACEHOLDER)
Momo!
Momoka!
Momoka! I love you!
Wanna just start?
Don't you think "leaving a mark"
is a nice concept?
Frantically struggling
and flailing around...
We'll hurt ourselves in the process,
but also our adversaries.
Maybe.
Your song ripped my heart out.
It left a mark on me.
And told me not to lose, no matter what.
Let's go leave our mark!
Shout what you feel.
Don't speak and
just shout what's in your heart.
Your dissatisfaction, anger, sadness,
shame, embarrassment,
past events that make you want to scream,
and all the regrets that
make you sweat to just think about...
Just bare it all!
Let's go!
LIAR
WITHDREW
I'm gonna bare it all!
TRUANT
What did we find
At the constantly flowing intersection?
Hollow words, shaving each other down
A fallen shooting star
Would blow it all away
Well, we couldn't change anything at all
We pretend not to know
So our hands stay clean
In the corner of our eyes
Our dreams crumble to pieces
We pretend not to notice
We pretend not to hear
Look, it's passing us by
The city flows down a whirlpool of truth
Where should we float to?
If we can smile when we arrive
Then let's hold hands
It's not a dream
We finally notice
After they've turned to ashes
Our wishes never reach
In this ever-changing world
What should we come up with?
What should we raise?
Will I be able to meet you?
Before everything ends
With our own hands
Let's draw it out
Next episode, "Hymn of the Stray"