All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"Bravo at Inobou!"
I just can't seem to get motivated
unless there's a deadline coming up.
Hot spring!
Yu!
Kazuki, let's go to a hot spring!
Hot spring?
The Kansai Comic Party!
It's held at the Osaka
National Culture Exhibition Hall.
Where writers and
readers from Osaka and Kobe
polish their talents,
and overcome hardship.
It's our battleground!
It's like a field of guts for Kansai doujin!
Kansai Comipa, huh?
So what does that have
to do with the hot spring?
Well about that, Kazuki...
How's about helping out Karamitei?
Huh? You mean your circle?
This time I wanna go
all out and sell like crazy!
An' besides, the more staff the better!
Okay? I'm counting on you!
Oh, I've already arranged a place
for you to stay, so don't worry 'bout that!
If ya stay at my place,
you can go in the hot
spring as much as ya want!
Oh yeah, that's right.
Your family runs an inn in Kobe.
Just help me out a little bit,
and after that, you can
relax and enjoy the hot spring!
Whaddya think? Sounds good, don't it?
A hot spring, huh?
I guess it wouldn't hurt to
take it easy once in a while.
Really?
Thanks a bunch!
I knew I could count on you!
What?
Oh, nothing.
I've heard the whole story.
You again.
Very impressive, Comrade Kazuki.
To think that to gain
a foothold on world conquest,
you are advancing toward Kansai!
--A hot spring, that's nice!
--Since time immemorial, once every year,
--Don't you think, Kazuki?
--special effects shows have tie-ins with local inns
--I guess there are some things
--only a hot spring panda can do.
--and do large-scale shooting.
--Following that ancient and honorable custom
--Thank you so much for
--inviting Subaru along too!
--isn't a bad idea at all.
Chisa is grateful too!
I'll make a pleasure trip out of this!
Hot springs are good
for your health, right?
Excuse me, I'll come too.
What a coincidence.
I was just chosen to observe
operations at the Kansai Comipa.
Hey, nice for all of you to come!
The more the merrier!
That's the best way to go!
Awright! There's going to be surprises!
There's going to be a little
peek-a-boo too! Hot spring, here we come!
Yeah!
Boo hoo hoo...
And so, we're all here!
"Inobou Inn"
It's a so-called long standing inn
that's been in my family for generations.
Whaddya think? Ain't it nice?
You can sure feel the history!
Yeah, I never expected it to be
so deep in the mountains though.
If it's been in your family for generations,
does that mean that you'll
become the innkeeper here one day?
Darn right!
That's been my dream since I was a kid!
Her dream since she was a child, huh?
I figure I'll marry a nice guy,
and we'll run the inn together.
Welcome!
Well, let's leave the
tedious chit-chat for later.
First up, let's get in the bath!
Yeah!
"Men's Bath"
"Women's Bath"
Aaah, this feels so nice.
So this is a hot spring! Chisa is impressed!
Big baths are the best!
Subaru is going to swim!
No, Subaru, you have to follow the rules.
It doesn't matter.
We're the only customers here today,
so it's like we've got
the whole place reserved.
Umm... Isn't there a lot of steam?
Oh, there's a few reasons for that.
Just bear with it.
Wow, Aya's skin is so smooth!
Where?
Umm... That tickles.
Hey everyone, notice my nice body!
Yeah, your scrawny "nice body."
You're the one who's as flat as a board!
What are they talking about?
Hi...
Oh! Ikumi!
I thought you were a kid,
but I see this part of you is
growing up pretty steadily there!
You think so?
Compared to the
rest of you, I'm just, well...
They're bigger than Chisa's!
Stop! That's embarrassing!
Ikumi, you've grown so
much before I even realized it.
Across all ages and lands,
one of the standard activities
at a hot spring is peeping!
What kind of hot spring story
would this be without peeping?
Arise, Comrade Kazuki!
Now is the time to rouse
that passionate blood within you!
By the way, I'm already roused.
But that's a crime!
You coward!
You should etch the long-cherished
desire of men deep into your eyes!
Hey!
Come on, knock it off, Taishi!
Oh my...
What do you think you're doing?
No!
Get out of here!
Bravo!
Ikumi's gotten bigger.
Then what exactly are you looking at?!
There's nothing like this after a bath!
Killer move! Peach Scramble!
What?
Daiei Ryu ultimate technique!
Fierce Tiger, White Dragon Smash!
Hot spring ping pong sure is fierce.
Okay, here I go.
All right! Go ahead!
There!
It looks like I lost.
What's so relaxing about a hot spring?
I can't take it easy at all.
Are you okay?
Huh?
Yu...
What's wrong?
If you're tired, I can set up
a futon in your room for you.
Oh, no, I'm totally fine.
Sorry to worry you.
Thank goodness you're all right.
I don't know what I would have
done if anything had happened to you.
You're exaggerating.
No, I'm not!
I really...
Actually, I've got something
important to talk to you about.
Something important?
Kazuki!
Kazuki, I...
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Kazuki, I...
Yu...
Hold it!
What do you think you're
doing to Kazuki, Hot Spring Panda?!
You were just off-handedly
hanging all over him!
What are you talking about?
Oh, there's lint.
That little act of yours won't work on me!
The Great Eimi's eyes
aren't lined, you know!
I think you mean "blind".
Your brain's as tiny as ever.
What's with you?! Who do you think I am?!
I'm the King of
Queens of the Comipa world!
The one who makes crying
kids laugh! The Great Eimi!
I don't even know where to
begin making fun of you for that.
Yu...
"Inobou Inn"
"Restroom"
I can't relax at all.
But Yu was acting kind of strange today.
He seems like a pretty nice boy.
No wonder you picked him.
You said his name is Sendo, right?
Have you come out and
told him how you feel, Yu?
Not yet. I'm worried
about if he turns me down.
That's not like me.
Then do you want me to tell him?
No, that's not a good idea!
This is my problem.
I'll find out how Kazuki feels myself.
It's for this inn.
Taking over this inn is my dream.
Yu's dream?
Darn right!
That's been my dream since I was a kid!
I figure I'll marry a nice guy,
and we'll run the inn together.
Could she really be serious about me?
Comic Party Revolution!
Je t'aime.
Comic Party
Revolution!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Hup, two, three, four...
That was close.
Thanks, Kazuki!
Are you all right?
Actually, I'm sorry, I was spaced out.
Oh, don't worry 'bout it!
Things are almost ready for
the party, so look forward to it!
Did you make all the
preparations yourself?
Well, yeah.
It might be "long standing,"
but in the end it's just a small inn.
The situation behind the
scene's lookin' pretty bad.
Yu...
Sorry, I shouldn't be
complainin' to a customer.
I'll just finish this up real quick.
Kazuki?
It's all right for me to carry this, right?
And if we get everyone else
to help, it will be done real fast!
But I couldn't ask customers to do that...
Don't call us customers, that's too formal.
We're friends, aren't we?
Kazuki...
See ya.
Wait a minute.
Yu...
Don't move.
Stay just like this, for just a little bit...
Uh, sure...
Thanks, Kazuki.
Sure...
Um, hey, listen...
Cheers!
Delicious!
This is the best!
Getting in the hot spring,
playing ping pong,
and even eating all this delicious food...
Hot springs are the best!
Oh, Chisa...
What are you sitting there,
eating so purposelessly for, Comrades?
When at a hot spring,
you must have a party!
And there's no party
without a special party stunt!
It's a law of the great universe!
I shall lead the way!
Have a real good look, oh, my sisters!
I saw something good.
Physical beauty, huh?
In that case, I will...
Big Brother, no!
Right... Fine, I understand.
Hey, this is pretty good food.
I guess there are some things
only a hot spring panda can do.
You're the only one
who calls me that, you know.
How dare you talk to me like
that?! I was giving you a compliment!
Darn right!
That's been my dream since I was a kid!
Kazuki...
Kazuki, I...
Stay just like this, for just a little bit...
What am I thinking?
Yu's the last one who
would do something like that.
What is "something like that"?
What am I thinking?
Delicious!
Big Brother, wake up!
Where's Kazuki?
This is my problem.
I'll find out how Kazuki feels myself.
Does she really have feelings for me?
Feels nice, huh?
Yu!
It's so nice, isn't it?
Soaking in a hot spring
and looking up at the moon?
Good evening, Moon!
Umm, well...
Why did you come in here,
Yu? This is the guy's bath!
At this time of night,
the open air bath is mixed bathing.
It's posted out on the door.
It is?
I'm sorry.
You don't gotta apologize.
Since it's mixed bathing,
it doesn't matter who comes in.
So we can both get in
without bein' embarrassed.
I guess you're right. Yeah...
So, isn't this nice?
Huh?
Isn't this a nice bath?
Even 'round here,
there aren't any other
hot springs where you can
take it easy as much as you can here.
It's our business's pride and joy!
Yeah, you're right.
Well, there's been a lot of commotion,
but you let me relax
for the first time in a while.
Really? Thanks.
No, thank you!
But once I take it over,
I'm going to make this inn even better.
I'd be happy if you get
to like it even more too.
Kazuki, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Sorry.
Huh?
I didn't notice your feelings at all.
Kazuki?
I can't believe you see so much in me.
I don't really know if I
should say thank you or what.
Oh, so you noticed?
Oh, yeah, I should apologize to you.
Asking you to help with the
Kansai Comipa was just an excuse.
Huh?
To tell ya the truth, I wanted you
to see my family's inn and hot spring.
But...
Yu...
But in that case, it makes
things simpler! Right, Kazuki?
Yu...
Here we are!
Greetings! Welcome to Inobou Inn!
Wow, what a nice looking couple!
Oh, you kid. Right, dear?
But that's kinda... It's not
like I hate you or anything, but...
Well, I think it's too soon.
It's not too soon at all!
The chance is now!
Take the plunge and leap into my chest!
Chest?
But I can't decide about
the future yet right now.
Huh?
There's still a lot
I want to do with doujinshi.
There's a lot I still want to write.
And is taking over this
inn even right for me at all?
Hold it, Kazuki.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about whether I should
marry you and take over this inn or not.
Huh?
You and me?
I see...
So that's what you thought, huh, Kazuki?
Yu...
So you're not gonna listen
to my request, no matter what?
Ah, no, you see, umm...
It's not like I won't do it no matter what...
I don't know what to do.
In that case...
Huh?
Would you do just one favor for me?
Uh, sure.
I'm sleepy.
We ended up carrying on until morning.
Jeez! That hot spring
panda gets too carried away!
To think that I would be hindered
by one of the three great desires,
the desire for sleep...
Could this be the plot of a secret society,
bent on preventing us
from conquering the world?
Or could it be...
"Karamitei"
Hey! What are you all
just standin' there for?
To us, this is a battlefield!
Ya gotta go all out!
Listen up! Our goal for today is to sell out!
Sell and sell and sell some more!
Speaking of which...
You got that, Mr. Boar?
Squeal, squeal...
Kazuki?!
You're wrong there!
It's Inobou Inn's cute mascot, Mr. Boar!
At any rate, you fit in
our costume perfectly!
I was right about picking you!
I made sure to take measurements too.
No wonder you picked him.
You said his name is Sendo, right?
In other words, this is
what that was all about, Yu?
Don't be that way,
you wouldn't have said yes if I asked ya
to do this right from
the start, now would ya?
--I've been tricked.
--Wow! How cute!
It looks rather good on you, Kazuki.
First a girl, now an animal?
Even Haga would have
trouble keeping up with that.
Well, that's just how Spot is, you know?
It's an animal hero of justice!
Awright!
We're gonna publicize both Karamitei
and Inobou Inn for all we're worth!
I'm countin' on all of you to go all out!
Yeah!
What was that nervous thrill all about?
Give me back my innocent emotions!
I could say the same thing.
I was pretty nervous too, ya know.
What were you nervous about, Yu?
It... It doesn't matter!
Come on, it's gonna be opening soon!
If you're ever in Kobe,
be sure to stop by the Inobou Inn!
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
This day has finally come.
Thank you so much for
everything you've done for me.
There's nothing left for me to teach you.
You've worked hard, Ikumi.
Big Sister Mizuki!
I... I...
Leave your tears for
later, until after we win!
Right!
Okay, let's go! To our court!
Next time: "Princess of Tennis (tentative)."
Not quite there yet, huh?