All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"Sunrise Café"
Whaaaaaaaat?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Congratulations, Kazuki.
Well, is this for real? I'm...
Yes! At the next Comic Party,
Brother 2 is going to
have a space against the wall.
But me? That's...
Congrats!
Now you're a full-fledged doujinshi artist!
I knew I was right about you!
Yeah, but...
Please have confidence in yourself.
My circle's going to have
a space against the wall?
This pisses me off!
This pisses me off! This pisses me off!
This super pisses me off!
It's a hundred billion light years too
early for Spot to get a space against the wall!
A group of impartial judges
from the preparation committee
determine the placements.
This just shows how
highly they think of Kazuki.
Better not let your guard
down or you'll get tripped up.
But it's not like I work in popular genres,
or make top selling books, so why me?
Draw what you want to draw!
That's what doujinshi's all about!
And if you can get
the customers to enjoy it...
What are you talking about?
Books that don't
sell don't mean a thing!
You can draw what you
want however much you want,
but if it doesn't sell,
it doesn't mean a thing!
Eimi...
Go ahead and draw as many
totally weak books as you want,
and make a total disgrace of yourself!
Huh?
Eimi don't you have a clue 'bout what
you should say and what you shouldn't?
Hmph!
Ah, just forget 'bout
what that Big Dummy Eimi said.
Just draw the manga you always do.
That's the most important thing.
Yeah...
"Kuhonbutsu, Taishi"
"Receiving"
Hello?
My Comrade! Are you
improving yourself by working hard?
At the upcoming Summer Comipa,
we shall realize our ambitions and...
Help me out once in a while!
Good morning!
Were you up all night again?
Mizuki, what's wrong?
You're having a hard time
with the next Comipa, right?
You see... I heard from Minami.
Yeah, I guess.
Com... Comipa is
important, but so is college.
Your afternoon class is required!
I know.
And...
See ya, I have to work on my manuscript.
Kazuki...
Oh, hi, Sendo!
Reiko...
I heard!
You're getting a space
against the wall at the next Comipa?
Are you sure you can
afford to be messing around here?
Well, this is a little change of pace.
Congratulations, Sendo.
It kind of makes us happy too!
Th... Thanks.
Of course, you're going to do a book about
my darling Sho and my darling Gash, right?
Probably not.
Oh no!
I was so looking forward to it!
Sendo you dummy, dummy, dummy!
You're going to betray the dreams
of three million girls all over Japan!
Well...
Just kidding!
It was a joke!
Your books are so pretty, I really like them.
In other words, draw
a book that comes from you.
Make the kind of book you like!
That's the most important thing.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well then, good luck on your manuscript!
Hey, we have to work on ours too!
This time we're going
to keep to the schedule!
Although we never have before!
The kind of book I like, huh?
But...
I guess I have no choice.
Let's go home together.
Mizuki...
Come on!
Mizuki!
Mizuki?
What?
I'm sorry about this morning.
I was irritated because the
manuscript wasn't going well.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
You don't remember?
He's doing nothing but drawing manga.
When it comes to test time,
he's going to ask to borrow my notes.
Not that I'm writing
them for him or anything.
This is... Right, this is
just a review of today's lecture.
"Kuhonbutsu, Taishi"
"Receiving"
Is your manuscript progressing well?
This time, I was thinking
we'd do a special porn...
I know, my so-called "Brother."
Looks like I'm out of paper.
"Uchudo"
Aya!
Congratulations on getting a wall space.
Oh, thanks.
Big Brother!
Kazuki!
What's going on, you two?
Subaru finished her manuscript too.
So I'm helping Chisa out.
It's the rebirth of the ultimate team!
I see. You're done
already. That's impressive.
You're the one who's impressive, Kazuki!
That's right!
Now that you've been given a wall space,
you're way out of the
usual league, like royalty!
Oh, don't exaggerate.
Subaru's going to apply herself,
work hard, and catch up to you!
Chisa's going to work hard too,
so please keep using Tsukamoto Printing.
I'm looking forward
to working with you more!
Good luck.
Bye now!
Good luck!
I have to get to it too.
Kazuki!
Mizuki!
That's a lot of food.
How many days worth is it?
Well, it's three days worth, I guess.
Three days worth?
Do you really eat that much?
It's enough for two people.
Huh?
Because I want you to eat right.
Would it bother you?
No, not at all.
Great!
Uh, well, sorry for the trouble.
Not at all! I'm doing it because I want to.
Oh, sorry, let me carry those.
Thanks, Kazuki.
Hey, which do you like
better: nikujaga or curry?
Well, nikujaga, I guess.
Okay, then let's have nikujaga.
Oh, but curry would be good too.
Then do you want curry?
No, maybe I'll have the nikujaga after all.
Okay, then why don't we have both?
Ramen tanmen tantanmen!
Remen nyumen hiyasomen!
The hands go like this,
the feet go... oh, like this...
Haga said that cosplaying a character
without understanding her is insulting.
If I cosplay, I wonder if
it would make him happy?
Forget I just said that!
Why would I do something
like this for a guy like him?
My eternal friend!
Have you begun to
long to hear my voice yet?
I'm going to block you,
my unwanted friend.
Yes?
Ikumi's big brother!
Is this for me?
Some snacks. Take it.
Th... Thank you very...
I have a message from Ikumi.
"Cough cough..."
Good luck, Kazuki.
I'll be cheering you on from under the sod.
That is all.
"From under the sod"? That sounds morbid.
Don't do anything that
will disappoint her, got it?
Su... Sure thing.
Jeez, whatever...
Kazuki!
Mizuki? When did you...
I finished cleaning.
What's this?
I'm going to do the laundry.
Do you have anything else to wash?
That's not what I was talking about.
Oh, nothing, never mind.
Okay.
Good! That's about right.
I guess the fact he's not very
picky makes it easier to cook for him.
And besides, if I don't make him eat
properly, he'll end up starving to death.
I'm doing this voluntarily too!
Don't get any strange ideas, all right?
Comic Party Revolution
Good morning, Kazuki.
Good morning, Mizuki.
Kazuki, why don't
we go somewhere today?
Huh?
The weather is gorgeous!
Okay?
Thanks.
Huh?
You were worried about me, right?
You just haven't seemed very well lately.
I was wondering if it was because
your art hasn't been going very well.
Yeah...
This has been a nice change of pace.
That's great! I'm glad I could help you.
Huh? Yeah...
I should do something
to thank you next time.
Then make a picture, a picture of me.
Use you as a model?
Yeah, because I love your art.
Okay, sure.
Then let's go back to your apartment.
He's not coming out.
C'mon, don't be so defiant, dammit!
--Like I said, I didn't do anything wrong!
--Huh?
--Just apologize!
Yu, Eimi...
What're you all doin' here?
Well, actually...
So in other words, you all got together
because you're worried
'bout Kazuki, but he ain't here.
Yes, this is his first
time at a wall spot, so...
We thought maybe
he's having a tough time.
He's always helping us out, so...
We want to help him out somehow.
As his senior from a popular major circle,
I thought I'd give him some random advisory!
That's "welcome advice!"
Before that though, you
gotta apologize for the other day!
But it's weird for him not to
be around right before the deadline.
Don't tell me that in there is...
Hold it! Stop that!
Mizuki!
Mizuki...
Make a nice picture of me, okay?
Okay?
You're kiddin' me, right?
It's protected by
some kind of powerful will.
Normal methods won't open it.
What?
What I make is...
Oil paintings, of course.
Huh? But I...
You couldn't get into an art college,
but you still kept
making the art you love, right?
And you said you were thinking
about being in the next art exhibition.
Isn't that right, Kazuki?
You make oil paintings.
I make oil paintings.
Your art is so gentle, so warm... I love it.
Hold it right there!
What do you think you're doing?
How thoughtless of you, to come
into someone's room with shoes on.
And through the window, no less!
I was going to bring some
snacks and the notes I took,
and I happened to see Kazuki there!
I have to make oil paintings.
I don't know who you are,
but get away from Kazuki!
Don't get me wrong.
This is something he wanted.
What was that?
He was given a wall space so suddenly...
He wasn't sure whether he should
draw what he wants, or what will sell.
But the deadline was coming up fast...
That's enough...
Let's go back to when
you drew what you wanted.
It was so much fun back then.
I am an illusion created by his emotions.
This is the world he desired.
The truth is, you never wanted
him to draw manga, did you?
What?
Isn't that right, Mizuki Takase?
Won't you come over here?
Come, now.
What?
Kazuki has a hard time getting up.
If I don't keep a good eye
on him, he'll skip all three meals.
He butts into people's business
even though he's irresponsible.
He's not serious,
he's immature, and he's rash...
But when it comes to his art...
He's more serious than
anything when it comes to his manga!
I won't accept Kazuki being like this!
Ramen tanmen tantanmen!
Remen nyumen hiyasomen!
Don't just take him into some weird world!
It looks like words aren't
going to get through to you.
It's no use.
As long as he desires this world,
you have no chance of winning!
Kazuki!
What? I know that voice!
Comrade Kazuki!
There's only one week
until the printing deadline!
How is your manuscript coming?
Oh, shut up!
If you're really that worried
about it, then help me out a little!
Nonsense!
I know full well how talented you are!
When you got an honorable mention
in the elementary school art contest,
I could feel it in my bones!
Listen, you...
Wait, what in the world am I doing?
Kazuki!
Mizuki? When did you...
Wait, there's two Mizukis?
Kazuki, you're going to draw manga, right?
Huh?
You're not going to
quit making doujinshi, right?
Mizuki?
You're not going to give
up because it's hard, right?
Oh, yeah, I was chosen
for a space on the wall.
Ka... Kazuki! You're
going to draw manga, right?
I...
I am going to draw manga!
It's about time for you
to be kicked out of here!
Super Attack! Peach Home Run!
Refresh!
Owww...
Guys!
It finally opened!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
Whoa! That's super dirty!
What in the world is going on here?
Kazuki, you don't have time, you know!
Hurry up and draw your manuscript!
Oh, yeah!
What's with you?
Comrade Mizuki, it seems you've
completely turned into one of us.
Comic Party is now open.
I have to go change!
I'm fine here, so go on ahead.
Keep it up until the very end, okay?
Yeah!
Oh, welcome!
Mizuki...
May I have one?
Yeah...
But why would you buy one?
Your art is so gentle, so warm... I love it.
That's why...
That took a lot of time!
I have to hurry back!
Thank you for all your hard work, everyone.
Comic Party is now closed.
We look forward to
seeing you all again next time.