All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"What We're After is
Superhuman Baseball!"
Take Minami to Koshien...
Maki!
Minami!
My, my, this is unusual.
What's the matter, you two?
What's going on here?
"Ohba, Eimi"
"Comic Party Exhibitor Pass"
"Inagawa, Yu"
Oh dear, they're the same number?
You'd better have a
good explanation for this!
This is a double booing!
You mean double booking.
Actually, I guess you're right, in a way.
There must have been
some mistake. I'm sorry.
But this is going to be a problem.
There aren't any empty spaces left.
Then just reject Karamitei.
How about you drop out?
Why don't the two
of you share the space?
Well, I'm okay with that.
I'd be worried 'bout this moron
interfering with business though.
That's my line!
If I get stuck with some panda,
my sales are going to drop!
What'd you say?
What, you want to fight?
Now, now, calm down, you two.
Just a moment, ladies!
Why don't we settle
this pleasantly with sports?
Man, you really like to
hide all over the place, don't ya?
I think that's a wonderful suggestion!
Wait! I'm not good at sports!
I'm okay with it.
If we settle this with a contest,
there won't be any hard feelings!
'Course, if ya don't wanna do it,
you could always just give up now.
Fine then! We'll go with sports!
Then we need to
decide what kind of sport.
Since it's two people,
you could do boxing or judo.
Or perhaps wrestling.
Watching young ladies intertwining
with each other is also very exciting.
Excuse me...
Why don't you settle it with baseball?
Kazuki! Baseball time!
Huh?
Starting today, you're one of my team!
Now let's get lookin' for
the rest of the team members!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
This's no time for complainin', dummy!
Kazuki, are you here?
You're too late, Eimi.
I already got Kazuki on my team.
I got beaten to the punch by a panda!
Then I have no choice!
--I'll try other people!
--Bye!
Jeez, what's going on?
So there you have it, Comrade Kazuki.
Will you chase the white ball with us?
You're on Yu's team too?
But why are we playing baseball
all of a sudden? I just don't get it.
This is no time to be
sittin' around sippin' tea!
We gotta get nine players together, fast!
Coming.
Who is it?
Hiya!
What are you slammin' the door shut for?
Because, I've got a really,
really bad feeling about this.
Don't be so cold, Mizuki!
We just came to ask if ya
wanna play some baseball!
Baseball?
So, since we assumed that you're
a good athlete, we came to scout ya.
But why do I get the feeling
you have some ulterior motive?
C'mon, please? We need your help!
It's so sudden though.
I can play softball, but
I'm not sure about baseball.
Such a shame.
With someone as
good as you on our team,
going to Koshien
wouldn't be just a dream!
Koshien?!
"Tsukamoto Printing"
Baseball?
Darn right! Kids should be outside,
in the fresh air! Let's baseball!
I'm happy that you asked me,
but Chisa isn't very good at sports.
Besides, I have to help out here,
so I don't have any free time.
Three thousand.
Tsukamoto Printing will get an order for
three thousand copies of the next book.
Really?
From Kazuki, that is.
Me?
I'm so happy, big brother!
Um, well...
Thank you very much!
Chisa will try her best at baseball!
All right! We got a team member!
Baseball?
You got it! We're gonna
save Comipa with baseball!
Eimi Ohba has begun her plot to invade
Comipa with an evil baseball army!
I've heard something like that before.
You ain't so naïve
any more, are ya, Subie?
Even Subaru grows up.
Anyway, we're going to play baseball.
And we need your help.
Just think of it as doing us a favor.
I understand!
Since you're the one asking,
Kazuki, I would love to help you!
Awright! Here's a symbol
that you're one of us!
What? Baseball? Sure, sure!
There!
That was fast.
Leave the uniforms to me!
I'll make them kind of cute!
How's it going, Kazuki?
I can't get a hold of Aya, and
Asahi said she's busy with work.
Bummer...
I wonder if that's Reiko?
Hi!
Hello!
Huh?
I called them over. They're
going to help me make the uniforms.
Awright!
Now we have ten people!
Hey, Yu, you can't
decide that without asking.
They've already come this far, so now
they're gonna be in the same boat as us.
Got that?
Yes...
They're late!
They're late! They're late! They're late!
What in the world are they doing?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm amazed you didn't
run away, hot spring panda.
I'll give you credit for that much.
That's my line!
We'll show ya the
results of our special training!
I don't know what kind
of special training you had,
but there's no way you can beat my team.
Chisa!
Aya!
You too, Taishi?
What's goin' on here, Chisa?
I'm sorry.
But big sister Eimi said she'd
give us an order for five thousand.
That's playin' dirty!
Why are you on that team, Aya?
Eimi asked me first.
That's sure a simple reason.
I can kind of imagine,
but what's your excuse, Taishi?
I am a free agent!
The signing bonus was a purchase
ticket for Cat or Fish's new issue.
Yup, I thought it was something like that.
Forget about the traitors.
Let's get to the game.
Now then, we will now begin the game
between the Inobou Rockers
and the Pretty Penguins.
We will start with the opening ceremony.
Opening ceremony?
Hello! I'm Asahi Sakurai!
Ooh! Asahi!
What is Asahi doing here?
Why, opening ceremonies are
a part of an idol's job, of course!
Here I go!
That was a good throw!
I practiced in order to play the
main character of a baseball anime.
Now we got all the players we need!
Hold it! What was that?!
I would like to be traded
to the Inobou Rockers.
Me too.
--Me too.
Denied! Denied! Denied!
First up, Pretty Penguins.
Okay, play ball!
Swing with all you've got, got it?
You can count on me!
Strike!
How could you let a
gopher ball like that slide by?
Strike!
After those two pitches,
I have all the data I need.
Here I go!
Strike! Batter out!
Tate!
Tate! Get up, Tate!
It got my hip.
Please go easy on me.
What are you doing?! Run!
Not this way, stupid!
Out!
That was a perfect chance!
Be careful, Mizuki.
You don't have to tell me that.
What incredible pressure...
Looks like it's finally my turn.
I'm gonna hit a beautiful home run!
Strike! Batter out!
"Pretty Penguins"
"Inobou Rockers"
Hey Eimi, ya sure you
can throw that thing right?
What's with you? I practiced!
Play ball!
Just watch the great
Eimi's gorgeous pitching!
Interesting placement!
Leave it to me!
Out!
So close!
Why didn't ya slide?
If you had slid,
ya woulda made it in time!
But that would get the uniform all dirty.
What're you talkin' about?
Ow, ow!
My comrade...
Hit for the moon!
Oh c'mon, it's daytime!
It doesn't matter if it's day or night!
What's that supposed to mean?
What's with the blabbering? Here I go!
Awright! It's outta here!
Out!
Number three Subaru! Ready to go!
A left grounder?
Ya gotta be kiddin'...
Safe!
Awright!
We've got a runner on base!
This is actually turning out to
be a decent game of baseball.
This is no time to relax!
At this rate, we're gonna lose!
Leave it to me. I'll bring
that runner home, count on it.
Sheesh, I'm pooped.
Hey, someone switch with me!
I could do it for a little while.
Then it's all yours.
What the heck? A relief pitcher?
What was with that throw?
It was so slow!
This is great! We can
definitely hit a pitch like that!
We're gonna turn this
game around in one shot!
She has no speed on her
pitches, and the control is weak.
Got it!
Strike!
This time for sure!
Strike two!
Strike! Batter out!
Good going, Aya! Keep it up!
Jeez, what kind of pitch do you call that?
What the heck are you doin'?
How'd you miss a pitch like that?
Strike! Batter out!
It's... It's a magic ball.
It's that magic ball they talk about.
Strike! Batter out!
She couldn't hit it either?
What the? What's going on here?
Ball four! Batter takes first base.
Time!
Are you okay, Mizuki?
You've been doing all
the pitching by yourself.
If they get a hit now,
the game's all but over.
Want me to take over?
No, I'm fine. I can keep going.
But...
I'm going to keep going!
I promised Coach!
Huh?
I promised Coach I'd never give up!
Takase! We're not done yet!
Coach, I can't go on.
Don't give up! If you give up, you lose!
To put in English,
that would be "makeinu!"
Coach, that's not English.
Weren't you trying to get to Koshien?
Coach...
Look, Takase! Isn't
that a gorgeous sunset?
Yes! I won't give up!
So I will keep on pitching!
Who in the heck is this "Coach"?
I will not lose.
Takase Tornado!
Batter out! Change!
Impossible...
All right, ninth inning!
We're gonna turn this
around no matter what!
Strike! Batter out!
There.
One more left. This game is ours!
I can't hit such a slow ball.
She didn't make it in time?
Time! Time! We got a pinch hitter!
Did I make it in time?
Ikumi...
What is Ikumi doing here?
I called her over. She's our secret weapon!
Secret weapon?
That's right!
To hit such a slow ball,
the batter's gotta be slow too.
It says so in a book!
And the one who can pull it off is...
You, Ikumi Tachikawa!
You're the only one!
I'll do my best!
Ikumi is...
Even though she's sickly,
Ikumi is playing baseball.
I'm...
I'm so incredibly moved right now.
She hit it!
Awright! Just like I planned!
But it's an outside fly.
We won!
Big brother! I hit the ball! Big brother!
Ikumi...
What are you doing?!
Get a hold of yourself and catch it!
I can't.
I... I can't catch Ikumi's ball.
I am super pissed off!
If you'd caught it like you
should have, we would've won!
My life span as a pitcher has ended.
Huh?
If I pitch any more,
I won't be able to hold a pen.
Eimi!
Let's finish this! We'll go one on one!
Fine! I'll do it!
Strike!
Not bad at all.
Foul!
I am definitely going to win!
I'm not gonna lose!
It got past him!
But he's in the outfield.
Ikumi!
Ikumi is running so... so desperately.
What are you doing? Throw it back home!
My... My sight's blurry.
Uh huh?
Uh huh...
Safe!
I'm turnin' this around in one shot!
Uh huh, uh huh...
Uh huh!
Oh, no you don't!
This is...
Out!
Which means...
The Inobou Rockers have
scored one run, bringing it to a 4-4 tie.
What do you mean, tie?
Let's have extra innings! Extra innings!
But look, everyone's already going home.
Hey, don't go home yet!
It's not over yet!
Yeah! Maki, call for extra innings...
Uh, she's gone.
Now I don't know why we bothered
to play the game in the first place!
That's what I'm saying!
--I ain't happy with this!
--I'm not happy with this!
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
Oh my, you draw doujinshi too?
Huh? Um, well...
And what kind of story is it?
It's basically about love.
Don't tell me it's going
to be a "boys love" story?
Um, no...
Is it yaoi?
Umm...
Could it be something
like you'd see in "June"?
Aren't those all the same?
No, I mean, I...
Oh look, we've run out of time.
Huh? Um, next time:
"Please Listen to My Feelings!"
Please listen to what I'm saying too!