Hi there!
How's it going, Kazuki? You all ready?
No, not yet. My books
haven't been delivered yet.
Tada!
The Doujin Queen,
the great Eimi, has come to greet you!
Here, Kazuki, I brought
you some homemade cookies.
Yoo-hoo! Sendo!
Take a look at my new costume!
Good morning, Kazuki.
I can't stop!
I finally stopped...
Hi, you're running late, aren't you?
Ow...
Are you all right?
Yeah, somehow...
This is a man-made island off
the beaten path on the edge of Tokyo.
However!
The time is coming when this island
of cold concrete will be set ablaze!
People will gather, draw manga, search
for manga, get passionate about manga!
A soulful festival of those who have
staked their entire youths on doujinshi!
I'm speaking of...
Comic Party!
Comic Party is now open!
All of a sudden,
you took my hand in yours
So that we wouldn't
get separated in the crowd
I was so happy I couldn't squeeze
your hand very tightly in return
That day, I realized I was in love
We started out as just friends
But now let's cross that boundary line
And take off together
I can't hold my feelings back
anymore It hurts so much I could cry
I love you so much
Listen, I can't lie to myself
This is embarrassing to ask, but
Please accept everything about me
Yes, now and forever
"I Want This Book to Sell!"
Um, what are you doing?
Praying.
Kazuki! Good afternoon!
Hi, Subaru. How are things going?
I see.
Oh yeah! Subaru,
take a look at Aya's book.
It's an original hero story.
What?! It's a hero story?!
Then it will be my pleasure to read it!
This is...
It's amazing! I'm so moved!
I never thought the transformation
item was the sunglasses!
It's, you know...
And it's so cool that his
ponytail turns into a blade too!
It's, you know...
I was so moved
by the effect of the gleaming background
when he revealed his true identity!
It's, you know...
Subaru can't write a manga like this!
You're amazing, Aya!
I'll take it!
T... Two hundred yen.
Wow! Such a great book for only
two hundred yen? What a bargain!
I've become a fan of yours, Aya!
I'm so lucky I was able
to buy it before it sold out!
Actually, that's the only
book we've sold all day.
And it isn't just today.
People just don't seem to
be interested in Aya's books.
That's strange! That's weird!
It's such a good book! Why doesn't it sell?
This must be someone's doing!
A plot by some evil secret society!
That's the only possible explanation!
Who are you?
You... You're an evil villain aren't you?
I, Subaru, shall punish evil!
Wait, Subaru! He's...
Here I come!
I don't know what's going on,
but if you pick a fight with me,
I have no choice but to fight back.
Daiei Ryuu ultimate technique!
Now, Subaru, you know better
than to fight in the exhibition hall.
She's still so naive.
Hello!
Hi, Subaru.
Is Aya here?
Yeah, she's here.
Subaru wants to get more
customers to read your books, Aya.
So I thought the best thing would be
to get advice from popular
authors who will be your teachers!
Teachers?
Yes!
Hi there!
Yu Inagawa is here!
Yu! When did you get in here?
Don't sweat the small
stuff or you'll go bald early.
I invited her from Kobe.
Yu's advice is worth listening to, Aya.
She's helped me out a lot too.
Well, in this industry, ya gotta help
each other out when you're in trouble.
Listen up, Aya.
There's one thing
your doujinshi don't have:
and that's passion!
Passion?
You got it!
Burning passion and
the passion of infatuation!
The strength of your personal
feelings toward the characters!
That's what I mean by passion!
Put that into your pen, then let it
flow onto the blank manuscript paper!
Passionate feelings will draw customers!
Be passionate! Even if it whittles
your life away, be passionate!
Sure, that might be important too, but...
You stay out of it!
The next teacher has arrived!
I am super pissed off!
What's with you?
The great Eimi has come all the way here,
and you can't even come out to greet me?
Quiet down, would ya? Stupid Eimi.
I'm not done with my lecture yet.
What is the hot spring panda doing here?
What about you? Did ya finish all
your homework like you're supposed to?
No problem!
You sure 'bout that?
She's a teacher too?
Don't talk about me that way!
You're no big deal yourself!
Please give us some advice, Ms. Eimi.
Very well.
I, the queen of the doujin world,
the super-popular Eimi Ohba the great,
will give you a special election!
Don't you mean "special lecture"?
If you get a lecture from her,
her dumbness will rub off on ya!
What's with you?
Just scoot on back to the
mountains of Kobe, right now!
Whaddya think you're
doin', ya big dummy?!
What was that, hot spring panda?!
---Panda! Panda! Panda! Panda! Panda!
--Dummy! Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
--Panda! Panda! Panda! Panda!
Would you two cut it out?!
If you're gonna fight, do it outside!
Man, I can't believe those two...
The next teacher is here!
It's him this time?
You seem to be in trouble,
young man and young women.
Why don't I, Taishi Kuhonbutsu,
show you how to catch an otaku's heart?
What kind of contraption
did you make in my room?
And how long have you been there?
My eternal brother,
I am always by your side.
Don't say stuff like that, it creeps me out.
Don't be so heartless, my brother.
Today, we are going to cook this fish.
First, mix this sticky liquid up really well.
Go away!
But comrade! My lecture has just begun.
Shut it!
Now that the fish is nice and brown,
let's pour this liquid
over it nice and thick and...
Yoo-hoo! Sendo!
Not Reiko too...
If you want to stand out, you need this!
It's a plan to draw
customers to your space, Aya.
I guess the plan's not too bad,
but who's going to wear them?
Who do you think?
You don't mean...
Come on, let's try them on!
Hey, wait!
No peeking, Sendo!
You have a nicer figure than I thought!
No, not really...
I might just have to touch...
Thank you for waiting!
It's amazing!
Not bad at all!
Excellent!
It's okay.
When did you guys get back?
Okay, next!
So Sendo, which one
got your blood pumping?
Well, I like...
That's not the point.
Look, Aya looks embarrassed!
Aya, if you don't want
to do this, just say no.
But Reiko...
Oh come on, don't worry so much!
I know you're really
happy deep down anyway!
Kazuki!
I tried making a new recipe!
It doesn't look very good,
but it smells kind of good,
so I think... it's... edible...
Shoulda seen this one coming.
Welcome.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
Come on in.
Say, Kazuki...
Do you feel sick?
I'm fine.
Oh no!
I need something to wipe it with.
Here.
Kazuki? Kazuki?
You're awake?
I...
You had a horrible fever.
Oh, I see.
You have to rest!
But my manuscript got ruined.
If I don't redraw it soon,
I won't make it by the deadline.
Please, rest until your fever breaks.
But...
Please! Please...
Sure...
Okay, I understand.
Thanks.
Well, are you hungry?
I'll make some porridge.
This is...
Kazuki?
Sorry, did I wake you up?
Did you re-draw this?
Yes, does anything look strange about it?
No, it's perfect.
It must have been hard.
But I've only done that one page.
That's plenty!
Thank you. I'll do the rest myself.
You still have a fever.
But if I keep resting,
I won't make it by the deadline.
Don't push yourself. I'll do the rest too.
I can't let you do that. You
won't finish your manuscript in time.
Your health is more important.
You can't do this!
If you don't publish your new book,
Subaru will be so disappointed!
But...
Work on your own manuscript, Aya.
Then...
Then, when your fever breaks,
help me with my manuscript.
But please rest until then.
What do you think of that?
All right, let's do that.
"Send manuscript to printer!!"
"Comipa"
It's done!
Thank you very much!
Just thirty minutes left.
So she didn't do very well today either.
A maid...
She's seriously cute.
Uh, well...
Hey, you guys, you can't just do
something like that without asking!
Be quiet, young man!
I'm curious to see if Aya's book sold well.
Uh huh... Uh huh!
That's...
Aya's in trouble!
Hey! Cut it out, you guys!
Listen you two! You
shouldn't bother other people!
What did you do that for all of a sudden?
I am angry, young woman!
Daiei Ryuu ultimate technique!
Dragon Fang Whirlwind Throw!
I'm flying!
I can fly!
Justice prevails!
Now Subaru, if you don't stop this right
now, I'll be forced to ban you from the hall.
All that commotion's brought
a lot of people around here.
Everyone!
Please take a look at
Jamming Book Store's new issue!
Please! Just a little bit!
Please take a look at her book!
Excuse me, may I take your picture?
Yes...
Well, if you don't mind...
Oh, sure.
Could I see one?
Yes, go ahead.
Hey, this is pretty good. I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
That will be two hundred yen.
Do you mind if I take a look at one?
No, go ahead.
Good work, everyone.
Comic Party is now closed.
We hope to see you again next time.
You didn't sell many after all, huh?
Too bad that crowd
didn't form just a little earlier.
But...
Having my books read
by more people than usual
made me very happy.
It's all thanks to Subaru,
Kazuki, and everyone else.
I hope your books are read by
even more people at the next Comipa.
Kazuki! Aya!
Did your book sell well, Aya?
Oh, I see...
We'll work harder so you
can sell even more the next time!
By the way, Subaru,
how did your book sell?
Well...
I didn't sell even one book.
All right! Then next time it's Subaru's turn!
I look forward to working with you!
Aya, let's do our best together!
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share our smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
I know you don't
like anything complicated
But I still keep on pulling your arms
I finally found this 2LDK
A table set would be fine too
But I think a kotatsu
would be better after all
The time we spend
just lying around together
Is more important than it sounds
It's not easy to find someone
you can always accept
And who will always accept you
But you are that person for me, so
Let's start living together right now
All that's missing is time
Don't you think we need a place
Where we can share smiles,
our tears, and our free time?
If I was with you,
I could stay there forever
You want to go to the beach, don't you?
You want to go to the beach!
What are you talking about?
Like I said!
All right, all right!
I want to go to the beach!
Then I guess there's
no choice. I'll go with you!
Wow! I'm so happy! I get to
go to the beach with the great Eimi!
Be grateful.
But are you sure you'll be okay?
Are you sure you won't
have summer classes?
Gulp!
Next time: "Fumyuun!
Take Me to the Beach!"
I'm going to the beach!